<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
	<reports>
		<report Number="0">
			<summary>Newest android client (1.3.12) crashes on Galaxy Tab</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Just installed the latest version from http://owncloud.org/support/android/ When I try to start it, there's a messagebox saying &quot;the application had to be closed&quot;.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="1">
			<summary>Suggestion to close the bugtracker https://github.com/bartoszprzybylski/owncloud-android/issues</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/4</url>
			<bugID>Issue #4</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		I suggest to close the bugtracker on https://github.com/bartoszprzybylski/owncloud-android/issues for new issues and to monitor and bugtrack everything here on https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues . see bartoszprzybylski/owncloud-android#42
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="2">
			<summary>Files like File_conflict_TIMESTAMP.txt when editing files on the Android device (Jota Text Editor)</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/5</url>
			<bugID>Issue #5</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		While testing the behaviour of down- and uploads with a single file File.txt for editing, I now noticed a spooky file File_conflict_20121030_084503.txt on the Android. I use server 4.5.1a Android 1.3.14 Jota Text Editor (Android) with enabled setting to use abackup version when editing. This editor creates a backup file with filename File.txt~ . Perhaps this backup file (renaming, swapping names of current and backup version ???) is causing the reported issue. In previous tests I disabled the backup file creation in the Jota Text Editor settings and everything (editing on the server, editing in Windows client and editing on the Android device) appeared to work fine, at least I did not notice problems when synchronising the Android client manually - for this see bartoszprzybylski/owncloud-android#43 ) The Delete button however only offers to the delete this particular file on the server(!). The Windows client does not show such a file in the file list. Questions: Please can you explain why the Android client offers &quot;delete on the server&quot; ? Should the text become &quot;delete locally&quot; because there is no File_conflict_TIMESTAMP.txt on the server but a conflicting backup file File.txt~ locally ? [UPDATE] I think I was wrong. The file is indeed on the server. This exact local file name (File.txt~) should be listed locally in the Android client, or File.txt~___conflict_TIMESTAMP [UPDATE] I think I was wrong. The file is indeed on the server.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="3">
			<summary>settings general header</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/27</url>
			<bugID>Issue #27</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		In settings, there is a header »General« up top. This is not really useful since there’s only this one category. The header can be removed.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="4">
			<summary>not possible to delete a folder</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/29</url>
			<bugID>Issue #29</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Am I missing something? Long click doesn’t work.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="5">
			<summary>Android won't work with self-signed ssl certificates</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/33</url>
			<bugID>Issue #33</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Hello, we have a self signed SSL Server for Owncloud in iOS we have no problems with it. But the Android app didn't allow.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="6">
			<summary>Unknown error when fetching http basic auth protected status.php</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/34</url>
			<bugID>Issue #34</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		The android client will try to fetch status.php from the user-provided URL on account creation. If this fails with a 401 HTTP status (Unauthorized), it will show &quot;Unknown error occurred!&quot;. I gave the client the username and password, it should be able to use them and so would be able to fetch status.php and continue. For the situation when there are no or wrong credentials entered, it should show an approriate error message.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="7">
			<summary>Update README.setup or setup_env.sh</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/37</url>
			<bugID>Issue #37</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		I followed the steps discribed in the README.setup. The output of the setup_env.sh is the following: georg@linux:~/workspace/android$ ./setup_env.sh Submodule 'actionbarsherlock' (git://github.com/JakeWharton/ActionBarSherlock.git) registered for path 'actionbarsherlock' Cloning into 'actionbarsherlock'... remote: Counting objects: 17237, done. remote: Compressing objects: 100% (4640/4640), done. remote: Total 17237 (delta 9681), reused 16864 (delta 9407) Receiving objects: 100% (17237/17237), 10.00 MiB | 856 KiB/s, done. Resolving deltas: 100% (9681/9681), done. Submodule path 'actionbarsherlock': checked out '90939dc3925ffaaa0de269bbbe1b35e274968ea1' ./setup_env.sh: Zeile 5: android: Kommando nicht gefunden. ./setup_env.sh: Zeile 6: android: Kommando nicht gefunden. ./setup_env.sh: Zeile 9: android: Kommando nicht gefunden. There are errors because the folders &quot;tools&quot; and &quot;platform-tools&quot; are missing in the PATH. There should be an information that its presupposed.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="8">
			<summary>Possible Support for App Development</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/38</url>
			<bugID>Issue #38</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		There are two very good open-source apps to sync calendars and contacts on android via caldav/carddav, both developed by Marten Gajda (http://dmfs.org/). According to Twitter he is currently working on an extension to sync tasks via caldav as well (caldav-todo app, http://code.google.com/p/caldavtodo/) and is looking for programmers to help him. Maybe this would be a good chance to collaborate and push the integration of calendar/contact/tasks syncing into the owncloud android app? Best, PR
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="9">
			<summary>implement Android Backup Service so that you can have own backups of apps settings</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/43</url>
			<bugID>Issue #43</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		http://developer.android.com/guide/topics/data/backup.html#BackupKey
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="10">
			<summary>Bug: after remove acc,new acc can't connect to server</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/44</url>
			<bugID>Issue #44</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Hi :) I installed the current version of the app on Android Jelly Beans (Asus tf201) .Everything works fine. But I changed the server-address (subdir to a subdomain), so I removed the account settings from the app. After that everything works fine too (other wedav clients and so on) but only the owncloud app doesn't work. The app can't connect to the new and the old server address. I get an unknown error. I reinstalled the app many times (deleted the syncfiles on android too) but every time the same error... As I said every other tool has no problems with the new OR the old settings. What's wrong? Is it a serverside problem? Greetings Edit: I use ownCloud 4.5.3 (current version) Edit2: Same problem in ownCloud 4.5.4
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="11">
			<summary>picture slideshow in android app</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/59</url>
			<bugID>Issue #59</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Hi, wouldn't it be nice to have a picture slideshow in the android app (maybe it the iOs app as well?)? best regards Herbert
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="12">
			<summary>V1.3.17: Synchronisation does not work - no files, no folders</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/65</url>
			<bugID>Issue #65</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		On my HUAWEI Y200, ownCloud resides in the (very small) internal telephone memory. I noticed once more again, that synchronisation does not work any more. When I click &quot;Aktualisieren&quot;, nothing happens. I suppose it has to do with the fact, that on my device only +/- 20 MB RAM are available. However, ownCloud should not silently fail to synchronise on low RAM but should show a suitable message &quot;cannot synchronise because of low RAM&quot; (if this is really the reason. I do not know.)
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="13">
			<summary>&quot;Rename&quot; feature removes slashes from full path of file.</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/68</url>
			<bugID>Issue #68</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		I want to rename the file &quot;wiki/todo.txt&quot; to &quot;dev.txt&quot;. The owncloud app strips off the slashes in the path, so the file is now called &quot;wikidev.txt&quot; and is located in the uppermost level of the WebDAV file structure, instead of in the &quot;wiki&quot; folder.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="14">
			<summary>Android client does not support SSL-SNI (Server name indication)</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/71</url>
			<bugID>Issue #71</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Heyho OC community, I have a bug report/feature request: The Android client does not support SSL-SNI (Server name indication, http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Server_Name_Indication). I am saying this because my Linux client seems to get the correct ssl cert (shared hosting) but my Android client doesn't, very strange. Thx a lot for the good work Laryllian
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="15">
			<summary>License infomation</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/74</url>
			<bugID>Issue #74</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Licensing information are missing. There is no LICENSE file with clear statement over licensing of source code and contributions.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="16">
			<summary>background sync for files that are &quot;kept up to date&quot;</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/82</url>
			<bugID>Issue #82</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		As I need some files to be up2date on my phone, I marked them as &quot;keep file up to date&quot;. The problem is, that this options does not trigger any background sync as I would expect. To automatically update this files I have to open owncloud, insert my PIN and wait for a refresh. So, this option does only keep files up to date after I did some steps manually, every single time. If I need the new version while out of signal, I'm lost.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="17">
			<summary>Feature request: Please enable contacts and calendar sync in Owncloud Android app</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/85</url>
			<bugID>Issue #85</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Hi, I think many people who wish their owncloud Android app be able to sync contacts (with caldav) and calendar (with carddav) with their ownlcoud instance without having to pay for apps such as: for contacts: Caldav-sync which costs 2,55 euro
or Acal Caldav which costs 1,49 euro
or Andal, whose unlock key costs 2,76 euro
 for calendar events: Cardav-sync beta which costs 1,89 euro
 I have searched github for a silimar request but couldn't find it. I hope this is not a double! Thanks in advance!!!
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="18">
			<summary>Connexion code</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/92</url>
			<bugID>Issue #92</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Hi people i search a code source of ownclown client connexion for android. plz help me
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="19">
			<summary>Connexion code</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/93</url>
			<bugID>Issue #93</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Hi people i search a code source of ownclown client's connexion for android. plz help me
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="20">
			<summary>Web address field cannot handle https: schemes</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/99</url>
			<bugID>Issue #99</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		When trying to use https://[...] I get a SSL Exception: Server error:Error: [...]SSL23_GET_SERVER_HELLO:unknown protocol [...] &quot;http://[...]&quot; works.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="21">
			<summary>ownCloud 4.5.7: Nginx + Android + Webdav broken</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/100</url>
			<bugID>Issue #100</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		I am using Nginx, PHP5-FPM and the nginx configuration as suggested in the install guide. Everything seems to work, except connecting with the ownCloud Android App, as the server always responds with HTTP 401 after redirecting with HTTP 301 to HTTPS. Has anybody heard of this? I will continue investigating in the meantime :/ owncloud/core#2002 Might this be a problem with the App? Available at http://owncloud.thomas-steinbrenner.net (test//test)
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="22">
			<summary>Change Local SDCard Folder</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/105</url>
			<bugID>Issue #105</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		I have been interested in owncloud since a few months specially due to its open source android app and that anyone can customize it according to their needs. I am still new to java and programming but have been playing around with the app code to do bit by bit modifications to suit my personal needs. I wanted to change the default owncloud folder location and folder name used by the app to learn more and suit my needs. I have tried to analogize the code and a few java files related to file operations in &quot;src&quot; but wasnt unable to find any hint related to change the folder. Can someone please point me to the file/part of code by which I can modify the name of the folder on localdisk on phone from &quot;owncloud&quot; to something like maybe &quot;cloud&quot; or &quot;instant backup&quot; etc. and secondly change it from / location to something like /folder/folder2/cloud Any help will be appreciated
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="23">
			<summary>.htaccess problem</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/108</url>
			<bugID>Issue #108</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		If I use .htaccess to identify users in owncloud i can't connect to the server with android. Because the popup access window from the web server pops up before it reaches owncloud. This leads to the problem that the connect button keeps unclickable.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="24">
			<summary>Problem to new layout by pressing a button in the Android application</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/114</url>
			<bugID>Issue #114</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Hi I tried putting a new layout by pressing a button in the android application. But I have not been successful. The source code is restricted to create new layout? I can tell the right way to put a new layout by pressing a button? thanks
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="25">
			<summary>android client 1.3.20 crashes unexpectedly when trying to open a folder, or root directory with a new file or files</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/119</url>
			<bugID>Issue #119</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		oc android client 1.3.20 on Android 2.3.6 and Android 4.0.4 The new android client 1.3.20 crashes when I want to open a subfolder with new file/s. This does not happen when using the previous version 1.3.18. There are no errors in the oc server log files.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="26">
			<summary>PHP Fatal error: Allowed memory size of 67108864 bytes exhausted (tried to allocate 64 bytes)</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/126</url>
			<bugID>Issue #126</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		When I access homepage it return 500 error and in error.log of apache2 it has this message I am using version 4.5.7 [Wed Apr 17 11:07:12 2013] [error] [client 127.0.0.1] PHP Fatal error: Allowed memory size of 67108864 bytes exhausted (tried to allocate 64 bytes) in /home/xxx/www/lib/db.php on line 173
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="27">
			<summary>Support for owncloud news</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/128</url>
			<bugID>Issue #128</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Browse, read and share news items from owncloud news.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="28">
			<summary>Crash when opening a big video file</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/134</url>
			<bugID>Issue #134</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Expected behaviour Once synced, video file sized of 120MB should be played from the application Actual behaviour One synced, the application crash instead of playing the video Steps to reproduce Place a large video file on the share (120MB+) Try to download it on the application and play it Server configuration Operating system: Ubuntu 12.04 Web server: Apache 2 Database: Mysql 5.5 PHP version: 5.3 ownCloud version: 5.0.4 Client configuration Browser: Owncloud Android Client Operating system: Android 4.1 Logs Web server error log [None] Insert your webserver log here [None] ownCloud log (data/owncloud.log) Insert your ownCloud log here [None] Browser log Insert your browser log here, this could for example include: [None]
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="29">
			<summary>[Feature] Sync the whole directory</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/135</url>
			<bugID>Issue #135</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		There should have a checkbox on each directories to sync all its content instead of having to open each files to force it to be synced and available offline.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="30">
			<summary>Integrate CALDAV and CARDDAV into Android Client</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/153</url>
			<bugID>Issue #153</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		I am pretty sure that is not a new feature request: But is there any work ongoing with an integration of CALDAV and CARDDAV into Android Client, so no other third party apps are necessary for that?
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="31">
			<summary>Store folder /data into mounted disk</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/157</url>
			<bugID>Issue #157</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Owncloud crushed when moving /data folder to mounted disk. Disk /dev/sdb1 mounted to /data folder in main catalog. Please help me to solve this problem.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="32">
			<summary>Translations are not synced ...</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/171</url>
			<bugID>Issue #171</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		@davivel almost all other ownloud repos are synced every night with transifex.com to get the latest translations. Are you interested in getting this setup as well?
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="33">
			<summary>After connection does not appear any folder</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/174</url>
			<bugID>Issue #174</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Hi dev team, I decided to compile for myself the android client in order to start getting used to the code base and in a near future to contribute to this valuable project. So, the issue i hit is that after the successful login, I don't see any of the folders that I have in my owncloud share. But if I create a file, it will be updated and it will appear into the share. Android version: 1.4.0 (checked the tag oc-android-1.4.0) I tried also the current master. ownCloud server: FreeBSD port of ownCloud + Nginx + MySQL I hope is enough. Feel free to drop a line if something else is needed.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="34">
			<summary>Add Videoupload</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/184</url>
			<bugID>Issue #184</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Would be great if you guys could add support for videouploads in the same way that pictuers are uploaded now in instantupload.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="35">
			<summary>Keep folders in sync</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/194</url>
			<bugID>Issue #194</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		I'd love to see functionality like dropsync has to periodically perform syncs on whole directories recursively. Something like tap and hold on folder -&gt; popup menu shows up with option keep folder in sync. 2-way-sync would be even better (thinking about keepass etc.)
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="36">
			<summary>OC-Application &quot;Store&quot;</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/203</url>
			<bugID>Issue #203</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		There are several Android devices in the family. Somtimes the mobil devices are refreshed, damaged or handed to someone else in the family. Every time the privat information should be cleared, in most cases the Apps are also cleared. So the need to buy apps multiple times over time is evident. To ease and overcome this, I invision to have an app repository in my OC, where all the apps that where bought are residing. Actually the idea is, that there could be a OC-app serving as &quot;buying agent&quot;, that buying agent &quot;installs&quot; the apps into that repository for further use (not as an app that runs in the OC rather an app that will be available for redistribution to be installed on multiple devices, Than another service app in the OC would act as a &quot;market place&quot; that can be accessed by all mobil devices. All devices/users with access to the privat OC-bought apps repository, should be able to access the app market (kind of an internal store, where my Mobil devices could install all apps from this &quot;internal store&quot; - to the device. This is kind of a apps archive and &quot;redistribution&quot; idea for apps in my home mobil device infrastructure.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="37">
			<summary>Poor performance on large file trees</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/207</url>
			<bugID>Issue #207</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		The OwnCloud Android app performs pretty poor on large file trees. FileListListAdapter traverses recursively through all subfolders get the file size of a directory while filling a view in getView(). This results in large database interactions in performance critical sections of the application. There are two possible solutions to this issue: calculate file size of directories on an own Thread. calculate file size of directories while syncing and safe directory size to the database. the latter one should be preferred as it doesn't fuck up the adapter and won't fill up the CPU/RAM/Stack
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="38">
			<summary>wish: possibility to sync folders outside of /owncloud/*</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/209</url>
			<bugID>Issue #209</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		I really much miss the possibility to so select a folder for syncing on Android which is outside the /owncloud-folder. At the moment I still have to use Dropbox for making backups/syncing of appdata (like e.g. Titanium Backup). Many apps have Dropbox implemented which makes it easy to use. But since they are basically just uploading a file/folder, it would be very easy to replace this function by Owncloud, if the Owncloud-syncclient for Android would able to select the folder the data is stored on the phone.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="39">
			<summary>Let user choose what folder in the remote server should be taken as root for synchronization</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/212</url>
			<bugID>Issue #212</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Please add the ability to choose which subfolder inside the owncloud root directory should be synced (as in the PC client). I have several subfolders, some are external storages, and I don't want all of them synced to my mobile device.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="40">
			<summary>App unusably slow / Unjustified &quot;Invalid credentials&quot; after reinstall</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/213</url>
			<bugID>Issue #213</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Expected behaviour App to react in a quick fashion, especially when in the same network as the server, with full WiFi reception. Actual behaviour The app is running unusably slow at the moment. Just when I start it, it takes about half a minute before it shows any folder listing, before it just shows the title bar and white for the rest of the screen. Then when it finally shows the file list, every action (clicking on any folder, clicking the back button, or even just clicking on the settings button or trying to save them) sometimes (every second time or so) takes about 10 seconds... frequently also the popup &quot;App is not reacting. Do you want to close it?&quot; pops up. I have no files which I keep &quot;up to date&quot;, the synchronisation in the account is disabled, I mainly use ownCloud on the android to access one file, which I infrequently manually download; I do have &quot;Instant Upload&quot; enabled (but that doesn't seem to be fully working either, it doesn't upload all my images, only some of them, but that's another story). When I'm saying the app is slow, I mean there is no feedback whatsoever if the app is still doing something (let alone what it is doing), the user interface is just stuck; when coming back from settings it sometimes just turns black for a few seconds... When coming back from the lock screen, I can't even scroll in the file list, I have to wait for a few seconds... Any more information I could provide to help resolve this? The GN shouldn't be that out of date for the app to run so slow? What could cause this? From my momentary perspective also the battery seems to drain quite fast when the app is running... Edit: Clearing the App's data didn't change anything. Will try reinstalling next, just to be sure. Edit 2: Great: After a re-install, it doesn't seem to be able to connect to the account again. It always (first time with the still existing account data, and two more times with the (definitely correctly) entered password) says &quot;invalid credentials&quot;. Edit 3: Removed and recreated the account, restarted the phone, re-tried entering the password several times, but now still just getting an unjustified &quot;Invalid credentials&quot; (the provided credentials are definitely correct). I guess this is basically the worst-case-scenario - going from unusably slow to not usable at all... Any hints what I could try? I've exhausted all usual methods of resolving Android app problems I could think of! Environment data Android version: 4.2.2 Device model: Galaxy Nexus Stock or customized system: Stock ownCloud app version: 1.4.1 ownCloud server version: 5.0.7 Logs Web server error log no relevant entries ownCloud log (data/owncloud.log) no relevant entries
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="41">
			<summary>implement or finish android caldav sync adaptor</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/217</url>
			<bugID>Issue #217</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		this free software project, if developed a bit, would enable syncing owncloud calendars with android's calendar app: https://github.com/gggard/AndroidCaldavSyncAdapater however, it's incomplete. there's no other free software app i know of that allows caldav to be used with android's default calendar. the only other option i know of is acal, and it's got some fairly major issues. it would be really nice if owncloud's calendar could be used on android with free software.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="42">
			<summary>&quot;Unfortunately owncloud has stopped&quot;</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/220</url>
			<bugID>Issue #220</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		upgrade to Android 4.3. Restart. Message displayed: &quot;unfortunately owncloud has stopped&quot; Expected behavior: owncloud should continue to work normally under Android 4.3
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="43">
			<summary>App stop working in Android 4.3</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/221</url>
			<bugID>Issue #221</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		The app crashes upon boot and every time I tried to launch it. Android 4.3 on Nexus 4 (no problem with 4.2.2). I can provide more details, please provide instructions.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="44">
			<summary>Deactivate the built-in ownCloud Music Player?</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/223</url>
			<bugID>Issue #223</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		This is my first time submitting an issue so bear with me. Expected behaviour Able to choose a default app for playing downloaded songs (mp3) instead of the built-in ownCloud music player. Actual behaviour When I try to download or listen to mp3-files that I have already downloaded, ownCloud still tries to open them in the built-in ownCloud music player instead of Google Music that I have choosen as my default player. I have already tried the following from the ownCloud music player: Hit &quot;Menu&quot; &gt; &quot;Open with&quot; and set Google Music as my default/standard player. But ownCloud does not respect this and insists on opening the file with the ownCloud built-in music player first so I have to use the &quot;Open with&quot; every time I want to listen to a mp3 from the ownCloud app. Is there a way to disable the built-in ownCloud music player? Environment data Android version: 4.1.2 Device model: Samsung Galaxy Note II Stock or customized system: Stock ownCloud app version: 1.4.3 ownCloud server version: 5.0.9
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="45">
			<summary>Too much localization on Camera Upload</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/226</url>
			<bugID>Issue #226</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		When Auto-Upload is activated in the app, the images are uploaded to the localized Folder-Name of &quot;InstantUpload&quot;, so devices with different system language sync to different folders, and there is no migration from the old name, so its even a problem when using just one device. so only the display name of the folder should be changed (or not, InstantUpload is just okay), not the name on the server.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="46">
			<summary>Feature Request: Ability to specify where files are synced to</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/229</url>
			<bugID>Issue #229</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Currently, files are synced to /data/owncloud//. It would be handy if you could specify the location where data is synced. I used Dropbox to sync to my SD card so that I could mount it as a USB drive for read-write access.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="47">
			<summary>Jenkins site http://ci.tmit.eu/job/ownCloud-Android/ is down. Please restart.</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/230</url>
			<bugID>Issue #230</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		There was this Jenkins integration site http://ci.tmit.eu/job/ownCloud-Android/ - but why is it down currently ?
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="48">
			<summary>OC not uploading if force closed</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/231</url>
			<bugID>Issue #231</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Suppose OC has been force closed. Then Instant Upload does not upload the picture. -- It is hard to know which pictures have been uploaded and which not. -- it would be nice to make OC sync the whole Camera folder and check which ones have been uploaded, and which ones not.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="49">
			<summary>Sync folders</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/232</url>
			<bugID>Issue #232</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		I would like to sync whole folders on Android with my server. For instance, I can load music in some folder from some computer, and then sync that folder to easily add and remove music from my phone.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="50">
			<summary>Maven compilation fails on MediaService.java:[160,40] cannot find symbol symbol : variable MEDIA_ERROR_UNSUPPORTED</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/233</url>
			<bugID>Issue #233</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		I've been trying to get the project to compile with Maven. I had to upgrade the android-maven-plugin from 3.5.0 to version 3.6.1 to get it to work, but then I end up with the following errors during compilation: [ERROR] COMPILATION ERROR : [INFO] ------------------------------------------------------------- [ERROR] /Users/nodje/Documents/project/ext/owncloud/android/src/com/owncloud/android/media/MediaService.java:[160,40] cannot find symbol symbol : variable MEDIA_ERROR_UNSUPPORTED location: class android.media.MediaPlayer [ERROR] /Users/nodje/Documents/project/ext/owncloud/android/src/com/owncloud/android/media/MediaService.java:[167,40] cannot find symbol symbol : variable MEDIA_ERROR_IO location: class android.media.MediaPlayer [ERROR] /Users/nodje/Documents/project/ext/owncloud/android/src/com/owncloud/android/media/MediaService.java:[174,40] cannot find symbol symbol : variable MEDIA_ERROR_MALFORMED location: class android.media.MediaPlayer [ERROR] /Users/nodje/Documents/project/ext/owncloud/android/src/com/owncloud/android/media/MediaService.java:[181,40] cannot find symbol symbol : variable MEDIA_ERROR_TIMED_OUT location: class android.media.MediaPlayer [INFO] 4 errors
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="51">
			<summary>Android client forgets login data</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/236</url>
			<bugID>Issue #236</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		I'm using the actual client on Android 2.3. The client forgets the login data (server, username and password) after each reboot of the phone. It seems that this happens only if the client is moved to the sd card. It doesn't occur when the app is stored in the phone memory. Any other people with this problem?
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="52">
			<summary>Android client can't connect to my ownCloud</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/238</url>
			<bugID>Issue #238</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Since one of the last updates the client no longer connect to my ownCloud 5.0.9, Android 4.1.2. I just get a &quot;sync error, wrong password&quot; error message. But the password is correct, I double-checked it. Other apps like the third-party carddav and caldav app can connect to my ownCloud just fine. Therefore I assume that it must be client related. I will happily provide more information if needed. Just tell me what you need. For the ssl connection I used a CACert signed certificate, but this was never a problem before. If useful I could also provide a test account on my ownCloud to one of the developers.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="53">
			<summary>caller uid is different than the authenticator's uid</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/248</url>
			<bugID>Issue #248</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		I just installed the owncloud app to my Asus Infinity TF700T Android 4.2.1. I face a problem that owncloud client fails to work after authentication. I have https server, which has several other devices working with the same version of the owncloud app I built myself from source. On the Asus TF700T 4.2.1 I get this: D/ExistenceCheckOperation(22154): Existence check for https://myserver.somewere.net/remote.php/webdav targeting for  existence finished with HTTP status 200
D/AuthenticatorActivity(22154): Successful access - time to save the account
W/AccountManagerService(  491): caller uid 10230 is different than the authenticator's uid
D/AndroidRuntime(22154): Shutting down VM
W/dalvikvm(22154): threadid=1: thread exiting with uncaught exception (group=0x4100d930)
E/AndroidRuntime(22154): FATAL EXCEPTION: main
E/AndroidRuntime(22154): java.lang.SecurityException: caller uid 10230 is different than the authenticator's uid
E/AndroidRuntime(22154):    at android.os.Parcel.readException(Parcel.java:1425)
E/AndroidRuntime(22154):    at android.os.Parcel.readException(Parcel.java:1379)
E/AndroidRuntime(22154):    at android.accounts.IAccountManager$Stub$Proxy.addAccount(IAccountManager.java:613)
E/AndroidRuntime(22154):    at android.accounts.AccountManager.addAccountExplicitly(AccountManager.java:571)
E/AndroidRuntime(22154):    at com.owncloud.android.authentication.AuthenticatorActivity.createAccount(AuthenticatorActivity.java:1038)
E/AndroidRuntime(22154):    at com.owncloud.android.authentication.AuthenticatorActivity.onAuthorizationCheckFinish(AuthenticatorActivity.java:951)
E/AndroidRuntime(22154):    at com.owncloud.android.authentication.AuthenticatorActivity.onRemoteOperationFinish(AuthenticatorActivity.java:658)
E/AndroidRuntime(22154):    at com.owncloud.android.operations.RemoteOperation$1.run(RemoteOperation.java:265)
E/AndroidRuntime(22154):    at android.os.Handler.handleCallback(Handler.java:725)
E/AndroidRuntime(22154):    at android.os.Handler.dispatchMessage(Handler.java:92)
E/AndroidRuntime(22154):    at android.os.Looper.loop(Looper.java:137)
E/AndroidRuntime(22154):    at android.app.ActivityThread.main(ActivityThread.java:5039)
E/AndroidRuntime(22154):    at java.lang.reflect.Method.invokeNative(Native Method)
E/AndroidRuntime(22154):    at java.lang.reflect.Method.invoke(Method.java:511)
E/AndroidRuntime(22154):    at com.android.internal.os.ZygoteInit$MethodAndArgsCaller.run(ZygoteInit.java:793)
E/AndroidRuntime(22154):    at com.android.internal.os.ZygoteInit.main(ZygoteInit.java:560)
E/AndroidRuntime(22154):    at dalvik.system.NativeStart.main(Native Method)
W/ActivityManager(  491):   Force finishing activity com.owncloud.android/.authentication.AuthenticatorActivity
D/WindowManager(  491): adjustConfigurationLw, config:{1.0 ?mcc?mnc ?locale ?layoutDir sw800dp w1280dp h752dp 240dpi xlrg land ?uimode ?night finger qwerty/v/v -nav/v} mLidState:1 mHasDockFeature:true mHasKeyboardFeature:true mHasHallSensorFeature:true config.hardKeyboardHidden:1
W/ActivityManager(  491): Activity pause timeout for ActivityRecord{41987450 u0 com.owncloud.android/.authentication.AuthenticatorActivity}
 Any ideas why? The same owcloud-release.apk works on several other devices in family, galaxy III, asus tf101 with CM10, some CM7 phones. The source is of todays version 112cc0f, the master branch. I have also some &quot;ownCloud Jelly Bean Workaround for lost credentials&quot; app installed from play store.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="54">
			<summary>Enhancement: allow folders to be synchronized automatically.</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/254</url>
			<bugID>Issue #254</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Consider the following use case: I use my device as an offline reader for PDFs that I find throughout the day on my desktop. When I find a document that I want to read later, I copy it to an ownCloud-shared folder. When I get to my Android device, I want all files collected during the day to be available on it, even in offline mode. Currently I have to perform the following tiresome sequence on the device: Press &quot;Update&quot; and wait until finishes Open the folder used to store new documents Click on each of the documents so that it gets downloaded and opened in a PDF viewer Close the viewer and proceed to the next file. When there are more than a couple of new files this sequence becomes a really boring thing to do. What I want to suggest is that certain folders can be marked as auto-update, just like it can be done for individual files today. The above scenario becomes much more simple: 0. Mark a folder as &quot;auto-update&quot; (once) Press &quot;Update&quot; and wait until all new files are downloaded to the device.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="55">
			<summary>Purchased app refuses to work without logging in to Amazon App-Shop</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/256</url>
			<bugID>Issue #256</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		After using Owncloud on my Windows-PC I purchased the Android Owncloud App from the Amazon App Shop. I got it to work without problem. Today when I wanted to use it on my Android Tablet again I got a notice that this app needs that I am logged in to the Amazon-App-Shop to work. ????????? After some time then I get a notice that an internal error has happened. I do not want to login to the Amazon Shop if I do not want to buy anything there. Is this a walware which wants to fish my Amazon login data? Franz47 Franz47 Newbie Beiträge: 2
Registriert: Mo Jul 22, 2013 5:31 pm
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="56">
			<summary>latest version 1.4.5 from Google Play always crashes on startup</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/260</url>
			<bugID>Issue #260</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		The latest version in the Google Play store ( 1.4.5 from 18. September 2013) crashes on startup, also delete all app files and cashes isn't working. On Android 4.3, Nexus 4.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="57">
			<summary>[newbie] Instructions for building integrating with actionbarsherlock</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/262</url>
			<bugID>Issue #262</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		I am a beginner in developing android apps in general. I downloaded the Eclipse ADT from google. I got most of anything available of the SDKs, the different versions and API releases, via the SDK manager. I got the sources for OC android app from git/here. It is mentioned actionbarsherlock but incidentally the corresponding folder here is empty. I went here: http://actionbarsherlock.com/download.html I got the actionbarsherlock tarball which I tried to integrate with owncloud android. I failed. There definitely is something I am not doing right to integrate the two and finalise a buildable owncloud app. Is it possible to have some instructions for beginners on how to build the downloaded projects fresh as they are from source? Some instructions which when followed on fresh installs/setups, would get the source to build successfully? I feel very disheartened that a copy-paste style of building an existing project, on a fresh environment, by following the available instructions, fails. Can there be some more detailed instructions on what does the owncloud android app need and depends on? (Such as actionbarsherlock). How to properly integrate them and result in a buildable OC app project from the main source, vanilla as is?
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="58">
			<summary>Android app don't login (IMAP user backend)</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/264</url>
			<bugID>Issue #264</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Hi, i'm running owncloud 5.0.11 with IMAP user backend. Login over web browser (on PC and Android), CalDAV on Android works fine. But ownCloud app do not login, it print &quot;Wrong username or password&quot;. When i use account from internal database (admin account) it login and synchronize successfully. android app version 1.4.5
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="59">
			<summary>Instantupload from Android 4.2.x does not work</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/275</url>
			<bugID>Issue #275</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		I have OC server v5.0.12 running. When I install the latest available client from Google Play on a cell phone Goggle Nexus with Android 4.1.2 the instantupload of photos works great. When I try a Samsung Galaxy S3 with Android 4.2.2 the instantupload does NOT work. Has anything changed in Android 4.2.2? Is it possible to update the client to fix this bug?
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="60">
			<summary>Branch refresh_folder_contents_when_browsed_into</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/288</url>
			<bugID>Issue #288</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Very nice work! 3 thoughts: The update procedure seems to be called even when there is no Internet connection (at least the update circle is shown for a moment before it disappears). This does not happen when manually initiating a &quot;refresh account&quot;. Is there a check for Internet connectivity? Can it also be used to this &quot;refresh_folder_contents_when_browsed_into&quot; feature? Folders are refreshed when browsed into. But also when coming out. It that necessary? When you step down the folder hierarchy, you usually just stepped up moments before, didn't you? So could here bandwidth be saved (for sacrificing a little freshness)?
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="61">
			<summary>Sync contacts</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/290</url>
			<bugID>Issue #290</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Right now it seems that it is not possible to sync my list of contacts. As the appropriate support on the server side is already there, it would be great if the Android application could make use of this.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="62">
			<summary>Uninstall doesn't remove the account in settings</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/297</url>
			<bugID>Issue #297</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		While trying to get my auto-image-upload to run again I uninstalled the app. While doing that I found out that the account doesn't get removed. Android 4.1.2
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="63">
			<summary>Path for Instant-Upload-Folder</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/332</url>
			<bugID>Issue #332</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Provide an option to specify the InstantUpload-Folder. It would be nice if it wouldn't be just the hardcoded locale-dependent like SofortUpload. I've got the need, that I have to sort all data of my phone in on one folder and in another the data of my Laptop, so it would be nice, if the DirectUpload function would move the file automatically into a nested tree, without doing manual actions. Use something like a menu, which chooses a folder and use only as default the folder SofortUpload.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="64">
			<summary>Development using IntelliJ / Android Studio</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/338</url>
			<bugID>Issue #338</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Are there any instructions available how to setup the project in IntelliJ?
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="65">
			<summary>Download/Sync a folder to disk</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/343</url>
			<bugID>Issue #343</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Being able to download/synchronize an entire folder on android would be a very usefull feature. Use case: We have a tablet that we use for photo presentations. if it would automatically update when we added new images to our owncloud gallery it would save a lot of time :-)
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="66">
			<summary>F-droid version</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/373</url>
			<bugID>Issue #373</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		The version on f-droid repo is still 1.5.2. Is there a reason ? On play store it's 1.5.3.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="67">
			<summary>Sync contact</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/409</url>
			<bugID>Issue #409</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Hello, I want to know is ownCloud have the sync contact function on android device yet? Best regards
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="68">
			<summary>Adding a local folder downloads entire folder from server</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/417</url>
			<bugID>Issue #417</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		I have a local folder. In that folder i created a folder with content. At the next sync, the client downloaded te complete folder. The owncloud webinterface shows that all the files and folders have not changed within a year (wich is correct) and the new local folder is uploaded. I did not login in the webinterface that day and there are no other users using that folder. I use ownCloud 5.0.14a on Apache an Ubuntu 12 Client is Windows 8 Owncloud client is 1.5.2 buiold 2445 (the latest at this moment)
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="69">
			<summary>S4 and App for OwnCloud blank screen after login</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/421</url>
			<bugID>Issue #421</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Dear reader, i searched the forums and found similar problems but no real fix for it. I have a Galaxy S4 and Owncloud installed on Linux. The owncloud is functioning fine, i can login with the App on Samsung S3, S2 and Webdav on win7 and with webbrowsers. So the problems doesnt seem to be in the server but on the S4. The S4 has Android version 4.3 on it. What happens is, as soon as i open the App (after i put in the server and password) a blank screen comes with the little Cloud in the Top and thats it. After that it does nothing. Does anyone has any ideas on how to fix this ? Thank you very much for your response in advance. And i already tried de-install and re-install etc. P.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="70">
			<summary>Is move feature coming to Andriod ?</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/422</url>
			<bugID>Issue #422</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		It would be great to have move features on Andriod App.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="71">
			<summary>Android app direct sharing of images</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/425</url>
			<bugID>Issue #425</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		I use the ownCloud app for android version 1.5.4 on my Google Nexus 5 (Kitkat 4.4.2). Somehow direct sharing of images doesn't work, no error whatsoever or at least not on screen or in the logs I viewed. Looks like the OC server isn't even accessed. For example I open gallery, choose a picture, choose owncloud in the sharing menu. Owncloud opens, I browse to my photo folder and click on upload. Nothing at all, again not even an error. Other types of files do work.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="72">
			<summary>Reply to mails please</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/428</url>
			<bugID>Issue #428</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		In the OwnCloud app there is a way to send a mail to apps@owncloud.com. Some kind of answer would be nice within one week.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="73">
			<summary>Enormous battery drain</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/431</url>
			<bugID>Issue #431</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		The app should never start itself when photo upload is disabled. At the moment the app (1.5.4) consumes most of the battery capacity even when it does not seem to run. Deleting Owncloud folder, &quot;App data&quot;, &quot;Cache&quot; and rebooting does not help. Astonishingly, after doing all this the app still has my credentials and lists my server's data. I will wait with uninstalling to provide more information if needed. The loading circle in the app always rotates. Maybe this is helpful.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="74">
			<summary>ownCloud app crashes</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/446</url>
			<bugID>Issue #446</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Hello, on Android 2.2 I have always crashes with ownCloud app in Version 1.5.4 while syncing from server to smartphone. I'm not able to send a report, because the popup window disappear before I can press a button.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="75">
			<summary>Cannot download 26Byte file</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/449</url>
			<bugID>Issue #449</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		I created a new text file, via owncloud's web interface (New -&gt; Text file). The resulting file is 26 bytes long. Downloading it via the android client is impossible (F-Droid , version 1.5.4) Tried a 1024 byte dummy file and it works. Is there a bottom limit at work I am not aware of? ownCloud 6.0.2 (stable) - running in debian 7, nginx 1.4.4
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="76">
			<summary>auto upload with Date Folder</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/467</url>
			<bugID>Issue #467</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Hello, is it possible to upload new pictures/Videos to an Folder within the upload Date?
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="77">
			<summary>Instant upload on Wifi does not check for connection</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/473</url>
			<bugID>Issue #473</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		When having the option &quot;only upload when on wifi&quot; checked i noticed a small problem when being abroad. Most hotel-wifis are open wifis but they need some kind of login through the browser. Owncloud client only checks to see if its connected to a wifi, when it actually should be checking if it is connected to internet(or atleast the owncloud server). Having used the camera quite alot the result was hundreds of notifications of failed uploads.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="78">
			<summary>Android auto upload not work in russia lang</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/478</url>
			<bugID>Issue #478</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		No description provided.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="79">
			<summary>F-Droid-Version still 1.5.4</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/479</url>
			<bugID>Issue #479</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		In GPlay the current version 1.5.5 is since much time, but in F-Droid there is still this old version. Is it possible for you to trigger an update?
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="80">
			<summary>Change Direct Upload-Folder</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/483</url>
			<bugID>Issue #483</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Current Behaviour 👎 There is only the predefined folder &quot;DirectUpload&quot; (in German &quot;SofortUpload&quot;). Expected Behaviour 👍 I am able to set in the settings the target-directory, where all my direct uploads are uploaded to. So i would be able to set my folder &quot;Images&quot;. And if i shoot a photo with my mobile phone camera, the taken photo will be uploaded directly to my &quot;Images&quot;-Folder.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="81">
			<summary>tls 1.2 support</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/484</url>
			<bugID>Issue #484</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		No description provided.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="82">
			<summary>High background data usage</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/515</url>
			<bugID>Issue #515</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		I was going over my data limit really early in the month and I've found that even with mobile upload off Owncloud has used 550mb in 20 days. This is with one account and no usage outside wifi except a few browses and downloads. Is there a way to work out how this is happening? I would have expected usage closer to 100mb with my usage of the app. Could the account sync be parsing my whole file database regularly? I have about 30gb in my Owncloud.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="83">
			<summary>&quot;Retry&quot; on failed upload</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/523</url>
			<bugID>Issue #523</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		I enabled InstantUpload and one file failed to upload. Then I clicked on the notification, which shows a notification. As a user it would be nice to have a retry button besides the dismiss button. The screenshot is from yesterday morning (maybe not the current version, which was released this weekend)
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="84">
			<summary>Reusing account data between different ownCloud apps</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/525</url>
			<bugID>Issue #525</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		The ownCloud newsreader app from @David-Development contains a function to import the credentials from other ownCloud apps. It would be awesome to share that code between the different apps that uses ownCloud. Otherwise the user have to type in the same credentials in each app. Is this possible to co-work on this?
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="85">
			<summary>Upload does not work</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/545</url>
			<bugID>Issue #545</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		I have tested my WebDAV installation by using Cyberduck, and everything works. Expected behaviour Photos are uploaded when captured, and files are uploaded when requested in the app. Actual behaviour Instant upload does not work and upload does not work (0% upload on Android) Steps to reproduce Open the app Try to upload a file Environment data Android version: 4.4.3 Device model: Nexus 4 Stock or customized system: Paranoid Android 4.4 RC2 (happens in CM11 also) ownCloud app version: 1.5.7 ownCloud server version: 6.0.3 Logs Web server error log Nothing strange
 ownCloud log (data/owncloud.log) {&quot;app&quot;:&quot;webdav&quot;,&quot;message&quot;:&quot;Sabre_DAV_Exception_NotFound: File with name pa_gapps (42).log could not be located&quot;,&quot;level&quot;:4,&quot;time&quot;:&quot;2014-06-20T15:45:32+00:00&quot;}
{&quot;app&quot;:&quot;webdav&quot;,&quot;message&quot;:&quot;Sabre_DAV_Exception_NotFound: File with name pa_gapps (43).log could not be located&quot;,&quot;level&quot;:4,&quot;time&quot;:&quot;2014-06-20T15:45:33+00:00&quot;}
{&quot;app&quot;:&quot;webdav&quot;,&quot;message&quot;:&quot;Sabre_DAV_Exception_NotFound: File with name pa_gapps (44).log could not be located&quot;,&quot;level&quot;:4,&quot;time&quot;:&quot;2014-06-20T15:45:33+00:00&quot;}
{&quot;app&quot;:&quot;webdav&quot;,&quot;message&quot;:&quot;Sabre_DAV_Exception_NotFound: File with name pa_gapps (45).log could not be located&quot;,&quot;level&quot;:4,&quot;time&quot;:&quot;2014-06-20T15:45:33+00:00&quot;}
{&quot;app&quot;:&quot;webdav&quot;,&quot;message&quot;:&quot;Sabre_DAV_Exception_NotFound: File with name pa_gapps (46).log could not be located&quot;,&quot;level&quot;:4,&quot;time&quot;:&quot;2014-06-20T15:45:34+00:00&quot;}
{&quot;app&quot;:&quot;webdav&quot;,&quot;message&quot;:&quot;Sabre_DAV_Exception_NotFound: File with name pa_gapps (47).log could not be located&quot;,&quot;level&quot;:4,&quot;time&quot;:&quot;2014-06-20T15:45:34+00:00&quot;}
{&quot;app&quot;:&quot;webdav&quot;,&quot;message&quot;:&quot;Sabre_DAV_Exception_NotFound: File with name pa_gapps (48).log could not be located&quot;,&quot;level&quot;:4,&quot;time&quot;:&quot;2014-06-20T15:45:34+00:00&quot;}
{&quot;app&quot;:&quot;webdav&quot;,&quot;message&quot;:&quot;Sabre_DAV_Exception_NotFound: File with name pa_gapps (49).log could not be located&quot;,&quot;level&quot;:4,&quot;time&quot;:&quot;2014-06-20T15:45:34+00:00&quot;}
{&quot;app&quot;:&quot;webdav&quot;,&quot;message&quot;:&quot;Sabre_DAV_Exception_NotFound: File with name pa_gapps (50).log could not be located&quot;,&quot;level&quot;:4,&quot;time&quot;:&quot;2014-06-20T15:45:35+00:00&quot;}
 This is an endless loop, until I manually Force Close the app from the apps dialog (but the app IS NOT STUCK)
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="86">
			<summary>Wrong downloading status 2147483647%</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/548</url>
			<bugID>Issue #548</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Trying to download a 12MB .doc file shows a wrong % number on the status bar. https://imgur.com/dZ544IA Nexus 5 Android 4.4.4 Owncloud client 1.5.7
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="87">
			<summary>Cahnge priority between upload and download cahnges</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/553</url>
			<bugID>Issue #553</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		The client should first upload his new data before downloading new ones from server. Use case: I use owncloud has a backup solution. Client1 uploaded a huge amount of photos. Client2 start and creates importants files, but they won't be upload to the server (thus backedup) until the whole photos are downloaded (which can take hours) Owncloud client 1.6.1 on windows 7
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="88">
			<summary>APK on Amazon Appstore is out of date</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/561</url>
			<bugID>Issue #561</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		I've bought it on the Amazon Appstore and it's never updated, contrary to the version on Play. BlackBerry will source its apps from the Appstore, so it would be great if releases could be made on all stores at the same time. Thanks!
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="89">
			<summary>Images not rotated based on EXIF in photo view</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/567</url>
			<bugID>Issue #567</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		ownCloud 7 Android App 1.5.7 I noticed pulling down images from my server that the app is not rotating them based on the EXIF data. When viewing the same files from the gallery app on android rotation is working, so the app is the issue not the files.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="90">
			<summary>Sharing notes from Evernote to ownCloud does not work</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/568</url>
			<bugID>Issue #568</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Expected behaviour When I share something from Evernote to ownCloud, I'd expect it would create a text file or document with the note contents, or give a meaningful error message, or not be present in the &quot;Share to...&quot; list in the first place. Actual behaviour The following error message appears: No content to upload No content was received. Nothing to upload. Steps to reproduce Open Evernote Long-tap a note Select Share Select ownCloud Environment data Android version: 4.4.2 Device model: Samsung Galaxy Note 3 Stock or customized system: Stock ownCloud app version: 1.5.8 (debug build from yesterday's git master) ownCloud server version: N/A Logs Web server error log N/A ownCloud log (data/owncloud.log) How do I get this? Here's a logcat excerpt instead: D/SSRMv2:CustomFrequencyManagerService(  870): acquireDVFSLockLocked : type : DVFS_MIN_LIMIT  frequency : 1958400  uid : 1000  pid : 870  pkgName : ACTIVITY_RESUME_BOOSTER@6
W/ActivityManager(  870): mDVFSHelper.acquire()
W/GA-SERVICE( 1610): Thread[Thread-100,5,main]:  Using destination https://ssl.google-analytics.com
W/ContextImpl(  870): Calling a method in the system process without a qualified user: android.app.ContextImpl.sendBroadcast:1468 com.android.server.am.ActivityStack.startPausingLocked:1002 com.android.server.am.ActivityStack.resumeTopActivityLocked:1906 com.android.server.am.ActivityStackSupervisor.resumeTopActivitiesLocked:2997 com.android.server.am.ActivityStackSupervisor.resumeTopActivitiesLocked:2975
D/PointerIcon(  870): setHoveringSpenIconStyle1 pointerType: 10001iconType:1 flag:0
D/PointerIcon(  870): setHoveringSpenCustomIcon IconType is same.1
V/SmartFaceService - 3rd party pause(  870): onReceive [android.intent.action.ACTIVITY_STATE/com.evernote/pause]
W/ApplicationPackageManager(21977): getCSCPackageItemText()
W/ContextImpl(  870): Calling a method in the system process without a qualified user: android.app.ContextImpl.sendBroadcast:1468 com.android.server.am.ActivityStackSupervisor.realStartActivityLocked:1143 com.android.server.am.ActivityStackSupervisor.startSpecificActivityLocked:1286 com.android.server.am.ActivityStack.resumeTopActivityLocked:2223 com.android.server.am.ActivityStackSupervisor.resumeTopActivitiesLocked:2997
V/SmartFaceService - 3rd party pause(  870): onReceive [android.intent.action.ACTIVITY_STATE/com.owncloud.android/create]
D/AbsListView(27649): onVisibilityChanged() is called, visibility : 4
D/AbsListView(27649): unregisterIRListener() is called
I/SpenGestureManager(  870): setFocusWindow0
D/EnterpriseDeviceManager(  870): ContainerId: 0
D/PointerIcon(  870): setHoveringSpenIconStyle1 pointerType: 10001iconType:1 flag:0
D/PointerIcon(  870): setHoveringSpenCustomIcon IconType is same.1
D/STATUSBAR-StatusBarManagerService(  870): manageDisableList what=0x0 pkg=WindowManager.LayoutParams
I/SurfaceFlinger(  276): id=401 createSurf (1x1),1 flag=4, Vploader
I/SurfaceFlinger(  276): id=402 createSurf (1080x1920),1 flag=404, Vploader
I/SurfaceFlinger(  276): id=399 Removed OoteShareSe (23/28)
I/SurfaceFlinger(  276): id=399 Removed OoteShareSe (-2/28)
I/SurfaceFlinger(  276): id=398 Removed QhoneMainAc (22/27)
I/SurfaceFlinger(  276): id=398 Removed QhoneMainAc (-2/27)
D/dalvikvm(  870): GC_FOR_ALLOC freed 3514K, 19% free 73212K/90012K, paused 114ms, total 114ms
D/SSRMv2:CustomFrequencyManagerService(  870): releaseDVFSLockLocked : Getting Lock type frm List : DVFS_MIN_LIMIT  frequency : 1958400  uid : 1000  pid : 870  tag : ACTIVITY_RESUME_BOOSTER@6
W/ActivityManager(  870): mDVFSHelper.release()
D/SSRMv2:CustomFrequencyManagerService(  870): acquireDVFSLockLocked : type : DVFS_MIN_LIMIT  frequency : 1958400  uid : 1000  pid : 870  pkgName : ACTIVITY_RESUME_BOOSTER@9
W/ApplicationPackageManager( 2523): getCSCPackageItemText()
D/SSRMv2:CustomFrequencyManagerService(  870): releaseDVFSLockLocked : Getting Lock type frm List : DVFS_MIN_LIMIT  frequency : 1958400  uid : 1000  pid : 870  tag : ACTIVITY_RESUME_BOOSTER@9
W/EDMNativeHelper(  266): EDMNativeHelperService is published
D/SSRMv2:Monitor(  870): SIOP:: AP = 380, Prev AP = 390, Duration = 10048, PST = 384
D/SSRMv2:AmoledAdjustTimer(  870): prevTemp = 339, currTemp = 339, prevStep = 5, currStep = 5
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="91">
			<summary>Sync Local File Directory AND Remote Directory together</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/572</url>
			<bugID>Issue #572</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		This is more of a feature than an issue, but it could be of some relevance to the automatic photo/video uploader. There needs to be a way where we can select a local directory and a remote directroy so that they can be synced either both ways, or just to the remote/local folder (a bit like FolderSync) since if the app wasn't running, then not all my photos/videos would be uploaded and since the app doesn't search for any new media, then they won't be uploaded to the server. It'd be great if this was up in the high priority list, but I know that there may be higher priorities already queued up.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="92">
			<summary>can't use android client to create a new account</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/574</url>
			<bugID>Issue #574</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		I can't use android client to create a new account (not add an account). The client returns &quot;username or passowrd not match&quot;.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="93">
			<summary>needs .nomedia in the owncloud directory</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/580</url>
			<bugID>Issue #580</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		So pictures do not show up in the gallery.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="94">
			<summary>[feature request] WLAN folder/all auto-sync</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/581</url>
			<bugID>Issue #581</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Hi, would it be possible to implement a function to auto-download and -sync all files on the cloud or in specific folders, so i don't have to select every file specifically? Sometimes i only have 3g or less, so downloading the files i need either takes forever or doesn't work at all when i need them. It would be nice if i would be able to autosync them while i have wifi and have them on my device when i need them. regards sicjay
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="95">
			<summary>Don't instantly save a second copy of an image to instantUpload on the phone</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/589</url>
			<bugID>Issue #589</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		After recently getting the ownCloud app on Android and enabling instant photo upload, I noticed that after taking a picture the app is automatically saving a copy of the picture in the owncloud folder on the phones memory, even though I haven't gone to view/download the photo in the app. Since I take a lot of photos this is just wasting space on the phone. Its also not likely I'm going to use the ownCloud app to view the photo if I can view it from the Android photo app anyway, so there isn't really any reason for them to be there. It would be nice to have the option to disable this if not have it removed as it probably doesn't make sense for a lot of people to do this.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="96">
			<summary>InstantUpload default folder</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/593</url>
			<bugID>Issue #593</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		owncloud should provide a way to use custom upload folders and dated folders like &quot;CustomName/Videos/Date&quot; and CustomName/Pictures/Date to help organizing.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="97">
			<summary>about class ContactSyncService</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/599</url>
			<bugID>Issue #599</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		How to start this service,I cann't start with using bindService, Can you help me ?
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="98">
			<summary>The InstantUpload feature is localised. This causes minor problems with language settings.</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/606</url>
			<bugID>Issue #606</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		When taking a picture with my phone, the image is instantly uploaded to owncloud\SofortUpload, since I got my device set on German. Today I changed the device to French - Pictures now arrive in owncloud\TéléversementInstantané. Maybe some of these options would improve the situation? Stick to a language, when it was already used once. Create a setting value for the name of the directory.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="99">
			<summary>Folders not updated when sharing</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/623</url>
			<bugID>Issue #623</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Using version: 1.5.8 When selecting a file for sharing in Android and chosing owncloud, folders are not refreshed. In my case, with a fresh installation owncloud only showed me the top level folder hierarchie, but when selecting a folder it appeared empty. Could the current folder be refreshed just like when opening it with the owncloud app?
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="100">
			<summary>Support TLSv1.2 ciphers (Android 4.4.*)</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/629</url>
			<bugID>Issue #629</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Steps to reproduce Install oc-android (v1.5.8) Try to add a Server which only supports TLSv1.2 Ciphers Expected behaviour Android 4.4.* supports TLSv1.2 so it should work with the following ciphers: TLS_ECDHE_RSA_WITH_AES_256_GCM_SHA384 TLS_ECDHE_RSA_WITH_AES_128_GCM_SHA256 TLS_DHE_RSA_WITH_AES_256_GCM_SHA384 TLS_DHE_RSA_WITH_AES_128_GCM_SHA256 TLS_ECDHE_RSA_WITH_AES_256_CBC_SHA384 TLS_ECDHE_RSA_WITH_AES_256_CBC_SHA TLS_DHE_RSA_WITH_AES_256_CBC_SHA256 TLS_DHE_RSA_WITH_AES_256_CBC_SHA TLS_ECDHE_RSA_WITH_AES_128_CBC_SHA256 TLS_ECDHE_RSA_WITH_AES_128_CBC_SHA TLS_DHE_RSA_WITH_AES_128_CBC_SHA256 TLS_DHE_RSA_WITH_AES_128_CBC_SHA Actual behaviour SSL-Initialisation fails Server configuration Operating system: Centos 6.5 Web server: nginx 1.7.5 Database: mysql PHP version: 5.3.3 ownCloud version: 7.0.2
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="101">
			<summary>Client does not always upload pdf files upon modification</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/647</url>
			<bugID>Issue #647</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		I am using the android client (v.1.5.8 from f-droid) on a Samsung Note 8 (android v. 4.2.2) and I am trying to keep some pdf files in sync. I expect files to automatically syncronize to the server after I add annotations or highlights, i.e. files should be uploaded soon after they are modified. However, this does not happen, not even if I force a sync tapping on &quot;Refresh account&quot;. When I check the modification time of the pdfs using a file browser, I can see the modification time is older than the one shown in the client. The only workaround I found is (1) to manually force a sync by long tapping the file and then choosing &quot;Refresh file&quot; or (2) to force the sync of another file in the same folder as in (1), then the other files are uploaded after I modified them (this seems to work consistently, at least as far as I could test) I don't have similar problems with other types of files, for instance text files are uploaded immediately after modification. Also there is nothing suspicious in owncloud.log on the server.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="102">
			<summary>Question: When will there be a next release?</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/650</url>
			<bugID>Issue #650</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Long time now since 1.5.8 was released, and what updates can we count with?
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="103">
			<summary>Music stops playing when upload notification appears</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/670</url>
			<bugID>Issue #670</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		UPDATE: Seems to be a general Android issue not necessarily due to Owncloud. I have problems with Owncloud on my Nexus 5. Whenever I listen to music and owncloud tries uploading a foto my music stops playing. I am not sure if it only happens when the upload fails or in general when uploading but it is really annoying!
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="104">
			<summary>Upload not possible when SSLv3 is disabled</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/679</url>
			<bugID>Issue #679</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Due to the recent poodle exploit I disabled SSLv3 in my apache configuration. Unfortunately after that uploading files doesn't work anymore with the OC Android client. Steps to reproduce: Having these lines in the apache virtual host configuration works: SSLCipherSuite ECDH+AESGCM:DH+AESGCM:ECDH+AES256:DH+AES256:ECDH+AES128:DH+AES:ECDH+3DES:DH+3DES:RSA+AESGCM:RSA+AES:RSA+3DES:!aNULL:!MD5:!DSS
SSLCipherSuite ALL:!ADH:!EXPORT56:!RC4+RSA:+HIGH:-MEDIUM:+EXP:+eNULL:-SSLv2:SSLv3
 Disabling SSLv3 like this will not work: SSLCipherSuite ECDH+AESGCM:DH+AESGCM:ECDH+AES256:DH+AES256:ECDH+AES128:DH+AES:ECDH+3DES:DH+3DES:RSA+AESGCM:RSA+AES:RSA+3DES:!aNULL:!MD5:!DSS
SSLCipherSuite ALL:!ADH:!EXPORT56:!RC4+RSA:+HIGH:-MEDIUM:+EXP:+eNULL:-SSLv2:-SSLv3
 My Environment Apache:   apache2 -version
  Server version: Apache/2.2.22 (Debian)
  Server built:   Jul 24 2014 15:34:00
 Android with cyanogenmod 10.1.3-n7000 on a Samsung Galaxy Note OC Android client 1.5.8
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="105">
			<summary>What could be improved or added as a new feature to make Android client better?</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/705</url>
			<bugID>Issue #705</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		This issue is meant to discuss improvements in the Android Client. I posted a workaround before, little bit like a wake up call to that many users request one thing, but nothing happens. This is purely a discussion, and nothing else. It´s not personal against anyone either. I just want to make it clear what is missing, and what would improve the client - a lot. PR´s are more than welcome. As I see it today we are missing or could improve: Photos and videos gets downloaded and is stored both in the regular photos folder of the phone in DCIM, and also by ownCloud client in &quot;Misc&quot;. #588 #592 #640 #601 #346 #156 #375 When a photo or video is taken and fails, it should retry again. #340 #646 Add a delay for Instant Uploads so you have time to delete the photos you don´t want before they get uploaded to the server. #643 A &quot;smart upload&quot; that get´s information from server and don´t upload it if there already is a copy, or upload it once more and overwrite the old file, or make a new copy, and only one copy in that case. #554 Only upload when phone is charging. #465 Two-way sync. #3 Browse the pictures without downloading them, instead - get the information from the server directly. #588 Delete the picture from phone (DCIM folder) after it have successfully been uploaded. #588 This is what my workaround fixes. But it should not have to be a workaround, it should be native, in the original ownCloud app. New suggestions: Download a folder - this is quite nice as people might have 100 mp3s in one folder for example. (Thanks @wakeup) ______________ Questions to begin with: Why haven´t this been prioritized before? What obstacles is present to make this happen? Why is this bad ideas design-wise? Why is so many users not being listened to? My intentions are good, and have always been. I spend 95% of my free time on/with ownCloud, of course I want to make it better but right now it feels like there are many different ways to deal (or not deal) with these issues. Could we please talk it through? CCing all that could be interested in this: @jancborchardt @davivel @lukeowncloud @stefan-niedermann @tobiasKaminsky @owncloud/designers
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="106">
			<summary>OwnCloudClient.executeMethod() generates invalid HTTP requests</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/720</url>
			<bugID>Issue #720</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Hello, I am preparing a pull request for displaying users's quota used/left. To do so I created a new RemoteOperation copying the GetRemoteUserNameOperation available. However, I am continuously getting 400 Bad Response back from the server, while with a simple Curl everything works nice and smooth. Since with a basic inspection of the headers I couldn't figure out I sniffed my own packets with Wireshark and found the problem: Working request: http://en.zimagez.com/zimage/rightreq.php Non working request: http://en.zimagez.com/zimage/wrongreq.php If you want to try it out we have a server up and running at 54.77.93.38 user/pass = demo demo . And finally here is the code I used: curl that works: curl -H &quot;Authorization: Basic ZGVtbzpkZW1v&quot; http://54.77.93.38/ocs/v1.php/cloud/users/demo Java code that doesn't   private static final String OCS_ROUTE =&quot;/ocs/v1.php/cloud/users/&quot;;

   String url = client.getBaseUri() + OCS_ROUTE + credentials.getUsername();
   get = new GetMethod(url);
   get.addRequestHeader(createAuthenticationHeader(credentials));
   get.setQueryString(new NameValuePair[]{new NameValuePair(&quot;format&quot;,&quot;json&quot;)});
   status = client.executeMethod(get);

private Header createAuthenticationHeader(OwnCloudCredentials credentials){
    Header h = new Header();
    h.setName(&quot;Authorization&quot;);
    String authString = credentials.getUsername()+&quot;:&quot;+credentials.getAuthToken();
    String encodedString = Base64.encodeToString(authString.getBytes(), **Base64.DEFAULT**);
    h.setValue(&quot;Basic &quot;+encodedString);
    return h;
}
 The problem are these extra termination characters added that obviously screw everything up. I have no knowledge of the apache commons httpclient, but Google didn't return any known issue. EDIT: I found the problem. the Android Base64.DEFAULT appends a \n to the end of the string. You must use the .NO_WRAP flag
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="107">
			<summary>Auto upload not working on HTC One X</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/732</url>
			<bugID>Issue #732</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Hey Devs, Just a heads up saying the auto upload functionality doesn't work on my wife's HTC One X. Client: Android version 4.2.2 ownCloud Android App version 1.6.1 Device is not rooted, just plain HTC Sense out of the box with all software updated to the newest version. Server: Owncloud server version 7.0.3-1 from suse repository debian_version 6.0.10 Tried: Rebooting android phone Rebooting ownCloud server Checking for updates, all was up to date. Checking/Unchecking auto upload Checking/Unchecking auto upload only on wifi Using different Camera app &quot;Vignette&quot;, saving photo's to DCIM folder
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="108">
			<summary>Upload of complte folder incl. subfolder</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/735</url>
			<bugID>Issue #735</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Still can't upload a folder incl. subfolders with a 'single' click!
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="109">
			<summary>As an Android user I want a new version to be released so that I may take advantage of the latest improvements</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/739</url>
			<bugID>Issue #739</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		AC: Froze the code and pass a regression test checking that all the features work as expected
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="110">
			<summary>Activity pause timeout for HistoryRecord</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/747</url>
			<bugID>Issue #747</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Owncloud 1.6.1 Android 2.3 After I enter PIN, a list of files appears and the circular &quot;progress bar&quot; is running, then ownCloud crashes. 11-23 20:04:25.007 W/PackageManager(25186): grantUriPermission URI=file:///mnt/sdcard/Android/data/org.fdroid.fdroid/cache/apks/com.owncloud.android_10600100.apk
11-23 20:04:30.087 I/ActivityManager(25186): Force stopping package com.owncloud.android uid=10127
11-23 20:04:30.087 W/ActivityManager(25186): Scheduling restart of crashed service com.owncloud.android/.services.observer.FileObserverService in 20000ms
11-23 20:04:30.087 I/ActivityManager(25186):   Force stopping service ServiceRecord{40e6f480 com.owncloud.android/.services.observer.FileObserverService}
11-23 20:04:31.527 I/PackageManager(25186): Package com.owncloud.android codePath changed from /data/app/com.owncloud.android-1.apk to /data/app/com.owncloud.android-2.apk; Retaining data and using new
11-23 20:04:31.527 I/PackageManager(25186): Unpacking native libraries for /data/app/com.owncloud.android-2.apk
11-23 20:04:35.277 W/PackageManager(25186): Code path for pkg : com.owncloud.android changing from /data/app/com.owncloud.android-1.apk to /data/app/com.owncloud.android-2.apk
11-23 20:04:35.277 W/PackageManager(25186): Resource path for pkg : com.owncloud.android changing from /data/app/com.owncloud.android-1.apk to /data/app/com.owncloud.android-2.apk
11-23 20:04:35.277 I/ActivityManager(25186): Force stopping package com.owncloud.android uid=10127
11-23 20:04:36.087 I/ActivityManager(25186): Force stopping package com.owncloud.android uid=10127
11-23 20:04:42.637 I/ActivityManager(25186): Starting activity: Intent { act=android.intent.action.MAIN flg=0x10000000 cmp=com.owncloud.android/.ui.activity.FileDisplayActivity } from pid 3949
11-23 20:04:42.867 I/ActivityManager(25186): Start proc com.owncloud.android for activity com.owncloud.android/.ui.activity.FileDisplayActivity: pid=4151 uid=10127 gids={3003, 1015}
11-23 20:04:43.837 I/ActivityManager(25186): Starting activity: Intent { cmp=com.owncloud.android/.ui.activity.PinCodeActivity (has extras) } from pid 4151
11-23 20:04:44.347 W/ActivityManager(25186): Activity pause timeout for HistoryRecord{407b0538 com.owncloud.android/.ui.activity.FileDisplayActivity}
11-23 20:05:38.437 I/ActivityManager(25186): Process com.owncloud.android (pid 4151) has died.
11-23 20:05:38.447 I/WindowManager(25186): WIN DEATH: Window{40a98b18 com.owncloud.android/com.owncloud.android.ui.activity.FileDisplayActivity paused=false}
11-23 20:05:38.537 W/ActivityManager(25186): Scheduling restart of crashed service com.owncloud.android/.services.observer.FileObserverService in 5000ms
11-23 20:05:43.547 I/ActivityManager(25186): Start proc com.owncloud.android for service com.owncloud.android/.services.observer.FileObserverService: pid=4816 uid=10127 gids={3003, 1015}
11-23 20:05:44.977 I/ActivityManager(25186): Starting activity: Intent { act=android.intent.action.MAIN cat=[android.intent.category.LAUNCHER] flg=0x10200000 cmp=com.owncloud.android/.ui.activity.FileDisplayActivity bnds=[0,410][117,528] } from pid 25310
11-23 20:05:45.317 I/ActivityManager(25186): Starting activity: Intent { cmp=com.owncloud.android/.ui.activity.PinCodeActivity (has extras) } from pid 4816
11-23 20:05:45.817 W/ActivityManager(25186): Activity pause timeout for HistoryRecord{40aa2168 com.owncloud.android/.ui.activity.FileDisplayActivity}
11-23 20:06:07.597 E/AndroidRuntime(4816):  at com.owncloud.android.providers.FileContentProvider.delete(FileContentProvider.java:169)
11-23 20:06:07.597 E/AndroidRuntime(4816):  at com.owncloud.android.providers.FileContentProvider.delete(FileContentProvider.java:216)
11-23 20:06:07.597 E/AndroidRuntime(4816):  at com.owncloud.android.providers.FileContentProvider.delete(FileContentProvider.java:209)
11-23 20:06:07.597 E/AndroidRuntime(4816):  at com.owncloud.android.providers.FileContentProvider.delete(FileContentProvider.java:154)
11-23 20:06:07.597 E/AndroidRuntime(4816):  at com.owncloud.android.providers.FileContentProvider.applyBatch(FileContentProvider.java:585)
11-23 20:06:07.597 E/AndroidRuntime(4816):  at com.owncloud.android.datamodel.FileDataStorageManager.saveFolder(FileDataStorageManager.java:388)
11-23 20:06:07.597 E/AndroidRuntime(4816):  at com.owncloud.android.operations.SynchronizeFolderOperation.synchronizeData(SynchronizeFolderOperation.java:405)
11-23 20:06:07.597 E/AndroidRuntime(4816):  at com.owncloud.android.operations.SynchronizeFolderOperation.fetchAndSyncRemoteFolder(SynchronizeFolderOperation.java:285)
11-23 20:06:07.597 E/AndroidRuntime(4816):  at com.owncloud.android.operations.SynchronizeFolderOperation.run(SynchronizeFolderOperation.java:199)
11-23 20:06:07.597 E/AndroidRuntime(4816):  at com.owncloud.android.lib.common.operations.RemoteOperation.run(RemoteOperation.java:276)
11-23 20:06:07.627 W/ActivityManager(25186):   Force finishing activity com.owncloud.android/.ui.activity.FileDisplayActivity
11-23 20:06:18.817 I/ActivityManager(25186): Process com.owncloud.android (pid 4816) has died.
11-23 20:06:18.817 W/ActivityManager(25186): Scheduling restart of crashed service com.owncloud.android/.services.observer.FileObserverService in 5000ms
11-23 20:06:19.027 W/ContentService(25186): binderDied() at ObserverNode name org.owncloud
11-23 20:06:23.837 I/ActivityManager(25186): Start proc com.owncloud.android for service com.owncloud.android/.services.observer.FileObserverService: pid=4875 uid=10127 gids={3003, 1015}
11-23 20:06:23.957 I/ActivityThread(4875): Pub org.owncloud: com.owncloud.android.providers.FileContentProvider
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="111">
			<summary>Update Description AppStore: Highlight Issue System on Github</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/753</url>
			<bugID>Issue #753</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		I have read the description of this app in the offical android app store. There is only the forum at forum.owncloud.org mentioned. I think there should be a link to the issue tracker system of GitHub as on Github the developer are reading it. And the text should encourage people to report issues and not just downvote it.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="112">
			<summary>Opening file details very slow</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/759</url>
			<bugID>Issue #759</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		When opening the details view of a file when NOT coming from the file list view (FileDisplayActivity) but for example clicking on the upload success notification or by calling:         Intent showDetailsIntent = new Intent(this, FileDisplayActivity.class);
        showDetailsIntent.putExtra(FileActivity.EXTRA_FILE, ocFile);
        showDetailsIntent.putExtra(FileActivity.EXTRA_ACCOUNT, file.getAccount(this));
        startActivity(showDetailsIntent);
 I determined that part of the delay is resulting from FileDisplayActivity.onResume() which refreshes all files in the current directory. However, for displaying just a single file this is not necessary. @davivel Should the details view better be separated from the file list?
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="113">
			<summary>[Funktion Request] reconnect when Auto Upload fail no connection</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/774</url>
			<bugID>Issue #774</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		On The App it gave the Auto Upload when i take a picture, but when at that time is no connection or the connection fail the Upload will not try agin. Can you make a Funktion to set a retry time, that the upload reload on a later time. Or a auto check that it start when the Phone is online agan. Other Funktion Wish: Can you make a Funktion that i can say auto syn other Files or directorys. More Data Syn Funktions. Not only auto upload Videos and pictures.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="114">
			<summary>Drop movie and audio player. Focus on important matters.</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/776</url>
			<bugID>Issue #776</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Why does owncloud app come with a media player for audio and video? It would make sense if media was streamed. But currently it is downloaded and then played. These files can be played with any player, cf. #775 Making a good movie player is out of scope for the owncloud app which is supposed to sync files. Currently the movie player does not work well: Movie starts over when turning device, when clicking on movie error is shown and movie stops, white background is annoying, no full screen, ... I propose to drop the movie player (which is the same as the audio player?).
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="115">
			<summary>Endless loading after deleting old OC account and adding new one</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/779</url>
			<bugID>Issue #779</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		I copied the content of one OC server to another. The desktop sync client works with the new OC server. But after deleting the old OC account from OwnCloud App (1.6.2) and adding the new one, I am now stuck in an endless loading loop (for about 2 hrs now). Although there were some connections to the server at the beginning of that loading loop, there is now no opened connection to the server. Reinstallation of the app, deleting app cache as well as owncloud folders on sd card did not help. Now when I delete that new account and add an account for the old OC server (which worked before), it also seems to endlessly load. The OC server is running stable version 7.0.3. It contains about 9800 files with a size of around 16 GB in that specific account. There are no specific errors or warnings logged on the server. EDIT: Just tested with an empty test account and it's the same.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="116">
			<summary>Android-client wastes insane amounts of bandwidth and time</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/785</url>
			<bugID>Issue #785</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		On Android if I have background data sync enabled for ownCloud it periodically starts a scan to refresh stats on files, but it goes through every file, not just those that have been tagged in the client as ones that should be kept up-to-date. In addition to this, it insists on querying every single god damn file and folder individually, using enormous amounts of data. Since I have thousands of files on my ownCloud-account this takes a long, long time, it keeps the connection open for hours and it consumes several megabytes every single refresh. It should obviously only refresh stats on the files that have been tagged, and even then, it should just send a single request to the server with all the files listed that it wants stats on and the server should just reply with a single response similarly with all the stats for the requested files.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="117">
			<summary>Steps to build using Android Studio</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/802</url>
			<bugID>Issue #802</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Hi, Please advice the steps to follow while building the app using Android Studio. Thank You
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="118">
			<summary>Relogin after update</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/809</url>
			<bugID>Issue #809</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Everytime i have to re-enter all my credentials and url when the client got an update. Why?
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="119">
			<summary>Duplicate Files problem (_conflict+date) on owncloud client.</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/815</url>
			<bugID>Issue #815</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Hello All, I have a problems when i upload file on owncloud client it show the duplicate file that create automatic (_conflict+date). on owncloud client it have this file but on the server it don't have. One more i have two user that the same group UserA and userB : userA shear one file to userB when userA edit on this file userB see the update on this file but when userB update on this file userA don't see what is userB update. I hope that all of you have any solution to shear me about this problem.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="120">
			<summary>Owncloud account selection in settings</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/816</url>
			<bugID>Issue #816</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		In the settings Dialog in Android, the account selection sozldn't be a xheckbox but an toggle button - cause only one can be selected at a time...
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="121">
			<summary>App just displays &quot;Loading...&quot;</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/833</url>
			<bugID>Issue #833</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Just upgraded phone, running 4.4.4, OC 1.6.2. The &quot;Loading...&quot; message is all I get. No problem with desktop.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="122">
			<summary>DAVdroid Sync Issue (Contact Name Problem)</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/835</url>
			<bugID>Issue #835</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Hi, actually I encountered a problem using DAVdroid to sync my Contacts. Though Firstname and Surname is filled and indicated correctly on my Z3 as well as using the Web client, the Contact Name is schown as 'Firstname Surname Surname Firstname'. Any Idea what is going wrong here? Best Stephan
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="123">
			<summary>Feature request: Sort files by on-device-status</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/840</url>
			<bugID>Issue #840</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		This kind of a follow-up on #639: I have some folders on my owncloud that contain a bunch (&gt;100) media files. Some (far less than 50 %) of them are also downloaded to my mobile phone. In some situations where I don't have any or not sufficient internet connectivity or don't want to waste data volume but want to watch a video or listen to some audio file I browse through those folders on my device to find something suitable. At the moment, I have to scroll through the file list and keep track of the small green arrows that indicate that the file was downloaded. As I can only access the files on the device in that situation, it would be convenient if I could just sort the files by their status, i.e. files that are stored on the device before those that aren't and therefore have all the available files in one bunch.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="124">
			<summary>can't find &quot;...&quot; menu in the right hand corner (Kitkat on Galaxy Note III)</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/845</url>
			<bugID>Issue #845</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Hello, On Android 4.2.2 Owncloud 1.6.2 (Sony Xperia S2) i can access Settings menu via &quot;...&quot; (3 dots vertically aligned). But in my Galaxy Note III Lite (Kitkat 4.4.2) i don't see the menu. Could you help me ? Best regards
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="125">
			<summary>Help publishing new Android manual</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/860</url>
			<bugID>Issue #860</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Hi everyone, I have created a nice shiny new Android app manual, but I don't know how to publish it. It needs to be on http://doc.owncloud.org/ like the other manuals, in HTML and PDF. Just like the desktop sync client. thanks, Carla @danimo @rperezb
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="126">
			<summary>Instant Upload Notification missing</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/862</url>
			<bugID>Issue #862</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Using Android 4.3 ... sometimes when a photo is taken there is no notification that it's beeing uploaded or has finished uploaded. The upload finishes successfully.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="127">
			<summary>add support for starttls</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/863</url>
			<bugID>Issue #863</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		App does not support starttls. It requires the insecure ssl(v3). Please add support for starttls. Tested with V1.6.2 off app
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="128">
			<summary>OwnCloud app shows incomplete list of folders</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/864</url>
			<bugID>Issue #864</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Having a folder with many subfolders, recent folders show up in the web interface for the respective user but the Android app fails to list recent subfolders even after hitting manual sync button. I'm using the latest version of the Android app and OC7.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="129">
			<summary>Recommend CalDAV and CardDAV</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/870</url>
			<bugID>Issue #870</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Many users want Calendar and Contacts syncing. Upon installation of the Android app, we could simply recommend these apps and offer to install them (link to the app store) and save ourselves from hundreds of feature requests and repeated questions about this missing feature ;-)
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="130">
			<summary>add menu entry for global upload of modified files</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/877</url>
			<bugID>Issue #877</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		In my issue report #876, I reported a bad behaviour of the client. I mentioned a &quot;second step&quot; as a work-around for this. The current implementation of the client if more file oriented. I have to download single files, mark singles files to stay in sync und upload single files is modified. To make ths a little bit more handy, the client should allow the upload of all modified files within a directory (from it's global menu). It isn't funny to manually sync / upload a couple of files by opening the context menu of each modified file. ;-) IMO it is worth thinking about an configuration option, where the user is able to choose between &quot;manually upload modified files&quot;, or &quot;automatically upload local changes&quot;.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="131">
			<summary>1.7 build failed on F-Droid</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/890</url>
			<bugID>Issue #890</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		@mvdan The owncloud 1.7 client build fails on F-Droid. https://f-droid.org/wiki/page/com.owncloud.android/lastbuild_10700000
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="132">
			<summary>Delay time for Photo/Video-Upload</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/903</url>
			<bugID>Issue #903</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Hey Guys, I've got a suggestion for another feature. If you take a photo and you have instant upload on, than the photo gets uploaded immediately. If the picture is blurred it gets uploaded anyway and wastes your limited mobile internet access. So if there is an option to delay the upload maybe one or two minutes, you have enough time to check the picture, delete it and take a new needle-sharp one and you save a lot of traffic.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="133">
			<summary>Federated Authentication error: &quot;Cannot authenticate against this server&quot;</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/907</url>
			<bugID>Issue #907</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Hello, I'm trying to access a OC server through a federated infrastructure. When trying to connect to a server at the following address: https://cana.imd.ufrn.br/oc-shib I get the following error message of the app: &quot;Cannot authenticate against this server&quot; Accessing through a browser is all normal. As well as in the desktop client that shows the page to choose the Idp and , since the IDP is selected, your login page appears , once authenticated I have access to my files. The problem is access through the android client. Analyzing the source code, I note that The mAuthTokenType variable in AuthenticatorActivity class is definied for &quot;owncloud.password&quot;, but the authentication method identified is SAML_WEB_SSO. So the authSupported method (in line 1065) returns false, generating the message &quot;auth_can_not_auth_against_server&quot;. On the other hand. When the auth_method_saml_web_sso(in steup.xml) is definied to &quot;on&quot;, the mAuthTokenType value is definied to &quot;owncloud.saml.web_sso.session_cookie&quot;. Thus the app shows only the server url field, and when I input the url, a webView dialog is shown, loading the page to the IDP choosing page. But when I interact with it, it crashes and the application returns to the initial screen. Apparently the value of mAuthTokenType is definied during startup(line 219) and is no longer modified. Even when the authentication method identified is the SAML_WEB_SSO. Why is this happening? federated authentication is actually supported by app? Any help would be much appreciated. Thank you.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="134">
			<summary>Eclipse build errors (SOLVED) - Read for instructions</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/942</url>
			<bugID>Issue #942</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		After I have import actionbarsherlock and ownCloud Android Library and build it. Then I was import owncloud-android after that Properties -&gt;&gt; Android and check that all librarys are marked. After Apply I have clean and build project and got 60 errors Most of them are: Description Resource Path Location Type SwipeRefreshLayout cannot be resolved to a type ExtendedListFragment.java /owncloud-android/src/com/owncloud/android/ui/fragment line 169 Java Problem Description Resource Path Location Type The hierarchy of the type ExtendedListFragment is inconsistent ExtendedListFragment.java /owncloud-android/src/com/owncloud/android/ui/fragment line 51 Java Problem Description Resource Path Location Type The import android.support.v4.widget.SwipeRefreshLayout cannot be resolved ExtendedListFragment.java /owncloud-android/src/com/owncloud/android/ui/fragment line 27 Java Problem Description Resource Path Location Type The method build() is undefined for the type NotificationCompat.Builder FileDownloader.java /owncloud-android/src/com/owncloud/android/files/services line 580 Java Problem Description Resource Path Location Type The method onRefresh() of type ExtendedListFragment must override or implement a supertype method ExtendedListFragment.java /owncloud-android/src/com/owncloud/android/ui/fragment line 292 Java Problem Description Resource Path Location Type The method setProgress(int, int, boolean) is undefined for the type NotificationCompat.Builder FileDownloader.java /owncloud-android/src/com/owncloud/android/files/services line 559 Java Problem Where am I wrong ?
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="135">
			<summary>Blacloud.de client for Android sync with owncloud. Instant upload photos in Android</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/961</url>
			<bugID>Issue #961</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		A new feature I would suggest: I use in Android Blacloud.de to sync my photos to my owncloud I would prefer if Instant upload folder doesn't get created in Android phone with photos taken by the camera. This create duplicated photos in my phone. Then I have the same photos in the gallery and in the Instant upload folder created by Blacloud.de Rather is the client for android sync all photos taken by my phone from the phone gallery to the Owncloud Please no &quot;Instant upload folder&quot;
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="136">
			<summary>Share with owncloud : possibility to create a directory</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/965</url>
			<bugID>Issue #965</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Quite often i want to share a bunch of images from my phone. For that i select (say) 10 photos using my viewer application, and then 'share' with owncloud. Typically i would create a new directory there to put my photo in. This seems (to me) a pretty common way of doing. Currently it is not possible. You have to first (using the phone or the browser on your desktop compuer) create the directory, then goes back to the image viewer and upload them (and usually you're hit by #198 , but it's another issue)
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="137">
			<summary>Syncing existing photos/files?</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/968</url>
			<bugID>Issue #968</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		I just installed opencloud8 and the android app and I find it works well, but… I can't find a good way to synchronise existing pictures without uploading them manually, either one by one or with file upload, meaning I have to select each file manually. It would be nice if the client could sync the entire gallery. Is this behaviour planned? Best regards roy
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="138">
			<summary>CHANGELOG.md hasn't been updated for 1.9</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/971</url>
			<bugID>Issue #971</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		File CHANGELOG.md hasn't been changed when 1.7.1 was released, and still refers to 1.7.0. This matters because users who download Owncloud from F-Droid (https://f-droid.org/repository/browse/?fdid=com.owncloud.android) are linked to https://github.com/owncloud/android/blob/HEAD/CHANGELOG.md which is currently out of date.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="139">
			<summary>Enhancement: Force instant upload via button press</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/980</url>
			<bugID>Issue #980</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Like many, I use the Instant Upload feature to backup pictures so I can remove the images from my device when it starts to fill up. However, often times I've noticed a failed instant upload is never retried and I've lost images because they weren't in sync with ownCloud. I would love a feature added to the app via a button press that checks for any files in DCIM that are not in the InstantUpload folder and uploads them. Or, if the app works by keeping track of successful uploads, forcing a sync on anything not marked as successful. Thanks.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="140">
			<summary>Allow creating folders in the upload pane</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/981</url>
			<bugID>Issue #981</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		No description provided.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="141">
			<summary>Add action to clear downloaded files cache</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/986</url>
			<bugID>Issue #986</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Please add the option to clear the downloaded files from within the app, without needing a total commander or similar tools. This is also important for 2. Or let the use define the maximum used storage quota for caching files. this is also important for #985
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="142">
			<summary>General usability issues</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/988</url>
			<bugID>Issue #988</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Hi! I think, the android app should work exactly like the desktop app. All files and folders added to the owncloud folder should be uploaded and synced automatically. Marking single files to be kept in sync is very complicated. And every change made locally on the device should be synced directly, or an option for that should be added. Overall a sync interval should be configurable.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="143">
			<summary>android client should retry automatically if no data is transferred after a while</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/991</url>
			<bugID>Issue #991</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Expected behaviour Tell us what should happen I use a owncloud server over an ADSL connection with dynamic ip and accessible through a dynamic dns hostname. If during some file transfer, my adsl connections drops and reconnect , after a while owncloud client should detect that no data is being transfered, times out and retries. Actual behaviour Client will hang forever in the same progress. Server configuration Operating system: Ubuntu 14.04 LTS Web server: apache 2.4 Database: mysql PHP version: 5.5.9-1ubuntu4.9 ownCloud version: 8.0.2-8 Storage backend: disk Client version = 1.7.1
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="144">
			<summary>Can't build using gradle</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1007</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1007</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Here's what a get from a fresh git clone: $ ./gradlew ass

FAILURE: Build failed with an exception.

* What went wrong:
A problem occurred configuring root project 'ownCloud'.
&gt; Cannot evaluate module owncloud-android-library : Configuration with name 'default' not found.

* Try:
Run with --stacktrace option to get the stack trace. Run with --info or --debug option to get more log output.

BUILD FAILED

Total time: 6.54 secs
 Is there any thing to do to make owncloud-android-library to work properly?
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="145">
			<summary>Monitor directories and upload new files like instant camera uploads</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1011</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1011</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		I was wondering why the instant camera uploads feature is so specific and not a more general feature which could upload new files from any of user-defined directories. This kind of syncing functionality is missing and, since instant camera uploads has been implemented, I don't see any reason why not implement multiple directory monitoring and automatic uploading of new files to main server. Kind Regards, George
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="146">
			<summary>[Grid] As an OC Android user I want the grid mode to be shown only when the 100% of the files are images so that by default it will be used the file list view</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1021</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1021</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		AC: By default it is shown the list view. Unless 100% of the files in the folder are images (not counting subfolders of course) – then the gallery (grid) view is used. Note: This is the first step, then it will come other user stories where a button to switch between views will be included Related to: #894
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="147">
			<summary>[ANDROID][New version] As an Android user I want a new version 1.7.2 to be released so that the sync error is fixed and other bug fixing</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1022</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1022</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		This version will include Lateral menu #900 OC-Total-Length header Support to forbidden characters on the server side Bug fixing #940 1.7.1 sync issue #947 crash when accessing to a folder with several images related to thumbnails Fix when sending a file from the email to ownCloud A regression test will be ran so that any integration bug may be found
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="148">
			<summary>Upload only on wifi with vpn connection</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1047</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1047</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Hello all, I use instant upload over wifi. It's working great since you expose your server to the internet. I would like to have more security using vpn. But until I activate the vpn tunnel the sync is already starting and gives error messages about missing IP. I would like to have a delay time after wifi connect for the sync. If possible adjustable. Let's say from 0 to 30 seconds. This would help a lot. Greetings Chucrute
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="149">
			<summary>logout when device is locked, or user choose log out</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1060</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1060</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		First to say, I like Owncloud. But I am disappointed that there is no option to logout using the android app. For security reasons, there should be a option to logout when the user choose so. Also, there should be a option to automatically logout, when the device is entering locked mode. When user is logged out, remember server settings, and user name if the user choose this as a option.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="150">
			<summary>Missing retry-option for instant upload</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1062</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1062</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Sometimes an instant upload is failing. If this happens I'm getting an error message which is stating that it failed. But there is no option to retry the upload (or even an option in the settings to automatically retry it after some minutes or so). When I'm clicking on the error message I'm just redirected to the folder in which my pictures should be uploaded. Makes the owncloud app nearly useless for me at the moment because I can't trust that everything is just working.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="151">
			<summary>No error messages when there are problems in the network connection</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1071</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1071</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Currently owncloud for android does a TERRIBLE job showing what is happening when there are problems with the network connection. I will show two examples: Right now i &quot;appear&quot; to be connected to my 3g network, but somehow cant connect to anything. If i open owncloud app, and try to refresh some file ( which i have sure it was modified on the server) owncloud will popup a progressbar with &quot;Wait a moment&quot; and a few seconds later the progress will disappear and nothing is done, the file is not downloaded, there are no error messages , just nothing. Even worse, if i try to enter any folder in this condition, i will get : &quot;nothing uploaded here&quot; which is clearly wrong !
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="152">
			<summary>File sorting on upload</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1087</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1087</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		It would be great if we could sort files in any way, when searching for upload them (from the ownCloud app), at least like usual folder browsing inside the app.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="153">
			<summary>Owncloud app should accept as many share content as possible</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1098</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1098</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		The owncloud app is listed among the apps to share information whenever you choice to share something. However, most of the time the share fails, since the owncloud app does not know how to handle the data. This is really frustrating. The most advantage purpose of having access to the owncloud server on an android device is the point that one is able to add very quickly content.. Owncloud on the go... The Owncloud app should therefore try to handle as much shared data as possible. If there are multiple ways, it could offer a selection. E.g. saving as txt or odt. Furthermore, the settings could define standard saving options. E.g. Save in the folder notes/income/ save as $date-time-app-name. It should be possible to save text, images, videos, links, html, etc. An example how such a saving method could work would be the save dialogs of the firefox webbrowser, where one can simply save as default by a single click or allow customized saving settings.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="154">
			<summary>Compile Issues</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1103</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1103</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Not a bug per se but should be noted so the readme can be updated with instruction. There are issues compiling with android studio (Error:Configuration with name 'default' not found.). Eclipse compile with no issues.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="155">
			<summary>Contacts and Calender syncing In-App</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1121</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1121</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		This would be a great feature - Syncing the local Calender/Contacts with your OwnCloud account if the app is enabled on the server. This would be a great because I'm sure other people, and not just my self, don't like the idea of downloading third-party applications and would rather prefer an original app from OwnCloud for dealing with sensitive information like this. I know Google use multiple applications, so I'm sure someone will come up with an idea whether to either have an application that does everything (aka OwnCloud), or split it into different apps from OwnCloud, e.g OwnCloud Contacts, OwnCloud Calender, etc.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="156">
			<summary>[Clarification request] SETUP.md instructions. /setup_env.sh: line 7: android: command not found</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1125</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1125</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		I do have the Android Studio installed (but not the stand-alone tools), working with it since a while. I wanted to start OC development and followed the instructions in https://github.com/owncloud/android/blob/master/SETUP.md . However, when running ./setup_env.sh gradle this fails on my machine in line 7 /setup_env.sh: line 7: android: command not found.
 Pls. assist, perhaps something is missing in the instructions, or not present in the PATH. If both the Android Studio and the stand-alone tools are needed, then it may be wise to add such a hint in the SETUP.md.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="157">
			<summary>Sync complete Directorys</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1133</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1133</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Hey Guys, just had the problem that i need to sync a complete Directory in my OwnCloud-Server to my Android-Device. Just for Example &quot;Music&quot;. If i add a Track to the Directory it should sync to the Server. Thx in advance!
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="158">
			<summary>Trouble while uploading Images with &quot;colons&quot; in the filename</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1139</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1139</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Uploading an image with the name &quot;IMG_20150620_171941:nopm:.jpg&quot; is failing. After renaming the filename to IMG_20150620_171941.jpg it is working fine. This happens on a Samsung S6 with current official Android 5.1.1 and ownCloud Android app 1.7.2 The photo was original taken on the same Samsung S6 camera app.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="159">
			<summary>Master build broken</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1140</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1140</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		After pulling the latest master to my branches I realized the code won't compile anymore and that this also applies for the master branch due to a missing string value: error_cant_bind_to_operations_service ping to @davivel and @masensio since I don't know what value needs to be put in or put back in. For now I added a dummy to my material branch, see b1f6b5e to avoid the compile error, see /home/travis/build/owncloud/android/src/com/owncloud/android/authentication/AuthenticatorActivity.java:228: error: cannot find symbol --&gt; R.string.error_cant_bind_to_operations_service in travis: https://travis-ci.org/owncloud/android/builds/79025877
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="160">
			<summary>Disable File System Access in Webview Activity</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1143</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1143</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		If an attacker somehow find themselves in a position to inject script into a WebView, then they could exploit the opportunity to access local resources. This can be somewhat prevented by disabling local file system access. It is enabled by default. The Android WebSettings class can be used to disable local file system access via the public method setAllowFileAccess. webSettings().setAllowFileAccess(false); This restricts the WebView to loading local resources from file:///android_asset (assets) and file:///android_res (resources).
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="161">
			<summary>release-1.8</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1153</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1153</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		AC: Freeze the code and regression test Release on the different markets: Google Play, Amazon and Blackberry NOTE: Code will be fronzen on the branch https://github.com/owncloud/android/tree/release-1.8
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="162">
			<summary>Do I need the latest SDK Build tool or a specific version to import the project?</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1156</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1156</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Setup Guide says Android SDK Build-Tools; any version from 20 or later should work fine; avoid preview versions, if any available. I get following error if I don't have 22.0.1 not installed. I have tried changing compileSdkVersion to 23 and builtToolVersion to 23.0.1 in build.gradle but there is no luck. Although this can be fixed very easily by installing that particular built tool version but I was wondering what's going on here. Do I need a specific version of build tool to import the project? Should I refrain from modifying the build.gradle dependency versions as I might get out of sync with the project? Error:failed to find Build Tools revision 22.0.1
install.build.tools&quot;&gt;Install Build Tools 22.0.1 and sync project
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="163">
			<summary>Enhansment sugusstion (upload)</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1158</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1158</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		I have been using owncloud for 9 months or so. Owncloud uploads all pictures and video to my server from the /sdcard/DCIM. Other applications place pictures in /sdcard/DCIM also like Tasker and some others. Would others users like the option to auto upload other directory on the phone or even include sub directories? Thanks you for considering. -Jay
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="164">
			<summary>Compile error using Eclipse</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1172</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1172</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		When I try to set up the owncloud androud project, I failed to compile it. I have following errors. Hope for solution!
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="165">
			<summary>Development Roadmap</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1173</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1173</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		What does the development roadmap of owncloud-android look like? Where is the focus of the developers today, tomorrow, ...? What are the next steps? What will be done later?
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="166">
			<summary>Deletion/modification of owncloud files from &quot;outside&quot;</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1175</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1175</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		from @joede: Just a stupid question. If other tools like QuickPic can see the images, can these tools delete these files too? If so, what happens to the sync process? Does the ownCloud client sync the deletion of the file? from @tobiasKaminsky: @joede The deletion of the local file on the device is not synced to the server. But I do not know, if the app is noticed about the deletion. I bet that the app tries to open the local file and fails as it is not there OR the app downloads the file again (which is most likely) from @joede: @tobiasKaminsky so the OC app should disallow modifications of the filename and deletions. Is this possible?
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="167">
			<summary>ocFile.getFileID does not match database value</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1186</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1186</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Using file.getFileId() in ThumnailsCacheManager does not return the same value as it is stored in database (oc_filecache). Am I just confused? @davivel @rperezb
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="168">
			<summary>Security</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1189</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1189</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		For security, I think 2FA is a must, TOTP should be sufficient. So that a compromised password isn't too big of an issue. Also, would it be possible for the Android and Desktop clients to check the SSL certificate fingerprint? Bassically, in the settings menu it should have a little information about the SSL certificate including the fingerprint. The app should give a warning when anything changed, that way MIT attacks are nearly impossible.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="169">
			<summary>New label: resolved by PR</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1202</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1202</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		There are many open issues that are only open as the corresponding PR is not yet merged. But it is hardly to see in the issue overview. So I suggest a new label &quot;resolved by PR/ PR exists&quot; or something that indicates that the issue is only open as long as the PR is not merged. For instance: #1181
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="170">
			<summary>Unable to login due to SSL</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1203</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1203</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Hi! I run OC 8.1.3 behind an nginx 1.8.0 proxy with php5-fpm and a self signed certificate. The certificate has been imported as a system cert in android for DavDroid. Everything including WebDAV and CalDAV runs find except for the OC android app: Problem: I cannot login due to an unrecognized error. Question: What could the reason be? Is it a bug in the OC app or has it something to do with my selfsigned certificate? I created it using openssl req -nodes -x509 -newkey rsa:4096 -keyout $1.pem -out $1.pem -days 730
 Here's first the ADB log when I add the following HTTP header: Strict-Transport-Security:max-age=31536000; includeSubdomains
 10-16 22:01:31.975 D/OperationsService(16094): Starting command with id 5
10-16 22:01:31.976 D/SimpleFactoryManager(16094): getClientFor(OwnCloudAccount ... : 
10-16 22:01:31.977 D/OwnCloudClient #4(16094): Creating OwnCloudClient
10-16 22:01:31.981 V/SimpleFactoryManager(16094):     new client {@cloud.domain/owncloud, 305893395}
10-16 22:01:32.021 I/ValidateNoPeople(  622): skipping global notification
10-16 22:01:32.042 D/OwnCloudClient #4(16094): REQUEST GET /owncloud/status.php
10-16 22:01:32.042 D/AdvancedSslSocketFactory(16094): Creating SSL Socket with remote cloud.domain:443, local null:0, params: org.apache.commons.httpclient.params.HttpConnectionParams@221f2fd2
10-16 22:01:32.042 D/AdvancedSslSocketFactory(16094):  ... with connection timeout 5000 and socket timeout 5000
10-16 22:01:32.072 I/ValidateNoPeople(  622): skipping global notification
10-16 22:01:32.894 E/GetRemoteStatusOperation(16094): Connection check at https://cloud.domain/owncloud: HTTP violation
10-16 22:01:32.894 E/GetRemoteStatusOperation(16094): org.apache.commons.httpclient.ProtocolException: Unable to parse header: &quot;; max-age=2592000; includeSubDomains
10-16 22:01:32.894 E/GetRemoteStatusOperation(16094):   at org.apache.commons.httpclient.HttpParser.parseHeaders(HttpParser.java:202)
10-16 22:01:32.894 E/GetRemoteStatusOperation(16094):   at org.apache.commons.httpclient.HttpMethodBase.readResponseHeaders(HttpMethodBase.java:1935)
10-16 22:01:32.894 E/GetRemoteStatusOperation(16094):   at org.apache.commons.httpclient.HttpMethodBase.readResponse(HttpMethodBase.java:1737)
10-16 22:01:32.894 E/GetRemoteStatusOperation(16094):   at org.apache.commons.httpclient.HttpMethodBase.execute(HttpMethodBase.java:1098)
10-16 22:01:32.894 E/GetRemoteStatusOperation(16094):   at org.apache.commons.httpclient.HttpMethodDirector.executeWithRetry(HttpMethodDirector.java:398)
10-16 22:01:32.894 E/GetRemoteStatusOperation(16094):   at org.apache.commons.httpclient.HttpMethodDirector.executeMethod(HttpMethodDirector.java:171)
10-16 22:01:32.894 E/GetRemoteStatusOperation(16094):   at org.apache.commons.httpclient.HttpClient.executeMethod(HttpClient.java:397)
10-16 22:01:32.894 E/GetRemoteStatusOperation(16094):   at org.apache.commons.httpclient.HttpClient.executeMethod(HttpClient.java:323)
10-16 22:01:32.894 E/GetRemoteStatusOperation(16094):   at com.owncloud.android.lib.common.OwnCloudClient.executeMethod(OwnCloudClient.java:222)
10-16 22:01:32.894 E/GetRemoteStatusOperation(16094):   at com.owncloud.android.lib.common.OwnCloudClient.executeMethod(OwnCloudClient.java:192)
10-16 22:01:32.894 E/GetRemoteStatusOperation(16094):   at com.owncloud.android.lib.resources.status.GetRemoteStatusOperation.tryConnection(GetRemoteStatusOperation.java:89)
10-16 22:01:32.894 E/GetRemoteStatusOperation(16094):   at com.owncloud.android.lib.resources.status.GetRemoteStatusOperation.run(GetRemoteStatusOperation.java:194)
10-16 22:01:32.894 E/GetRemoteStatusOperation(16094):   at com.owncloud.android.lib.common.operations.RemoteOperation.execute(RemoteOperation.java:136)
10-16 22:01:32.894 E/GetRemoteStatusOperation(16094):   at com.owncloud.android.operations.GetServerInfoOperation.run(GetServerInfoOperation.java:81)
10-16 22:01:32.894 E/GetRemoteStatusOperation(16094):   at com.owncloud.android.lib.common.operations.RemoteOperation.execute(RemoteOperation.java:136)
10-16 22:01:32.894 E/GetRemoteStatusOperation(16094):   at com.owncloud.android.services.OperationsService$ServiceHandler.nextOperation(OperationsService.java:478)
10-16 22:01:32.894 E/GetRemoteStatusOperation(16094):   at com.owncloud.android.services.OperationsService$ServiceHandler.handleMessage(OperationsService.java:413)
10-16 22:01:32.894 E/GetRemoteStatusOperation(16094):   at android.os.Handler.dispatchMessage(Handler.java:102)
10-16 22:01:32.894 E/GetRemoteStatusOperation(16094):   at android.os.Looper.loop(Looper.java:135)
10-16 22:01:32.894 E/GetRemoteStatusOperation(16094):   at android.os.HandlerThread.run(HandlerThread.java:61)
 After removing the header there's another unrecognized error: 10-16 23:44:46.124 D/NetworkUtils(18097): Searching known-servers store at /data/data/com.owncloud.android/files/knownServers.bks
10-16 23:44:46.157 D/OwnCloudClient #0(18097): Creating OwnCloudClient
10-16 23:44:46.158 V/SimpleFactoryManager(18097):     new client {@cloud.domain.net/owncloud, 68049972}
10-16 23:44:46.166 D/OwnCloudClient #0(18097): REQUEST GET /owncloud/status.php
10-16 23:44:46.185 D/AdvancedSslSocketFactory(18097): Creating SSL Socket with remote cloud.domain.net:443, local null:0, params: org.apache.commons.httpclient.params.HttpConnectionParams@7b92f59
10-16 23:44:46.185 D/AdvancedSslSocketFactory(18097):  ... with connection timeout 5000 and socket timeout 5000
10-16 23:44:46.563 D/Sensors (  622): LightSensor readEvents x = 337.000000, raw = 337
10-16 23:44:46.807 E/GetRemoteStatusOperation(18097): Connection check at https://cloud.domain.net/owncloud: SSL recoverable exception
10-16 23:44:46.807 E/GetRemoteStatusOperation(18097): com.owncloud.android.lib.common.network.CertificateCombinedException
10-16 23:44:46.807 E/GetRemoteStatusOperation(18097):   at com.owncloud.android.lib.common.network.AdvancedX509TrustManager.checkServerTrusted(AdvancedX509TrustManager.java:105)
10-16 23:44:46.807 E/GetRemoteStatusOperation(18097):   at com.android.org.conscrypt.Platform.checkServerTrusted(Platform.java:116)
10-16 23:44:46.807 E/GetRemoteStatusOperation(18097):   at com.android.org.conscrypt.OpenSSLSocketImpl.verifyCertificateChain(OpenSSLSocketImpl.java:550)
10-16 23:44:46.807 E/GetRemoteStatusOperation(18097):   at com.android.org.conscrypt.NativeCrypto.SSL_do_handshake(Native Method)
10-16 23:44:46.807 E/GetRemoteStatusOperation(18097):   at com.android.org.conscrypt.OpenSSLSocketImpl.startHandshake(OpenSSLSocketImpl.java:318)
10-16 23:44:46.807 E/GetRemoteStatusOperation(18097):   at com.owncloud.android.lib.common.network.AdvancedSslSocketFactory.verifyPeerIdentity(AdvancedSslSocketFactory.java:248)
10-16 23:44:46.807 E/GetRemoteStatusOperation(18097):   at com.owncloud.android.lib.common.network.AdvancedSslSocketFactory.createSocket(AdvancedSslSocketFactory.java:185)
10-16 23:44:46.807 E/GetRemoteStatusOperation(18097):   at org.apache.commons.httpclient.HttpConnection.open(HttpConnection.java:707)
10-16 23:44:46.807 E/GetRemoteStatusOperation(18097):   at org.apache.commons.httpclient.MultiThreadedHttpConnectionManager$HttpConnectionAdapter.open(MultiThreadedHttpConnectionManager.java:1361)
10-16 23:44:46.807 E/GetRemoteStatusOperation(18097):   at org.apache.commons.httpclient.HttpMethodDirector.executeWithRetry(HttpMethodDirector.java:387)
10-16 23:44:46.807 E/GetRemoteStatusOperation(18097):   at org.apache.commons.httpclient.HttpMethodDirector.executeMethod(HttpMethodDirector.java:171)
10-16 23:44:46.807 E/GetRemoteStatusOperation(18097):   at org.apache.commons.httpclient.HttpClient.executeMethod(HttpClient.java:397)
10-16 23:44:46.807 E/GetRemoteStatusOperation(18097):   at org.apache.commons.httpclient.HttpClient.executeMethod(HttpClient.java:323)
10-16 23:44:46.807 E/GetRemoteStatusOperation(18097):   at com.owncloud.android.lib.common.OwnCloudClient.executeMethod(OwnCloudClient.java:222)
10-16 23:44:46.807 E/GetRemoteStatusOperation(18097):   at com.owncloud.android.lib.common.OwnCloudClient.executeMethod(OwnCloudClient.java:192)
10-16 23:44:46.807 E/GetRemoteStatusOperation(18097):   at com.owncloud.android.lib.resources.status.GetRemoteStatusOperation.tryConnection(GetRemoteStatusOperation.java:89)
10-16 23:44:46.807 E/GetRemoteStatusOperation(18097):   at com.owncloud.android.lib.resources.status.GetRemoteStatusOperation.run(GetRemoteStatusOperation.java:194)
10-16 23:44:46.807 E/GetRemoteStatusOperation(18097):   at com.owncloud.android.lib.common.operations.RemoteOperation.execute(RemoteOperation.java:136)
10-16 23:44:46.807 E/GetRemoteStatusOperation(18097):   at com.owncloud.android.operations.GetServerInfoOperation.run(GetServerInfoOperation.java:81)
10-16 23:44:46.807 E/GetRemoteStatusOperation(18097):   at com.owncloud.android.lib.common.operations.RemoteOperation.execute(RemoteOperation.java:136)
10-16 23:44:46.807 E/GetRemoteStatusOperation(18097):   at com.owncloud.android.services.OperationsService$ServiceHandler.nextOperation(OperationsService.java:478)
10-16 23:44:46.807 E/GetRemoteStatusOperation(18097):   at com.owncloud.android.services.OperationsService$ServiceHandler.handleMessage(OperationsService.java:413)
10-16 23:44:46.807 E/GetRemoteStatusOperation(18097):   at android.os.Handler.dispatchMessage(Handler.java:102)
10-16 23:44:46.807 E/GetRemoteStatusOperation(18097):   at android.os.Looper.loop(Looper.java:135)
10-16 23:44:46.807 E/GetRemoteStatusOperation(18097):   at android.os.HandlerThread.run(HandlerThread.java:61)
10-16 23:44:46.812 D/FileActivity(18097): Received result of operation in FileActivity - common behaviour for all the FileActivities 
 Kind Regards
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="171">
			<summary>Uploader: colorify primary action</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1204</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1204</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		#1168 (comment): Colorify primary action (upload) after #1209 is merged. File: Uploader.java / uploader_layout.xml Depends on: #1209, #1168 material buttons #1209 avoid duplicates #1168
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="172">
			<summary>View a file without downloading it</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1207</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1207</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		I would like to be able to view a file without having to download it to my phone
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="173">
			<summary>Public Beta</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1213</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1213</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		In order to pre-test the PRs by the community I suggest to create a public beta in a new branch. There will be an apk, that experienced user can download, install and test. This branch will contains all PRs that are &quot;3 - to review&quot; or above. Issues regarding the beta will get the label &quot;Beta&quot;. Found bugs or improvements are implemented in the corresponding original PRs and merged back to beta. The main advantage of this is, that the PRs are tested by far more user than &quot;only&quot; the QA. Furthermore if the PRs have fewer issues, the workload of the QA should be lower and thus can result in a faster merge process. I am willing to maintain this branch and do a merge if the belonging PRs are changing. What do you think? @davivel @rperezb @jancborchardt @AndyScherzinger @lukeowncloud
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="174">
			<summary>Short with own YOURLS Links Shorter</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1222</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1222</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Hey there, could you please reduce the over YOURLS integrate? Thanks! Best, Benny
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="175">
			<summary>Confusing: Size is too close to date</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1232</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1232</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		At least for me I read &quot;27, 2 Mb&quot; and not &quot;Jun 27&quot; and &quot;2 Mb&quot;. While I understand the approach to have the Filesize left aligned, I guess this not perfect... Ps.: Is this beta related? I do not know from which PR this is...
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="176">
			<summary>Menu action: &quot;Set picture as&quot; also not non-picture</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1247</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1247</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Open a non-picture file (e.g. mp3), click menu: It contains entry &quot;Set picture as&quot;. Clicking this action has no effect. However, it should not be there in the first place!
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="177">
			<summary>Share with users menu is missing detailed options</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1261</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1261</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Thank You Tobias for bringing this possibility to share with ownCloud users!! I suppose that You plan to add the options of sharing for files and folders (can share, can edit, access control - create, change, delete), as it is important to be able to set the folder readonly when sharing.. I just wanted to leave the mention that they are missing for now. Thank You sooo muuuchh!!
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="178">
			<summary>Owncloud Android doesnt like Android 6 Marshmallow</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1262</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1262</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Hey all, Took delivery of a Android 6 enabled phone yesterday and put the Owncloud app on it. It does not like it one bit to be honest, frequent black screen / crash and upload is not working. I did notice that at no time was i asked for permissions management, this is new in Android 6 in that permissions are supposed to be requested as an when they are needed rather than at install time via marketplace and i'm wondering if this is to blame (access to storage etc). Anyone else using Android 6 ATM who can confirm?
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="179">
			<summary>So i have a security issue to discuss - should i post it here?</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1263</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1263</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Do you guys have an e-mail i can send it too or should i post here?
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="180">
			<summary>Beta: add some kind of indication of which build I am using.</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1264</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1264</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		I thought that I could use the &quot;View Changelog&quot; menu entry to check which version am I using, but I just noticed that it opens: https://raw.githubcontent.com/owncloud/android/beta/CHANGELOG.mg , which I believe is the changelog for the whole branch. I almost reported an issue using old build (I installed newer build on the phone yesterday, but not on the tablet, and I used the tablet today) Adding some kind of indication to identify the build in the app would be nice. Especially for filtering dumb mistakes like the one I almost made.. 😓
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="181">
			<summary>Beta: 2015-11-05 Suggestion: Make the list / grid view a simple toggle</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1267</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1267</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		I was very happy when You introduced the possibility of using the grid view for all folders as I have many forlders with both documents and pictures or scans. Sometimes I do switch between the views as both have its advantages. When I was using the beta now, I found out that it is a little schizofrenic when EACH folder remembers the last viewing method. Several times I switched to grid view to look for some picture quickly, and I went through several subdirectories. Later I was viewing some of the diretories in list view. After some time I ended up with directories (seemingly) randomly switching between grid and list views as I was going through them. It was kind of.. odd behaviour. I think it would be better to have the grid/list as a mode switch like in other file managers. (When You use Nautilus or anything else, Your view also doesn’t switch from icon to list view as You go through the directory tree). Do You agree with me or do You have a different reason to have the view remembered for each folder?
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="182">
			<summary>Date changed to date of upload (not original)</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1271</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1271</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		When uploading a file from Android (only?) the time and date of the file ist changed to time and date of upload. Is it possible to keep the original date and time? Thanks!
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="183">
			<summary>Change storage path: folder already exists</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1299</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1299</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Due to playing with the changing storage path feature I managed to move the folder to a parent folder where &quot;owncloud-beta&quot; already exists. At this point it stops. Maybe a question if the app should proceed and write into it (and maybe overwrite something) is a useful idea?
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="184">
			<summary>Instant upload doesn't check wifi on every upload file start</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1305</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1305</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		I've activated instand photo upload only on wifi. If I connect back to wifi, the app starts with upload. But if the wifi connection where lost and some pictures have to be uploaded, the app uses the mobile connection to upload. Looks like, that the app doesn't check the wifi connection on every picture or video on start upload.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="185">
			<summary>Don't use an own folder on mobile for uploaded files</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1306</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1306</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		The uploaded files where copied to an own owncloud folder. Thats not good, because of to many files in the gallery and to much space consumption. Please use to check to uploaded file the original folder and files.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="186">
			<summary>Android - Duplicate files.</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1324</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1324</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		When I upload a file from my phone to my server, the app creates a folder on my phone and copies the file to that folder... so now I have 2 copies of ever file I upload on my phone. This effectively cuts my phone storage in half, and is crazy if I want to upload hundreds or thousands of photos. What is the thinking behind this? Dropbox does not do this. If this &quot;feature&quot; is going to remain then it should be able to be turned off in the settings. Yes, I could upload a file then go and delete the copy that was made on my phone, but I don't want to do this.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="187">
			<summary>owncloud 1.9 does not install while beta is installed and vice versa</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1327</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1327</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		I get repeatedly the error 505 while
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="188">
			<summary>Allow downloading of files (especially pictures) unzipped from share link</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1345</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1345</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Zipped downloads are not common for mobile useres. Users do not know (and do not want) to handle zipped files on their phone. I would be happy, if files could be downloaded as single file.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="189">
			<summary>Implement a Document Provider</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1352</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1352</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		One sorely lacking feature (unless it's already implemented in which case this is a bug report) is the lack of ownCloud's app acting as a document provider. A document provider essentially tells the Android operating system that it is an application that manages files. Google Drive is a document provider, and therefore whenever the OS-level file picker comes up (for example, when selecting a new image as a wallpaper), Google Drive is offered as one such service you can use to browse files. Implementing this feature shouldn't be too terrible hard, all the documentation on it is provided here: http://developer.android.com/guide/topics/providers/document-provider.html
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="190">
			<summary>View Photos Temporarily without Downloading them to System</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1353</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1353</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		One personal annoyance is that the ownCloud app downloads every image that I open on my devices to the internal storage. Sometimes, I want to view an image just temporarily and NOT have it automatically downloaded and stored to /sdcard/owncloud/.../. Perhaps downloading them into a cache would be more proper, then if the user clicks the menu button, offer to let them download the image and then it would be appropriate to save it to /sdcard/owncloud/.../. Otherwise every image I view from a different folder (and I have many, many folders) from the ownCloud app triggers Google Play Services to shoot me a notification asking if I want to backup that folder to Google Photos.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="191">
			<summary>Client keeps scanning directory even though it should not be synched</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1379</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1379</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Expected behaviour it should be possible to not autosynch/refresh specific folders. Actual behaviour the client is relentless and goes on for hours, synching scanning a folder that was removed locally, until the phone runs out of battery. i have a directory in my owncloud storage that i do not want to synch on my phone as it's rather big (~2GB). what i've done so far is select the directory in the client, select 'remove' and then 'local copy only'. i'm not sure if this is supposed to disable the synching of this directory from that point on, but as i see no other setting where i can exempt this folder, i guess it should. Steps to reproduce have a rather big folder in your owncloud (~2gb in my case) wait. Environment data Android version: 5.1 Device model: Moto G LTE 1st gen Stock or customized system: stock ownCloud app version: 1.9.0 ownCloud server version: 8.1.2 Logs Web server error log this goes on for hours: PROPFIND /remote.php/webdav/that_folder/[...]
 ownCloud log (data/owncloud.log) there are no entries from the time the issue occured.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="192">
			<summary>Automatic upload works only sometime</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1380</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1380</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		What I'm doing : -Check automatic picture upload -Check only wifi What is happening : -Nothing most of the time -If I'm on wifi + owncloud in the background + I take a picture : It uploads it What I'm expecting to happen : -Should upload all the pictures that has been taken when I didn't had wifi -The app shouldn't have to be launched to upload pictures Some suggestion : -Maybe a way to disable the owncloud notification / icon on each upload. -Are the weird kind of &quot;loading&quot; dots on the top of the app made on purpose ? They look weird. -Users should be able to chose the folder name for auto upload, if you have more than one device it is a mess. Thanks for reading :)
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="193">
			<summary>Only leave application with open navigation drawer</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1384</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1384</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Maybe this is something I got used to by other apps and I really don't know whether this is an Android-UI-Guidline or not. Currently the ownCloud-Client closes when the back button is pressed in the root folder view. Other apps, e.g. the ownCloud Newsreader, first open the navigation drawer and when pressing back a second time with the open drawer it leaves the app.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="194">
			<summary>Owncloud client warns with valid letsencrypt HTTPS certificate</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1385</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1385</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		I've just deployed a letsencrypt HTTPS certificate on my owncloud server. Firefox and Chrome are fine with the cert and can successfully validate it, however, the Owncloud Android app still issues a warning that the cert is signed by an unknown authority. A quick Google search tells me that this may be related to which Android URL API is in use, however, I can't give more details ATM. Issue occurs on Owncloud app 1.9.0.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="195">
			<summary>Instant photo upload: Cannot modify header information ... Sapi.php#58</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1388</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1388</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Hi, instant photo uploading with android client 1.9.0 produces this error: Error PHP Cannot modify header information - headers already sent by (output started at /var/www/owncloud/3rdparty/sabre/http/lib/Sapi.php:70) at /var/www/owncloud/3rdparty/sabre/http/lib/Sapi.php#58 Photos were uploads successfully. sudo -u www-data php ./occ app:list Enabled: activity: 2.1.3 calendar: 0.8.1 contacts: 0.5.0.0 direct_menu: 0.5 files: 1.2.0 files_external: 0.3.0 files_pdfviewer: 0.7 files_sharing: 0.7.0 files_texteditor: 2.0 files_trashbin: 0.7.0 files_versions: 1.1.0 files_videoviewer: 0.1.3 firstrunwizard: 1.1 gallery: 14.2.0 provisioning_api: 0.3.0 templateeditor: 0.1 user_otp: 2.5 Disabled: documents encryption external notifications ownbackup storagecharts2 user_external user_ldap System: Owncloud: 8.2.2 [ http://download.owncloud.org/download/repositories/stable/Ubuntu_14.04/ ] System: Ubuntu 14.04 LTS Webserver: apache2 2.4.7-1ubuntu4.8 PHP: php5 5.5.9+dfsg-1ubuntu4.14 Database: mysql 5.5.46-0ubuntu0.14.04.2 Ciao Marcus 👎 1
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="196">
			<summary>(optional) Delete of successful uploaded files e.g. images, videos</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1406</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1406</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Hi, I noticed, that images uploaded to OC, are copied to owncloud/OC-installation/SofortUpload and that they are remaining there - until forever, thus still blocking urgently needed storage space on the SD-CARD . Selecting an Option like: Delete image (video) after successful upload will make better use of the limited resources on a handset. Since the image is stored in the DCIM folder as well, there is still ONE local copy available and not TWO copies, whereas the copy in the OC folder is only required for upload purposes. regards, hitam4450
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="197">
			<summary>Enhancement: Ability to create bookmarks</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1407</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1407</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		I think that the current concept of Favorites is somewhat misleading. I might have a &quot;Favorite&quot; folder that lies deep within the folder tree which I want to access quickly, but it does not necessarily mean that I want this whole folder synced on my phone. Would it be possible to make &quot;Bookmarks&quot; in the left menu part (where the access to configuration, and on device / all files switch is now) that would be merely a list of shortcuts to get us quickly deep into menu structure?
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="198">
			<summary>Folder list is not updated when a file is uploaded</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1408</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1408</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		and as a consequence it is impossible to upload a file to a folder that was created after the app updated the folder list. I think it would be good if fresh folder list would be fetched withing upload file dialog (when shared from other application)
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="199">
			<summary>Keep in sync additional folders</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1417</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1417</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		I'd like to keep in sync additional custom folders (WhatsApp Images, Screenshots...). To keep things simple from a UI prospective we could store these folders inside the same paths selected for camera pictures.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="200">
			<summary>Settings and log should replace the content just like the files list instead of opening separate views</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1429</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1429</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Just as said in the title. Amy reasom we do not do this at the moment?
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="201">
			<summary>Secondary button text color</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1435</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1435</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Currently the secondary button is grey with the dark ownCloud blue as text. However that's a bit much use of the brand color. Better would be to have the text color here black. Or if that's too intense compared to the primary button, a dark shade of grey.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="202">
			<summary>Synchronization has to be performed manually</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1443</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1443</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Hi ! When using the Android OwnCloud client, I have to manually select a file and click on &quot;synchronize&quot; otherwise, its content is not updated -- although the file properties are correctly updated in the Owncloud client. STEPS TO PERFORM perform the initial synchronization for instance I have a file called todo.txt in Documents/ which is properly synced I make a modification on my desktop client (KDE under Kubuntu). I make sure this is properly uploaded to the server : this is OK (checked from web interface) the file is not synced on the Android device I check the Owncloud client on the Android device : I can see the new filesize and new file date is displayed but when I click on the file, I can still see its former content the only way to make the OC Android client sync it properly is to select &quot;synchronize&quot; in the file context menu The problem is it has to be done manually each time. This is misleading as files attributes, in the OC client, are the right ones but the file content is not updated. Using : Server : Owncloud 8.1 (web4all.fr hosting) Desktop client : Kubuntu 14.04 LTS + Owncloud client v.2.1 Android Phone : Samsung Galaxy Core Prime LTE ; Android 5.0.2 Android Owncloud client : 1.9.0 Thanks to everyone involved ! Cheers !
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="203">
			<summary>Beta 20160120: Missing german translation for new setting options</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1446</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1446</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		In the german version the new settings are not translate: First level: &quot;On device&quot; --&gt; &quot;Lokal gespeichert&quot; In Settings (Einstellungen): &quot;Storage path&quot; --&gt; &quot;Speicherort&quot; &quot;Upload when charging only&quot; --&gt; &quot;Upload nur beim aufladen&quot; (absolut correct german would be: &quot;Hochladen nur während des Aufladens&quot; but &quot;Upload&quot; does not necessarily be translated and it would be too long) &quot;Original file will be...&quot; --&gt; &quot;Original speichern ...&quot; ... &quot;kept in original folder&quot; --&gt; &quot;im ursprünglichen Ordner&quot; ... &quot;moved to app folder&quot; --&gt; &quot;in Owncloud Ordner verschieben&quot; &quot;Common&quot; --&gt; Allgemein &quot;Cache size&quot; --&gt; Cache größe&quot; Beta specific settings (if needed): &quot;Download latest beta version&quot; --&gt; &quot;Letzte Betaversion runter laden&quot; &quot;Changelog beta version&quot; --&gt; Änderungsliste betaversion And btw: I think the translation &quot;Dies einem Freund empfehlen&quot; should be called &quot;Owncloud weiterempfehlen&quot; or &quot;Die App weiterempfehlen&quot;.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="204">
			<summary>Can't upload videos to OC from mobile</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1448</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1448</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Hello, I'm newbie in OC, but I'm stuck and cannot find any solution. I'm running OC8.2 on headless Debian Server (Trusty) with MySQL. I am running OwnClient Android appli on Android 5.0.2/Samsung S5: I have Instant video upload and Inst enabled on Android App, with upload via Wifi only Here is description of the issue and outcome of my investigations: If I'm connected on my Wifi home network with my mobile and I record a video, the video is immediately uploaded to OC. This is perfect. If I'm not connectd on wifi network and I record a video, this video will never be uploaded to my OC when I'm back at home, connected on my Wifi. Additinal information :idea: : I have also changed the OC folder for video upload several time (I have initially suspected that using same folder for images and videos could cause troubles), but it does not change anything. when a video is uploaded successfully (when I'm at home, recording and connected), I get the following error in the logs: Cannot modify header information - headers already sent by (output started at /var/www/owncloud/3rdparty/sabre/http/lib/Sapi.php:70) at /var/www/owncloud/3rdparty/sabre/http/lib/Sapi.php#58 Your help will be appreciated. Zevleu Newbie Message(s) : 2 Inscription : Dim Jan 03, 2016 7:46 pm ownCloud version: 8.2.2 Webserver: nginx Database: MySQL OS: Linux PHP version: 5.4.45 Haut Re: Video upload does not work properly Message par Zevleu » Lun Jan 04, 2016 8:32 am I forgot to add that upload of images runs fine in all cases. The issue occurs only with videos. Zevleu Newbie Message(s) : 2 Inscription : Dim Jan 03, 2016 7:46 pm ownCloud version: 8.2.2 Webserver: nginx Database: MySQL OS: Linux PHP version: 5.4.45 Haut Re: Video upload does not work properly Message par tflidd » Lun Jan 04, 2016 11:04 am For Android issues please see https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="205">
			<summary>Video not uploaded to OC from mobile</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1449</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1449</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Actual behaviour I'm running OC8.2 on headless Debian Server (Trusty) with MySQL. I am running OwnClient Android appli on Android 5.0.2/Samsung S5: I have Instant video upload enabled on Android App, with upload via Wifi only Image upload runs perfectly. The issue is with video. Here is description of the issue and outcome of my investigations: If I'm connected on my Wifi home network with my mobile and I record a video, the video is immediately uploaded to OC. This is perfect. If I'm not connectd on wifi network and I record a video, this video will never be uploaded to my OC when I'm back at home, connected on my Wifi. Additinal information :idea: : I have also changed the OC folder for video upload several time (I have initially suspected that using same folder for images and videos could cause troubles), but it does not change anything. when a video is uploaded successfully (when I'm at home, recording and connected), I get the following error in the logs: Cannot modify header information - headers already sent by (output started at /var/www/owncloud/3rdparty/sabre/http/lib/Sapi.php:70) at /var/www/owncloud/3rdparty/sabre/http/lib/Sapi.php#58 Environment data Android version: 5.0.2 Device model: Samsung S5 SM-G901F Stock or customized system: ownCloud app version: 1.9.0 ownCloud server version: 8.2.2 Logs Error PHP Cannot modify header information - headers already sent by (output started at /var/www/owncloud/3rdparty/sabre/http/lib/Sapi.php:70) at /var/www/owncloud/3rdparty/sabre/http/lib/Sapi.php#58 2016-01-22T22:04:57+00:00 Error PHP Cannot modify header information - headers already sent by (output started at /var/www/owncloud/3rdparty/sabre/http/lib/Sapi.php:70) at /var/www/owncloud/3rdparty/sabre/http/lib/Sapi.php#58 ownCloud log (data/owncloud.log) {&quot;reqId&quot;:&quot;1tjBrYjQLLFxJ55ma0ZR&quot;,&quot;remoteAddr&quot;:&quot;192.168.0.14&quot;,&quot;app&quot;:&quot;PHP&quot;,&quot;message&quot;:&quot;Cannot modify header information - headers already sent by (output started at /var/www/owncloud/3rdparty/sabre/http/lib/Sapi.php:70) at /var/www/owncloud/3rdparty/sabre/http/lib/Sapi.php#58&quot;,&quot;level&quot;:3,&quot;time&quot;:&quot;2016-01-22T22:04:43+00:00&quot;} {&quot;reqId&quot;:&quot;XA+ExzSWjJtMQlVkq7Ow&quot;,&quot;remoteAddr&quot;:&quot;192.168.0.14&quot;,&quot;app&quot;:&quot;PHP&quot;,&quot;message&quot;:&quot;Cannot modify header information - headers already sent by (output started at /var/www/owncloud/3rdparty/sabre/http/lib/Sapi.php:70) at /var/www/owncloud/3rdparty/sabre/http/lib/Sapi.php#58&quot;,&quot;level&quot;:3,&quot;time&quot;:&quot;2016-01-22T22:04:57+00:00&quot;}
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="206">
			<summary>sdk componet not installed in android studio.</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1456</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1456</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		sdk componet not installed : build-tools-21.1.1 i f any know then provide me download link.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="207">
			<summary>Beta 20160120: crash - uploading picture to owncloud using &quot;Easy Share Action&quot;</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1472</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1472</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Expected behaviour Picture should be uploaded to ownCloud Actual behaviour ownCloud app crashes Steps to reproduce open Gallery share picture by using &quot;Easy Share Action&quot; button ownCloud App crashes Environment data Android version: 6.0.1 Device model: Nexus 4 Stock or customized system: Cyanogenmod 13 ownCloud app version: 20160120 ownCloud server version: ownCloud 8.2.2 Logs Web server error log No Web Server error log, because app crashes before connecting to server ownCloud log (data/owncloud.log) No ownCloud log, because app crashes before connecting to server Android Log ************ CAUSE OF ERROR ************ java.lang.RuntimeException: Unable to start service com.owncloud.android.files.services.FileUploader@2fccfd1 with Intent { cmp=com.owncloud.android.beta/com.owncloud.android.files.services.FileUploader (has extras) }: java.lang.IllegalArgumentException: Trying to create a OCFile with a non valid remote path: at android.app.ActivityThread.handleServiceArgs(ActivityThread.java:3071) at android.app.ActivityThread.-wrap17(ActivityThread.java) at android.app.ActivityThread$H.handleMessage(ActivityThread.java:1461) at android.os.Handler.dispatchMessage(Handler.java:102) at android.os.Looper.loop(Looper.java:148) at android.app.ActivityThread.main(ActivityThread.java:5466) at java.lang.reflect.Method.invoke(Native Method) at com.android.internal.os.ZygoteInit$MethodAndArgsCaller.run(ZygoteInit.java:726) at com.android.internal.os.ZygoteInit.main(ZygoteInit.java:616) Caused by: java.lang.IllegalArgumentException: Trying to create a OCFile with a non valid remote path: at com.owncloud.android.datamodel.OCFile.(OCFile.java:103) at com.owncloud.android.files.services.FileUploader.obtainNewOCFileToUpload(FileUploader.java:771) at com.owncloud.android.files.services.FileUploader.onStartCommand(FileUploader.java:286) at android.app.ActivityThread.handleServiceArgs(ActivityThread.java:3054) ... 8 more ************ DEVICE INFORMATION *********** Brand: google Device: mako Model: Nexus 4 Id: MMB29U Product: occam ************ FIRMWARE ************ SDK: 23 Release: 6.0.1 Incremental: 35b26cafd4
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="208">
			<summary>No resource found: 'style/Theme.Sherlock.Light.Dialog'</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1474</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1474</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Error:(727) Error retrieving parent for item: No resource found that matches the given name 'style/Theme.Sherlock.Light.Dialog'. I clone the latest repos and in the first compile I run into this error. Anyone know how to solve it?
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="209">
			<summary>&quot;Couldn't Establish Connection&quot; message when trying to connect</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1477</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1477</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		I am trying to get the app to connect to my owncloud, but get the message &quot;Couldn't Establish Connection&quot;. Here is the adb logcat output: 02-13 16:10:38.887  4091 11713 E GetRemoteStatusOperation: Connection check at http://owncloud.iandouglasscott.com: Socket exception
02-13 16:10:38.887  4091 11713 E GetRemoteStatusOperation: java.net.ConnectException: failed to connect to owncloud.iandouglasscott.com/2001:19f0:ac00:be6:5400:ff:fe1b:b1b4 (port 443) after 5000ms: isConnected failed: ECONNREFUSED (Connection refused)
02-13 16:10:38.887  4091 11713 E GetRemoteStatusOperation:      at libcore.io.IoBridge.isConnected(IoBridge.java:234)
02-13 16:10:38.887  4091 11713 E GetRemoteStatusOperation:      at libcore.io.IoBridge.connectErrno(IoBridge.java:171)
02-13 16:10:38.887  4091 11713 E GetRemoteStatusOperation:      at libcore.io.IoBridge.connect(IoBridge.java:122)
02-13 16:10:38.887  4091 11713 E GetRemoteStatusOperation:      at java.net.PlainSocketImpl.connect(PlainSocketImpl.java:183)
02-13 16:10:38.887  4091 11713 E GetRemoteStatusOperation:      at java.net.PlainSocketImpl.connect(PlainSocketImpl.java:452)
02-13 16:10:38.887  4091 11713 E GetRemoteStatusOperation:      at java.net.Socket.connect(Socket.java:884)
02-13 16:10:38.887  4091 11713 E GetRemoteStatusOperation:      at com.owncloud.android.lib.common.network.AdvancedSslSocketFactory.createSocket(AdvancedSslSocketFactory.java:184)
02-13 16:10:38.887  4091 11713 E GetRemoteStatusOperation:      at org.apache.commons.httpclient.HttpConnection.open(HttpConnection.java:707)
02-13 16:10:38.887  4091 11713 E GetRemoteStatusOperation:      at org.apache.commons.httpclient.MultiThreadedHttpConnectionManager$HttpConnectionAdapter.open(MultiThreadedHttpConnectionManager.java:1361)
02-13 16:10:38.887  4091 11713 E GetRemoteStatusOperation:      at org.apache.commons.httpclient.HttpMethodDirector.executeWithRetry(HttpMethodDirector.java:387)
02-13 16:10:38.887  4091 11713 E GetRemoteStatusOperation:      at org.apache.commons.httpclient.HttpMethodDirector.executeMethod(HttpMethodDirector.java:171)
02-13 16:10:38.887  4091 11713 E GetRemoteStatusOperation:      at org.apache.commons.httpclient.HttpClient.executeMethod(HttpClient.java:397)
02-13 16:10:38.887  4091 11713 E GetRemoteStatusOperation:      at org.apache.commons.httpclient.HttpClient.executeMethod(HttpClient.java:323)
02-13 16:10:38.887  4091 11713 E GetRemoteStatusOperation:      at com.owncloud.android.lib.common.OwnCloudClient.executeMethod(OwnCloudClient.java:222)
02-13 16:10:38.887  4091 11713 E GetRemoteStatusOperation:      at com.owncloud.android.lib.common.OwnCloudClient.executeMethod(OwnCloudClient.java:192)
02-13 16:10:38.887  4091 11713 E GetRemoteStatusOperation:      at com.owncloud.android.lib.resources.status.GetRemoteStatusOperation.tryConnection(GetRemoteStatusOperation.java:106)
02-13 16:10:38.887  4091 11713 E GetRemoteStatusOperation:      at com.owncloud.android.lib.resources.status.GetRemoteStatusOperation.run(GetRemoteStatusOperation.java:202)
02-13 16:10:38.887  4091 11713 E GetRemoteStatusOperation:      at com.owncloud.android.lib.common.operations.RemoteOperation.execute(RemoteOperation.java:136)
02-13 16:10:38.887  4091 11713 E GetRemoteStatusOperation:      at com.owncloud.android.operations.GetServerInfoOperation.run(GetServerInfoOperation.java:81)
02-13 16:10:38.887  4091 11713 E GetRemoteStatusOperation:      at com.owncloud.android.lib.common.operations.RemoteOperation.execute(RemoteOperation.java:136)
02-13 16:10:38.887  4091 11713 E GetRemoteStatusOperation:      at com.owncloud.android.services.OperationsService$ServiceHandler.nextOperation(OperationsService.java:486)
02-13 16:10:38.887  4091 11713 E GetRemoteStatusOperation:      at com.owncloud.android.services.OperationsService$ServiceHandler.handleMessage(OperationsService.java:421)
02-13 16:10:38.887  4091 11713 E GetRemoteStatusOperation:      at android.os.Handler.dispatchMessage(Handler.java:102)
02-13 16:10:38.887  4091 11713 E GetRemoteStatusOperation:      at android.os.Looper.loop(Looper.java:148)
02-13 16:10:38.887  4091 11713 E GetRemoteStatusOperation:      at android.os.HandlerThread.run(HandlerThread.java:61)
02-13 16:10:38.887  4091 11713 E GetRemoteStatusOperation: Caused by: android.system.ErrnoException: isConnected failed: ECONNREFUSED (Connection refused)
02-13 16:10:38.887  4091 11713 E GetRemoteStatusOperation:      at libcore.io.IoBridge.isConnected(IoBridge.java:223)
02-13 16:10:38.887  4091 11713 E GetRemoteStatusOperation:      ... 24 more
 As far as I understand, this says it is failing to retrieve https://owncloud.iandouglasscott.com/status.php, but that loads properly in the browser on my phone, so I don't know why this isn't working. It is probably a server-side issue, since using https://demo.owncloud.org as the url works. Edit: The Linux desktop client seems to be working fine.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="210">
			<summary>Cant Download and Upload file from Android</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1478</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1478</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		cant download any file i try 1kb file and 40MB file both same cant download ... error .. Operation finished with HTTP status code 503(fail) in log file... But from desktop client it does not have any issue
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="211">
			<summary>APK on Amazon Appstore is out of date</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1481</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1481</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		The Amazon App Store is still distributing version 1.8.0 of the ownCloud client app for Android. This has happened before: #423 and #561.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="212">
			<summary>Fix New Folder Alertdialog padding</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1495</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1495</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		New Folder Alertdialog padding is not right. EditText expands to the both edges. According to Material Design guidelines, Alertdialog should have 24dp padding on left and right sides and 20dp between title and content. Here is how it currently looks. Here is the added padding according to Material Design guidelines.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="213">
			<summary>Please provide steps for working with android studio in windows 7</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1504</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1504</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Please provide steps for working with android studio in windows 7... i want to run owncloud android code in android studio with windows 7... want some modification in own cloud android application.... so please provide me brief step for android application development
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="214">
			<summary>Remove actionbarsherlock</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1507</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1507</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Actionbarsherlock is not used any longer by the app, so the complete directory should be deleted, or?
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="215">
			<summary>Amazon no updated version</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1508</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1508</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Hi, Can you update Amazon app store with new version app, the last version is 1.8.0 http://www.amazon.fr/gp/product/B00944PQMK Thanks
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="216">
			<summary>ownCloud app don't open the last revision of a modified file</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1519</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1519</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Expected behaviour When you open a file in the ownCloud app, it should show you the last version of the file (the one on the server). Actual behaviour When you open the ownCloud app it check if there is updated files and see them. Then when you open a file that you have previously updated on your computer (that is synced to the server) the ownCloud app show you a previous version of the file. Steps to reproduce Modify a file from your ownCloud folder on your computer Sync it to the server Open it in the ownCloud app on your Android phone Environment data Android version: 4.4 Device model: Razr i Stock or customized system: CM11 ownCloud app version: 1.9.1 ownCloud server version: 8.0.2 Logs I don't have logs since it's my ownCloud provider that handle them. Thanks
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="217">
			<summary>Autoupload - two or more accounts</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1547</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1547</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Expected behaviour I should be able to define for which owncloud account I want to activate automatic upload or configure automatic upload for both accounts seperately. Actual behaviour Configuration for automatic upload will be used by all added owncloud accounts Steps to reproduce Add two or more owncloud accounts Activate automatic image and/or video upload Create picture or video Environment data Android version: 6.0 Device model: HTC One m8 Stock or customized system: CM13 ownCloud app version: 1.9.1 ownCloud server version: 9.0
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="218">
			<summary>Continues Wifi-only upload when not on wifi</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1550</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1550</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Expected behaviour The app is performing a long-running wifi-only upload (in my specific case, triggered by instant upload triggered by me being briefly near my home). I then leave wifi range within a few seconds of entering it. The app should suspend the ongoing upload (because I told it on its settings page that I only want it to upload on wifi). Actual behaviour The app proceeded to drain my data allowance by continuing to upload on an (unfortunately very fast LTE-based) cell network. Steps to reproduce Start wifi-only upload Leave wifi range Watch it drain your data allowance Environment data Android version: 6.0.1r22 Device model: One plus One Stock or customized system: Cyanogenmod nightly from Mar 21 ownCloud app version: 1.9.1 from FDroid ownCloud server version: 8.2
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="219">
			<summary>[Android]: could not establish a connection</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1563</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1563</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Hi, after a chrash I wiped my tablet. After that I installed ownloud app and tried to connect with my owncloud server. After I entered the server address I get an error: could not establish a connection. (in German: Konnte keine Verbindung aufbauen) The connect button is grey,I can't connect to the server. Before the crash everything works fine. If I enter the url in a browser I get the login on my server and everything is fine. Sync client on my pc althoug works without problems. I use a Galaxy Tab 2 10.1 with Cyanogen Mod 11, and current owncloud app (Ver 1.9.1). Owncloud-Server ist 8.2.2 on BananaPi with Debian Wheezy an nginx. SSL enabled, SSL certificate from LetsEncrypt. I connect to the server with an DynDns Domain name like https://myDynDns.com:40000
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="220">
			<summary>Typo in the Android transifex XML</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1564</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1564</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		String number 358: &quot;Settings, database and server certificates from %1$s's data will be deleted permanentlty. \n\nDownloaded files will be kept untouched.\n\nThis process can take some time.&quot; permanentlty --&gt; permanently Steps to reproduce https://www.transifex.com/owncloud-org/owncloud/viewstrings/#is/android/74359823 There are some other; is this really the best place to announce typos?
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="221">
			<summary>Upload files: automatically create thumbnail</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1566</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1566</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		When uploading an image the app should automatically generate a thumbnail. This enhances the UX as the app has only to generate thumbnails for files on the server when entering a folder.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="222">
			<summary>Can't open the file using android develpoer</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1571</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1571</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Expected behaviour Tell us what should happen Actual behaviour Tell us what happens instead Steps to reproduce Environment data Android version: Device model: Stock or customized system: ownCloud app version: ownCloud server version: Logs Web server error log Insert your webserver log here
 ownCloud log (data/owncloud.log) Insert your ownCloud log here
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="223">
			<summary>Need to view from server without downloading</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1574</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1574</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Let's say I upload some images from my Android phone's photo gallery into a folder called &quot;Uploads&quot; on my ownCloud server. When I use the ownCloud app to view the Uploads folder, if I tap an image that I want to see, it gets automatically downloaded to my phone and put in a new folder named Uploads. Great... If I view 100 photos now I have 100 duplicate images on my phone wasting space. Seems to me the act of downloading and saving, as opposed to simply viewing the image on the server, should be an optional selection. For example long press on the image and choose Download from a popup menu.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="224">
			<summary>If password not enforced, error message not found</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1580</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1580</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Steps to reproduce In server side, enable password policy app, set a policy, and disable password enforcing for links In app, share by link with a password that not match the previously set-up policy Actual behaviour No feedback about the error is returned Expected behaviour A message is shown about the error Environment Tested with Nexus9 v6, server v9 enterprise
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="225">
			<summary>Synced Files disappear on Samsung Galaxy S6 every day</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1588</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1588</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Expected behaviour Files that were synchronized should stay on my smartphone until i delete them (local or remote) Actual behaviour All files get deleted by Samsungs Smart Manager App every day (or even faster??). The app somehow recognizes the synchronized files as temporary files and cleans up storage as soon as a (unknown) limit is reached. The app can't be uninstalled/deactivated as it is a preinstalled system app by Samsung. Steps to reproduce Synchronize a file/folder in the client Start Smart Manager app and cleanup storage All synced files are gone Environment data Android version: 6.0.1 Device model: Samsung Galaxy S6 Stock or customized system: stock ownCloud app version: 1.9.1 ownCloud server version: 9.0
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="226">
			<summary>Enhancement: Search option</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1589</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1589</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Expected behaviour It would be great to have the ability to search from within the app. This could be either folderwise (in the long press menu) or at the top right corner of the app - that's were I expected it to be. Possible Implementation Search function could just call the serverside search function and display its results. Environment data Android version: Any Device model: Any ownCloud app version: 1.9.1 ownCloud server version: 9.0
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="227">
			<summary>weird problem (only mine!)</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1593</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1593</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		please help me to solve this weird problem: i've installed owncloud on alt f firmware on my nas and it works gr8 in local i can use it via web or with the app on my android device. so i've tested with external connections, i can use it via browser perfectly.. but i can log in with the app, without getting any file, the app writes &quot;nothing is inside! upload something&quot; if i try to upload or create a folder.. it gives me error, also i already tested other apps... nothing changed!! HELP ME PLEASE!
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="228">
			<summary>Log.wtf() should not be used unless an assertion fails</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1603</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1603</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Expected behaviour ownCloud should not crash on any build for non-assertion failures Actual behaviour ownCloud crashes when Log.wtf is called on userdebug devices. Steps to reproduce Run ownCloud on userdebug build on Android Log into demo.owncloud.org This crashes either immediately or after you have signed in seemingly depending on the speed of your phone (if it can display the file list fragment before it switches to login activity) Can this problem be reproduced with the official owncloud server? (url: https://demo.owncloud.org, user: test, password: test) Yes. Environment data Android version: Android MHC19Q Device model: Nexus 6P Stock or customized system: Stock compiled as userdebug using instructions at https://source.android.com/source/building.html ownCloud app version: ownCloud server version: Logs Web server error log Insert your webserver log here
 ownCloud log (data/owncloud.log) Insert your ownCloud log here
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="229">
			<summary>BIG file upload slow</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1619</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1619</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		wrong place
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="230">
			<summary>Cannot import into Android Studio</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1678</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1678</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Not sure if I'm doing this correctly but, I've read the SETUP.md file I've imported the project into Android Studio However I cannot do anything as it keeps giving me this error: Error:A problem occurred configuring root project 'android-stable'. Cannot evaluate module owncloud-android-library : Configuration with name 'default' not found. I've tried using different branches. I've ran the setup_env.bat file and still nothing Any help?
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="231">
			<summary>[2.0.0] Unclear German translation in Uploads view</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1691</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1691</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Steps to reproduce Install ownCloud 2.0.0 on a Andoid device that runs German as language Open the ownCloud application and goto &quot;Uploads&quot; view Tab the &quot;Option&quot; Button in the right top Try to understand what I can do in this menu: Can some explain what the options in the Upload menu are good for? The German translation doesn't make sense at all in my eyes: I have no idea what the app should when I choose on of the four options I have no idea what the app actually does when I choose on of the four options The german translation doesn't make sense at all Manual doesn't help: https://doc.owncloud.org/android/android_app.html#managing-files If someone can provide me with the English translation I'll be happy to translate into German. I saw more German participants here, so all are invited to discuss.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="232">
			<summary>Uploads get stuck always at 57 % !!!!</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1701</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1701</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Actual behaviour -Tell us what happens Uploads get stuck Expected behaviour -Tell us what should happen Upload should be successfull Steps to reproduce Can this problem be reproduced with the official owncloud server? (url: https://demo.owncloud.org, user: test, password: test) Environment data Android version: 4.4.2 Device model: Galaxy Grand 2 Stock or customized system: ownCloud client version: 2.0 ownCloud server version: 9.02 Logs Web server error log Insert your webserver log here
 ownCloud log (data/owncloud.log) Insert your ownCloud log here
 Every upload - immediate or initated - get stuck at 57%
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="233">
			<summary>Meeting me</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1708</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1708</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Actual behaviour -Tell us what happens Expected behaviour -Tell us what should happen Steps to reproduce Can this problem be reproduced with the official owncloud server? (url: https://demo.owncloud.org, user: test, password: test) Environment data Android version: Device model: Stock or customized system: ownCloud app version: ownCloud server version: Logs Web server error log Insert your webserver log here
 ownCloud log (data/owncloud.log) Insert your ownCloud log here
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="234">
			<summary>Create a ThumbImageView</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1721</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1721</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Thumbnails of images are currently shown in 3 different places. The uploadlist, the local file browser and the normal folder view of an nextcloud folder. The code to generate a thumbnail / kickof the thumbnail generation is present in all of there places. To unify this, i would like to propose a ThumbImageView class which subclases ImageView. This Class should handle all concern regarding File or OCFile -&gt; Thumbnail, by calling ThumbManager and so on. The ImageView objects are reused in the list views, all code accesing these Views has to check whether the reference they use, still refer to a View with the initial File, this could be solved by having a Reference to OCFile or File on the ThumbImageView aswell as the unique thumbnail CacheKey! So we have some new methods like void setFile(File file); void setOCFile(OCFile file); int getCacheKey(); (maybe override .hashCode(), but this could be problematic with OCFiles not existing) Another possibility would be to introduce two additional classes FileThumbImageView and OCFileThumbImageView.. As far as i understand it, the Upload Queue and local filebrowser lists use File and the nextcloud folder browser uses OCFile.. This should only a refactor not any addition of new functionality.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="235">
			<summary>[Feature request] Rename uploaded pictures with a friendly name</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1723</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1723</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		I noticed that with the dropbox app when I take a picture from my phone it uploads the picture and changes the name from IMG_YYYYMMDD_SOME_OTHER_CHARS.jpg to a more friendly YYYY-MM-DD HH.MM.SS.jpg Is there some way to do that also with the owncloud app?
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="236">
			<summary>degsowncloudandroid</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1728</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1728</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Actual behaviour -Tell us what happens Expected behaviour -Tell us what should happen Steps to reproduce Can this problem be reproduced with the official owncloud server? (url: https://demo.owncloud.org, user: test, password: test) Environment data Android version: Device model: Stock or customized system: ownCloud app version: ownCloud server version: Logs Web server error log Insert your webserver log here
 ownCloud log (data/owncloud.log) Insert your ownCloud log here
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="237">
			<summary>view not download - how?</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1739</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1739</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		I installed Owncloud and am loving it except for the mobile app (android). I'm use to the Dropbox app. The Owncloud app downloads the file before I can view it where Dropbox allows me to view automatically. Can Owncloud do this and how? If not, can someone tell me how to change the default download directory for the mobile app as I don't want my phones memory filling up when I have an external memory card I could be using. I'm using a Samsung Galaxy S4 running 4.4.4 stock ownCloud app version: 2.0.1 ownCloud server version: 8.0 Thank you
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="238">
			<summary>Error in res/values/strings.xml</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1741</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1741</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Pushing translations for resource owncloud.android: Pushing source file (res/values/strings.xml) Exception: Could not import file: Bad '' element in line number 459. The plurals element in the uploaded content has 3 plural forms but language 'English (en)' requires 2 plural forms.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="239">
			<summary>Automatic Picture Upload on Android not working</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1747</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1747</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Actual behaviour The owncloud Android app is enabled to upload pictures automatically. However, this does not work on my Galaxy A3 / Android 5.1.1 Manual upload through the app works, hence it can't be a matter of permission but must be something else. Please let me know what information I can provide to further narrow down the issue and help solve it. Many thanks in advance!
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="240">
			<summary>Update copyright</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1751</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1751</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Update Copyright to 👍 @copyright Copyright (c) 2016, ownCloud GmbH. 
 Related to: owncloud/core#25518
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="241">
			<summary>Feature Request: Option: Upload only if phone in charge mode</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1756</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1756</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Expected behaviour A setting in the config section: Upload media only when the battery is in charge mode
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="242">
			<summary>Auto upload, exif problem</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1761</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1761</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Actual behaviour When the app automatically upload a picture after it's been taken, the exif of the image file indicate the date of the upload, not the original date and time of the picture. If the upload succeed imediately after the photo shoot, there is not big problem. But when the upload fails, the exif of the image indicate the datetime of the retried upload, not the original exif. Expected behaviour The exif of an uploaded image should always be the original one. Else, it mess up the order and the chronology and it's a problem. Environment data Android version: up to date. Device model: One Plus One Stock or customized system: Cyanogen ownCloud app version: up to date. ownCloud server version: 9.0.1
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="243">
			<summary>Issue report</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1762</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1762</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		ExtendedListFragment.onCreateView() mProgressBar = (ProgressBar) v.findViewById(R.id.syncProgressBar); mProgressBar is null, so setProgressBarAsIndeterminate method crash. Need remove merge block in res/layout/top_progress_bar.xml.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="244">
			<summary>View Images before downloading</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1769</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1769</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Is it possible to live view images and docs on the app, like the browser version? Images only can viewed with a green tick... That would be very nice :) Regards :) //EDIT: Missing only the fullscreen view, middlebig view is already included...
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="245">
			<summary>No Photo/video upload for Android 7 (Android n preview 5)</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1773</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1773</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Actual behaviour Installed owncloud 2.1 for Android on Nexus 5X running Android 7 NPD90G build (beta 5). Set up the client and it connects and shows all the dirs. Gave the app permission to access the Photo's. Enabled direct uploads, set it to a proper directory, but it won't start uploading. Expected behaviour It should start uploading Steps to reproduce Grab an Android 7 beta phone Download Owncloud 2.1 for Android Set up your account in the app Enable direct uploads Snap a picture Can this problem be reproduced with the official owncloud server? YEs Environment data Android version: NPD90G Device model: Nexus 5X Stock or customized system: Stock ownCloud app version: 2.1 ownCloud server version: Using the TransIP version called Stack. Version unknown. Logs Web server error log Na ownCloud log (data/owncloud.log) Na
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="246">
			<summary>let users know what kind of error occurred</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1776</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1776</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Actual behavior -Tell us what happens i have uploaded something, again and again it worked but than ive got an unknown error Expected behavior -Tell us what should happen a proper error message should be shown instead what i did then i logged into the webinterface and seen that i am out of storage, i have increased my quota and now anything fine again but first i was quite confused about that facile/meaningless error message. you should fix that! Steps to reproduce fill your owncloud account until its full upload something Can this problem be reproduced with the official owncloud server? (url: https://demo.owncloud.org, user: test, password: test) its clear i dont need to do nonsense things Environment data Android version: 6.0.1 Device model: not relevant, just a phone like everyphone else Stock or customized system: cyanogenmod 13 ownCloud app version: 2.1.0 (from fdroid) THATS ENOUGH IRRELEVANT QUESTIONS, WHY DONT ALLOW USERS FREE TEXT? please fix that. thanks in advance
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="247">
			<summary>use correct emojs in repo description</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1777</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1777</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		if you have to use this modern nonsense then you should at least use 📱 (U+1F4F1 Mobile Phone) or 🖁 instead of this unbefitting fixed-line telephone
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="248">
			<summary>Error compiling [branch: externalSD2]</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1794</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1794</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		should branch externalSD2 compile ok? Actual behaviour error while compiling Expected behaviour hopefully compile ok Steps to reproduce see full log here: https://circleci.com/gh/zoff99/owncloud_android/7 Errors are: &gt; Building 56% &gt; :compileDebugJava/home/ubuntu/owncloud_android/src/com/owncloud/android/MainApp.java:96: error: method startLogging in class Log_OC cannot be applied to given types;
&gt; Building 56% &gt; :compileDebugJava            Log_OC.startLogging(MainApp.storagePath);
&gt; Building 56% &gt; :compileDebugJava                  ^
&gt; Building 56% &gt; :compileDebugJava  required: no arguments
&gt; Building 56% &gt; :compileDebugJava  found: String
&gt; Building 56% &gt; :compileDebugJava  reason: actual and formal argument lists differ in length
&gt; Building 56% &gt; :compileDebugJava/home/ubuntu/owncloud_android/src/com/owncloud/android/ui/activity/StorageMigration.java:249: error: cannot find symbol
&gt; Building 56% &gt; :compileDebugJava            Log_OC.stopLogging();
&gt; Building 56% &gt; :compileDebugJava                  ^
&gt; Building 56% &gt; :compileDebugJava  symbol:   method stopLogging()
&gt; Building 56% &gt; :compileDebugJava  location: class Log_OC
&gt; Building 56% &gt; :compileDebugJava/home/ubuntu/owncloud_android/src/com/owncloud/android/ui/activity/StorageMigration.java:262: error: method startLogging in class Log_OC cannot be applied to given types;
&gt; Building 56% &gt; :compileDebugJava            Log_OC.startLogging(mStorageTarget);
&gt; Building 56% &gt; :compileDebugJava                  ^
&gt; Building 56% &gt; :compileDebugJava  required: no arguments
&gt; Building 56% &gt; :compileDebugJava  found: String
&gt; Building 56% &gt; :compileDebugJava  reason: actual and formal argument lists differ in length
&gt; Building 56% &gt; :compileDebugJava/home/ubuntu/owncloud_android/src/com/owncloud/android/ui/activity/StorageMigration.java:287: error: cannot find symbol
&gt; Building 56% &gt; :compileDebugJava            Log_OC.stopLogging();
&gt; Building 56% &gt; :compileDebugJava                  ^
&gt; Building 56% &gt; :compileDebugJava  symbol:   method stopLogging()
&gt; Building 56% &gt; :compileDebugJava  location: class Log_OC
&gt; Building 56% &gt; :compileDebugJava/home/ubuntu/owncloud_android/src/com/owncloud/android/ui/activity/StorageMigration.java:321: error: method startLogging in class Log_OC cannot be applied to given types;
&gt; Building 56% &gt; :compileDebugJava                Log_OC.startLogging(mStorageSource);
&gt; Building 56% &gt; :compileDebugJava                      ^
&gt; Building 56% &gt; :compileDebugJava  required: no arguments
&gt; Building 56% &gt; :compileDebugJava  found: String
&gt; Building 56% &gt; :compileDebugJava  reason: actual and formal argument lists differ in length
&gt; Building 56% &gt; :compileDebugJava/home/ubuntu/owncloud_android/src/com/owncloud/android/ui/activity/StorageMigration.java:328: error: method startLogging in class Log_OC cannot be applied to given types;
&gt; Building 56% &gt; :compileDebugJava            Log_OC.startLogging(mStorageTarget);
&gt; Building 56% &gt; :compileDebugJava                  ^
&gt; Building 56% &gt; :compileDebugJava  required: no arguments
&gt; Building 56% &gt; :compileDebugJava  found: String
&gt; Building 56% &gt; :compileDebugJava  reason: actual and formal argument lists differ in length
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="249">
			<summary>able to use different Storage (external SD)</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1804</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1804</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Actual behaviour storage directory for the whole app not selectable Expected behaviour select from available storage cards without this the app fills up the internal storage and stops working (out of space), at the same time lots of GB are free on the extSD Card. what is the reason that the branch for this [externalSD2] is not merged? it seems to work just fine
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="250">
			<summary>Unable to Login to account with TOTP Two-Factor Authentication enabled</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1815</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1815</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Actual behaviour Account with two-factor enabled displays &quot;Wrong username or password&quot; but without two-factor enabled it logs in correctly. Expected behaviour Needs support for two-factor authentication (new screen to prompt for otp if the account has it enabled.) Steps to reproduce Implement Two Factor App (TOTP Provider 0.4.1) Set an account to use it (i.e. with Google Authenticator) Account can no longer log in using Android app Can this problem be reproduced with the official owncloud server? (url: https://demo.owncloud.org, user: test, password: test) App is unavailable there (and it would lock the account if it were) Environment data Android version: 6.0.1 Device model: SM-N920V Stock or customized system: Stock ownCloud app version: 2.1.2 ownCloud server version: 9.1.1 Logs Web server error log Insert your webserver log here
 ownCloud log (data/owncloud.log) Insert your ownCloud log here
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="251">
			<summary>here is values-zh-rCN,all translated,add something below</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1830</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1830</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		here is values-zh-rCN,all translated,add something below values-zh-rCN.zip
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="252">
			<summary>Login fails</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1832</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1832</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		### Reproduction of the problem use login screen of owncloud app version 2.1.2. Fill in my own owncloud https URL (self-signed certificate). Note that this happens also in pure http. Give valid credentials, and push on CONNECT button. I got the message: unknown error occured just below the password field ### Expected behaviour Login success. Can this problem be reproduced with the official owncloud server? (url: https://demo.owncloud.org, user: test, password: test) no, with demo.owncloud.org, the login process is working well. ### Environment data Android version: 6.0.1 Device model: Galaxy S6 Stock or customized system: Stock ownCloud app version: 2.1.2 ownCloud server version: this is the latest version from apt repository in raspbian. ### Logs from web server: tail -5 /var/log/apache2/access.log [24/Oct/2016:11:10:22 +0200] &quot;HEAD /owncloud/remote.php/webdav/ HTTP/1.1&quot; 200 476 &quot;-&quot; &quot;Mozilla/5.0 (Android) ownCloud-android/2.1.2&quot; [24/Oct/2016:11:10:22 +0200] &quot;GET /owncloud/index.php/ocs/cloud/user?format=json HTTP/1.1&quot; 302 775 &quot;-&quot; &quot;Mozilla/5.0 (Android) ownCloud-android/2.1.2&quot; [24/Oct/2016:11:10:22 +0200] &quot;GET /owncloud/index.php/ocs/cloud/user?format=json HTTP/1.1&quot; 302 775 &quot;-&quot; &quot;Mozilla/5.0 (Android) ownCloud-android/2.1.2&quot; [24/Oct/2016:11:10:22 +0200] &quot;GET /owncloud/index.php/ocs/cloud/user?format=json HTTP/1.1&quot; 302 775 &quot;-&quot; &quot;Mozilla/5.0 (Android) ownCloud-android/2.1.2&quot; [24/Oct/2016:11:10:23 +0200] &quot;GET /owncloud/index.php/ocs/cloud/user?format=json HTTP/1.1&quot; 302 775 &quot;-&quot; &quot;Mozilla/5.0 (Android) ownCloud-android/2.1.2&quot; from owncloud: nothing to show
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="253">
			<summary>Mini FAB labels bug</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1834</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1834</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Actual behaviour Mini FAB labels disappear due to a bug Expected behaviour Mini FAB labels should always be visible Steps to reproduce Open owncloud App Click on &quot;+&quot; sign on bottom right of the screen (See screen shot) Do not upload anything and just go back to the App Close the application (without closing the application it works normal) Open the app again Click on the &quot;+&quot; sign again 7- Mini FAB labels will not show
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="254">
			<summary>share with users or groups</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1837</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1837</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		when share with users or groups the search function not working Expected behaviour when type text the list show with all filter users or groups that contains text Steps to reproduce select file share select share with users or groups Environment data Android version: android studio 1.3.2 Device model: samsung not 3
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="255">
			<summary>App crash on refresh</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1838</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1838</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Actual behaviour The app crashes when refreshing (or loading to show files) Expected behaviour Just work. Steps to reproduce Lunch the app Refresh to get the files list Crash Can this problem be reproduced with the official owncloud server? No, it's working fine. (url: https://demo.owncloud.org, user: test, password: test) Environment data Android version: down in the log Device model: down in the log Stock or customized system: stock ownCloud app version: Beta 20160606 ownCloud server version: 9.1.2 Logs From the beta app ************ CAUSE OF ERROR ************ java.lang.RuntimeException: Parcelable encountered IOException writing serializable object (name = com.owncloud.android.lib.common.operations.RemoteOperationResult) at android.os.Parcel.writeSerializable(Parcel.java:1468) at android.os.Parcel.writeValue(Parcel.java:1416) at android.os.Parcel.writeArrayMapInternal(Parcel.java:686) at android.os.BaseBundle.writeToParcelInner(BaseBundle.java:1330) at android.os.Bundle.writeToParcel(Bundle.java:1079) at android.os.Parcel.writeBundle(Parcel.java:711) at android.content.Intent.writeToParcel(Intent.java:7793) at android.app.ActivityManagerProxy.broadcastIntent(ActivityManagerNative.java:3043) at android.app.ContextImpl.sendStickyBroadcast(ContextImpl.java:1016) at android.content.ContextWrapper.sendStickyBroadcast(ContextWrapper.java:509) at com.owncloud.android.operations.RefreshFolderOperation.sendLocalBroadcast(RefreshFolderOperation.java:519) at com.owncloud.android.operations.RefreshFolderOperation.run(RefreshFolderOperation.java:208) at com.owncloud.android.lib.common.operations.RemoteOperation.run(RemoteOperation.java:303) at java.lang.Thread.run(Thread.java:818) Caused by: java.io.NotSerializableException: org.apache.harmony.xml.dom.ElementImpl at java.io.ObjectOutputStream.writeNewObject(ObjectOutputStream.java:1344) at java.io.ObjectOutputStream.writeObjectInternal(ObjectOutputStream.java:1651) at java.io.ObjectOutputStream.writeObject(ObjectOutputStream.java:1497) at java.io.ObjectOutputStream.writeObject(ObjectOutputStream.java:1461) at java.io.ObjectOutputStream.writeFieldValues(ObjectOutputStream.java:959) at java.io.ObjectOutputStream.defaultWriteObject(ObjectOutputStream.java:360) at java.io.ObjectOutputStream.writeHierarchy(ObjectOutputStream.java:1054) at java.io.ObjectOutputStream.writeNewObject(ObjectOutputStream.java:1384) at java.io.ObjectOutputStream.writeObjectInternal(ObjectOutputStream.java:1651) at java.io.ObjectOutputStream.writeObject(ObjectOutputStream.java:1497) at java.io.ObjectOutputStream.writeObject(ObjectOutputStream.java:1461) at java.io.ObjectOutputStream.writeFieldValues(ObjectOutputStream.java:959) at java.io.ObjectOutputStream.defaultWriteObject(ObjectOutputStream.java:360) at java.io.ObjectOutputStream.writeHierarchy(ObjectOutputStream.java:1054) at java.io.ObjectOutputStream.writeNewObject(ObjectOutputStream.java:1384) at java.io.ObjectOutputStream.writeObjectInternal(ObjectOutputStream.java:1651) at java.io.ObjectOutputStream.writeObject(ObjectOutputStream.java:1497) at java.io.ObjectOutputStream.writeObject(ObjectOutputStream.java:1461) at android.os.Parcel.writeSerializable(Parcel.java:1463) ... 13 more ************ DEVICE INFORMATION *********** Brand: google Device: hammerhead Model: Nexus 5 Id: MOB30M Product: hammerhead ************ FIRMWARE ************ SDK: 23 Release: 6.0.1 Incremental: 2862625
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="256">
			<summary>Downloading a image while offline displays a black &quot;downloading screen&quot; forever.</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1856</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1856</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Actual behaviour When trying to download an image while offline, the app is stuck in a black screen. Expected behaviour When in &quot;disconnected mode&quot;, the Downloading... black screen shouldn't be displayed or as soon as the Download failed notification arrives at the device, stop showing it. Steps to reproduce Turn off WiFi/data connection Open an image/video (to see the differences) image stays stuck on the black Downloading... screen video shows the Downloading... progress bar briefly Environment data Android version: 4.3 Device model: Nexus 7 Stock/customized system: Stock ownCloud app version: 2.2.0
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="257">
			<summary>java.lang.SecurityException: uid ***** cannot get user data for accounts of type: bitfire.at.davdroid</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1866</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1866</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Actual behaviour When starting app, it crashes immediately. Expected behaviour I expect the app to start, and not crash immediately. Steps to reproduce Upgrade to version 2.2.0 Click app icon Crash Can this problem be reproduced with the official owncloud server? Unknown, cannot access UI to set this up. Environment data Android version: Android 7.1.1 Device model: Nexus 5X Stock or customized system: Stock ownCloud app version: 2.2.0 (from F-Droid) ownCloud server version: 9.1.3-1.1 (Ubuntu) Logs Web server error log Not relevant ownCloud log (data/owncloud.log) 12-26 15:31:52.374 4931 7656 I ActivityManager: Start proc 14814:com.owncloud.android/u0a89 for activity com.owncloud.android/.ui.activity.FileDisplayActivity 12-26 15:31:52.458 14814 14814 W System : ClassLoader referenced unknown path: /data/app/com.owncloud.android-1/lib/arm64 12-26 15:31:52.586 14814 14829 D ThumbnailsCacheManager: create dir: /storage/emulated/0/Android/data/com.owncloud.android/cache/thumbnailCache 12-26 15:31:52.591 14814 14814 V FileDisplayActivity: onCreate() start 12-26 15:31:52.609 14814 14814 W art : Before Android 4.1, method android.graphics.PorterDuffColorFilter android.support.graphics.drawable.VectorDrawableCompat.updateTintFilter(android.graphics.PorterDuffColorFilter, android.content.res.ColorStateList, android.graphics.PorterDuff$Mode) would have incorrectly overridden the package-private method in android.graphics.drawable.Drawable 12-26 15:31:52.613 14814 14814 D FileDisplayActivity: onCreate(Bundle) starting 12-26 15:31:52.703 14814 14814 I AppCompatViewInflater: app:theme is now deprecated. Please move to using android:theme instead. 12-26 15:31:52.780 14814 14814 V FileDisplayActivity: onCreate() end 12-26 15:31:52.782 14814 14814 V FileDisplayActivity: onStart() start 12-26 15:31:52.782 14814 14814 D FileDisplayActivity: onStart() starting 12-26 15:31:52.900 14814 14814 D FileDisplayActivity: Initializing Fragments in onAccountChanged.. 12-26 15:31:52.900 14814 14814 E FileDisplayActivity: Access to unexisting list of files fragment!! 12-26 15:31:52.900 14814 14814 E FileDisplayActivity: Still have a chance to lose the initializacion of list fragment &gt;( 12-26 15:31:52.908 14814 14831 D NetworkUtils: Searching known-servers store at /data/user/0/com.owncloud.android/files/knownServers.bks 12-26 15:31:52.909 14814 14814 V FileDisplayActivity: onStart() end 12-26 15:31:52.910 14814 14831 D NetworkSecurityConfig: No Network Security Config specified, using platform default 12-26 15:31:52.920 14814 14814 E FileDisplayActivity: Access to unexisting list of files fragment!! 12-26 15:31:52.920 14814 14814 E FileDisplayActivity: OCFileListFragment is null 12-26 15:31:52.921 14814 14831 D OwnCloudClient #0: Creating OwnCloudClient 12-26 15:31:52.922 14814 14831 D AccountUtils: Restoring cookies for @ 12-26 15:31:52.922 14814 14814 V FileDisplayActivity: onResume() start 12-26 15:31:52.923 14814 14814 D FileDisplayActivity: onResume() starting 12-26 15:31:52.923 14814 14814 E OCFileListFragment: onAttach 12-26 15:31:52.924 14814 14814 I OCFileListFragment: onCreateView() start 12-26 15:31:52.924 14814 14814 D ExtendedListFragment: onCreateView 12-26 15:31:52.936 14814 14831 D AccountUtils: Restoring cookies for @ 12-26 15:31:52.941 14814 14831 E ThumbnailsCacheManager: Generation of avatar for null failed 12-26 15:31:52.941 14814 14831 E ThumbnailsCacheManager: java.lang.SecurityException: uid 10089 cannot get user data for accounts of type: bitfire.at.davdroid 12-26 15:31:52.941 14814 14831 E ThumbnailsCacheManager: at android.os.Parcel.readException(Parcel.java:1684) 12-26 15:31:52.941 14814 14831 E ThumbnailsCacheManager: at android.os.Parcel.readException(Parcel.java:1637) 12-26 15:31:52.941 14814 14831 E ThumbnailsCacheManager: at android.accounts.IAccountManager$Stub$Proxy.getUserData(IAccountManager.java:887) 12-26 15:31:52.941 14814 14831 E ThumbnailsCacheManager: at android.accounts.AccountManager.getUserData(AccountManager.java:400) 12-26 15:31:52.941 14814 14831 E ThumbnailsCacheManager: at com.owncloud.android.lib.common.accounts.AccountUtils.restoreCookies(AccountUtils.java:300) 12-26 15:31:52.941 14814 14831 E ThumbnailsCacheManager: at com.owncloud.android.lib.common.accounts.AccountUtils.restoreCookies(AccountUtils.java:343) 12-26 15:31:52.941 14814 14831 E ThumbnailsCacheManager: at com.owncloud.android.lib.common.SingleSessionManager.getClientFor(SingleSessionManager.java:123) 12-26 15:31:52.941 14814 14831 E ThumbnailsCacheManager: at com.owncloud.android.lib.common.DynamicSessionManager.getClientFor(DynamicSessionManager.java:40) 12-26 15:31:52.941 14814 14831 E ThumbnailsCacheManager: at com.owncloud.android.datamodel.ThumbnailsCacheManager$GetAvatarTask.doInBackground(ThumbnailsCacheManager.java:443) 12-26 15:31:52.941 14814 14831 E ThumbnailsCacheManager: at com.owncloud.android.datamodel.ThumbnailsCacheManager$GetAvatarTask.doInBackground(ThumbnailsCacheManager.java:383) 12-26 15:31:52.941 14814 14831 E ThumbnailsCacheManager: at android.os.AsyncTask$2.call(AsyncTask.java:305) 12-26 15:31:52.941 14814 14831 E ThumbnailsCacheManager: at java.util.concurrent.FutureTask.run(FutureTask.java:237) 12-26 15:31:52.941 14814 14831 E ThumbnailsCacheManager: at android.os.AsyncTask$SerialExecutor$1.run(AsyncTask.java:243) 12-26 15:31:52.941 14814 14831 E ThumbnailsCacheManager: at java.util.concurrent.ThreadPoolExecutor.runWorker(ThreadPoolExecutor.java:1133) 12-26 15:31:52.941 14814 14831 E ThumbnailsCacheManager: at java.util.concurrent.ThreadPoolExecutor$Worker.run(ThreadPoolExecutor.java:607) 12-26 15:31:52.941 14814 14831 E ThumbnailsCacheManager: at java.lang.Thread.run(Thread.java:761) 12-26 15:31:52.947 14814 14832 D OwnCloudClient #1: Creating OwnCloudClient 12-26 15:31:52.947 14814 14832 D AccountUtils: Restoring cookies for @ 12-26 15:31:52.948 14814 14832 D AccountUtils: Restoring cookies for @ 12-26 15:31:52.950 14814 14832 E ThumbnailsCacheManager: Generation of avatar for null failed 12-26 15:31:52.950 14814 14832 E ThumbnailsCacheManager: java.lang.SecurityException: uid 10089 cannot get user data for accounts of type: bitfire.at.davdroid 12-26 15:31:52.950 14814 14832 E ThumbnailsCacheManager: at android.os.Parcel.readException(Parcel.java:1684) 12-26 15:31:52.950 14814 14832 E ThumbnailsCacheManager: at android.os.Parcel.readException(Parcel.java:1637) 12-26 15:31:52.950 14814 14832 E ThumbnailsCacheManager: at android.accounts.IAccountManager$Stub$Proxy.getUserData(IAccountManager.java:887) 12-26 15:31:52.950 14814 14832 E ThumbnailsCacheManager: at android.accounts.AccountManager.getUserData(AccountManager.java:400) 12-26 15:31:52.950 14814 14832 E ThumbnailsCacheManager: at com.owncloud.android.lib.common.accounts.AccountUtils.restoreCookies(AccountUtils.java:300) 12-26 15:31:52.950 14814 14832 E ThumbnailsCacheManager: at com.owncloud.android.lib.common.accounts.AccountUtils.restoreCookies(AccountUtils.java:343) 12-26 15:31:52.950 14814 14832 E ThumbnailsCacheManager: at com.owncloud.android.lib.common.SingleSessionManager.getClientFor(SingleSessionManager.java:123) 12-26 15:31:52.950 14814 14832 E ThumbnailsCacheManager: at com.owncloud.android.lib.common.DynamicSessionManager.getClientFor(DynamicSessionManager.java:40) 12-26 15:31:52.950 14814 14832 E ThumbnailsCacheManager: at com.owncloud.android.datamodel.ThumbnailsCacheManager$GetAvatarTask.doInBackground(ThumbnailsCacheManager.java:443) 12-26 15:31:52.950 14814 14832 E ThumbnailsCacheManager: at com.owncloud.android.datamodel.ThumbnailsCacheManager$GetAvatarTask.doInBackground(ThumbnailsCacheManager.java:383) 12-26 15:31:52.950 14814 14832 E ThumbnailsCacheManager: at android.os.AsyncTask$2.call(AsyncTask.java:305) 12-26 15:31:52.950 14814 14832 E ThumbnailsCacheManager: at java.util.concurrent.FutureTask.run(FutureTask.java:237) 12-26 15:31:52.950 14814 14832 E ThumbnailsCacheManager: at android.os.AsyncTask$SerialExecutor$1.run(AsyncTask.java:243) 12-26 15:31:52.950 14814 14832 E ThumbnailsCacheManager: at java.util.concurrent.ThreadPoolExecutor.runWorker(ThreadPoolExecutor.java:1133) 12-26 15:31:52.950 14814 14832 E ThumbnailsCacheManager: at java.util.concurrent.ThreadPoolExecutor$Worker.run(ThreadPoolExecutor.java:607) 12-26 15:31:52.950 14814 14832 E ThumbnailsCacheManager: at java.lang.Thread.run(Thread.java:761) 12-26 15:31:52.995 14814 14814 I OCFileListFragment: onCreateView() end 12-26 15:31:52.996 14814 14814 E OCFileListFragment: onActivityCreated() start 12-26 15:31:53.137 14814 14814 V FileDisplayActivity: onResume() end 12-26 15:31:53.160 14814 14814 D OperationsService: Creating service 12-26 15:31:53.164 14814 14814 D FileDownloader: Creating service 12-26 15:31:53.170 14814 14814 D FileUploader: Creating service 12-26 15:31:53.173 14814 14814 V UploadsStorageManager: Updating state of any killed upload 12-26 15:31:53.183 14814 14814 V UploadsStorageManager: No upload was killed 12-26 15:31:53.185 14814 14814 D FileObserverService: onCreate 12-26 15:31:53.187 14814 14814 D FileObserverService: Starting command Intent { act=com.owncloud.android.services.observer.FileObserverService.action.START_OBSERVATION cmp=com.owncloud.android/.services.observer.FileObserverService } 12-26 15:31:53.187 14814 14814 D FileObserverService: Loading all available offline files from database to start watching them 12-26 15:31:53.225 14814 14814 V FileObserverService: Adding a file to be watched 12-26 15:31:53.226 14814 14814 D FileObserverService: Observer added for folder /storage/emulated/0/owncloud/@// 12-26 15:31:53.235 14814 14814 D AvailableOfflineObserver: Watching folder /storage/emulated/0/owncloud/@// for changes in ************* 12-26 15:31:53.235 14814 14814 D FileObserverService: Added /storage/emulated/0/owncloud/@///************* to list of observed children 12-26 15:31:53.237 14814 14814 V FileObserverService: Adding a file to be watched 12-26 15:31:53.238 14814 14814 D AvailableOfflineObserver: Watching folder /storage/emulated/0/owncloud/@// for changes in ************* 12-26 15:31:53.238 14814 14814 D FileObserverService: Added /storage/emulated/0/owncloud/@///************* to list of observed children 12-26 15:31:53.240 14814 14814 V FileObserverService: Adding a file to be watched 12-26 15:31:53.240 14814 14814 D FileObserverService: Observer added for folder /storage/emulated/0/owncloud/@/************* 12-26 15:31:53.241 14814 14814 D AvailableOfflineObserver: Watching folder /storage/emulated/0/owncloud/@/************* for changes in ************* 12-26 15:31:53.241 14814 14814 D FileObserverService: Added /storage/emulated/0/owncloud/@// to list of observed children 12-26 15:31:53.287 14814 14835 I Adreno : QUALCOMM build : a5b4970, If5818605d9 12-26 15:31:53.287 14814 14835 I Adreno : Build Date : 10/12/16 12-26 15:31:53.287 14814 14835 I Adreno : OpenGL ES Shader Compiler Version: XE031.09.00.04 12-26 15:31:53.287 14814 14835 I Adreno : Local Branch : N24D 12-26 15:31:53.287 14814 14835 I Adreno : Remote Branch : 12-26 15:31:53.287 14814 14835 I Adreno : Remote Branch : 12-26 15:31:53.287 14814 14835 I Adreno : Reconstruct Branch : 12-26 15:31:53.293 14814 14835 I OpenGLRenderer: Initialized EGL, version 1.4 12-26 15:31:53.293 14814 14835 D OpenGLRenderer: Swap behavior 1 12-26 15:31:53.509 14814 14819 I art : Do partial code cache collection, code=15KB, data=25KB 12-26 15:31:53.512 14814 14819 I art : After code cache collection, code=14KB, data=25KB 12-26 15:31:53.512 14814 14819 I art : Increasing code cache capacity to 128KB 12-26 15:31:53.573 14814 14814 D FileActivity: Operations service connected 12-26 15:31:53.574 14814 14814 D FileDisplayActivity: Download service connected 12-26 15:31:53.574 14814 14814 D FileDisplayActivity: Upload service connected 12-26 15:31:53.724 4931 5000 I ActivityManager: Displayed com.owncloud.android/.ui.activity.FileDisplayActivity: +1s364ms 12-26 15:31:53.728 14814 14814 D ExtendedListFragment: Setting progress visibility to true 12-26 15:31:53.735 14814 14842 D OwnCloudClient #2: Creating OwnCloudClient 12-26 15:31:53.735 14814 14842 D AccountUtils: Restoring cookies for @ 12-26 15:31:53.737 14814 14842 D AccountUtils: Restoring cookies for @ 12-26 15:31:53.739 14814 14842 E AndroidRuntime: FATAL EXCEPTION: Thread-2 12-26 15:31:53.739 14814 14842 E AndroidRuntime: Process: com.owncloud.android, PID: 14814 12-26 15:31:53.739 14814 14842 E AndroidRuntime: java.lang.SecurityException: uid 10089 cannot get user data for accounts of type: bitfire.at.davdroid 12-26 15:31:53.739 14814 14842 E AndroidRuntime: at android.os.Parcel.readException(Parcel.java:1684) 12-26 15:31:53.739 14814 14842 E AndroidRuntime: at android.os.Parcel.readException(Parcel.java:1637) 12-26 15:31:53.739 14814 14842 E AndroidRuntime: at android.accounts.IAccountManager$Stub$Proxy.getUserData(IAccountManager.java:887) 12-26 15:31:53.739 14814 14842 E AndroidRuntime: at android.accounts.AccountManager.getUserData(AccountManager.java:400) 12-26 15:31:53.739 14814 14842 E AndroidRuntime: at com.owncloud.android.lib.common.accounts.AccountUtils.restoreCookies(AccountUtils.java:300) 12-26 15:31:53.739 14814 14842 E AndroidRuntime: at com.owncloud.android.lib.common.accounts.AccountUtils.restoreCookies(AccountUtils.java:343) 12-26 15:31:53.739 14814 14842 E AndroidRuntime: at com.owncloud.android.lib.common.SingleSessionManager.getClientFor(SingleSessionManager.java:123) 12-26 15:31:53.739 14814 14842 E AndroidRuntime: at com.owncloud.android.lib.common.DynamicSessionManager.getClientFor(DynamicSessionManager.java:40) 12-26 15:31:53.739 14814 14842 E AndroidRuntime: at com.owncloud.android.lib.common.operations.RemoteOperation.run(RemoteOperation.java:281) 12-26 15:31:53.739 14814 14842 E AndroidRuntime: at java.lang.Thread.run(Thread.java:761) 12-26 15:31:53.744 4931 23330 W ActivityManager: Force finishing activity com.owncloud.android/.ui.activity.FileDisplayActivity
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="258">
			<summary>Need improvement UI of edit_box_dialog</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1872</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1872</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Actual behaviour The EditText in edit_box_dialog.xml has no margin, hence it doesn't look good. Expected behaviour It should atleast have some marginLeft and marginRight having Thanks
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="259">
			<summary>ownCloud Android login to NextCloud 11 servers fails - linked issue recorded below - NC Android has fixed this</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1874</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1874</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Actual behaviour -&quot;An unknown error occurred&quot; response on login attempt Expected behaviour -Login should take place like in the ownCloud 2.2.4 desktop application Steps to reproduce Attempt to log into NextCloud 11 with ownCloud Android 2.2.0 Fail nextcloud/android-library#18 3. Can this problem be reproduced with the official owncloud server? (url: https://demo.owncloud.org, user: test, password: test) Environment data Android version: Marshmallow Device model: S7 Galaxy Stock or customized system: Stock ownCloud app version: ownCloud server version: Logs Web server error log : None Insert your webserver log here
 ownCloud log (data/owncloud.log): Nothing reported Insert your ownCloud log here
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="260">
			<summary>[UX] Main/settings menu only accessible from root folder</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1875</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1875</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Steps Navigate into a deep folder From another app, upload some stuff using the &quot;share&quot; feature and picking ownCloud Wait for upload to finish and all notifications to disappear Now I want to go have a look at the upload list Expected When inside a deep folder, I'd like to have a way to go to the main menu. Actual No way to go to the main menu directly. Need to click the &quot;Back&quot; button on the top left of the mobile app until I reach the root folder. Only then can I access the upload list. I'm not familiar with the regular Android app design, maybe the current approach is an existing and acceptable design pattern. Now you might say that it's not a common use case to want to access the finished upload list and that it's ok to have that menu item there. To be discussed. @davivel @owncloud/design
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="261">
			<summary>Trash icon too close to &quot;three dots&quot; menu</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1877</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1877</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Note: I usually use vimtouch to open text files Install vimtouch (or any other text editor) Upload some text file &quot;test.txt&quot; from another machine In the ownCloud app, navigate into the folder of the file &quot;test.txt&quot; Hold on the &quot;test.txt&quot; item (we want to edit but don't want to view the file with the built-in viewer) Use the &quot;three dots&quot; menu to select &quot;open with&quot; but be clumsy and tap a bit on the left of it Expected No trash icon so close to &quot;three dots&quot; Actual Risk of tapping the delete icon when aiming for the three dots menu. Note: in general I'm not too happy to have to use this menu when editing a file. But due to the new built-in viewer I need to do more manual action to be able to open the file in an external editor. (maybe I'll make another separate report)
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="262">
			<summary>Beta link broken</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1903</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1903</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		The link to the beta version from the README seems to be ´broken (404) https://github.com/owncloud/android/raw/beta/apks/latest.apk
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="263">
			<summary>Automatic upload not working under Nougat on Sony Xperia Z5 Compact</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1912</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1912</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Actual behaviour -Tell us what happens The app (which used to work under 6.x) does not upload pictures taken by the camera anymore automatically after updating my Z5 Compact to Nougat... Expected behaviour -Tell us what should happen Steps to reproduce Can this problem be reproduced with the official owncloud server? (url: https://demo.owncloud.org, user: test, password: test) Environment data Android version: Device model: Stock or customized system: ownCloud app version: ownCloud server version: Logs Web server error log Insert your webserver log here
 ownCloud log (data/owncloud.log) Insert your ownCloud log here
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="264">
			<summary>ownCloud android</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1916</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1916</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Actual behaviour -Tell us what happens Expected behaviour -Tell us what should happen Steps to reproduce Can this problem be reproduced with the official owncloud server? (url: https://demo.owncloud.org, user: test, password: test) Environment data Android version: Device model: Stock or customized system: ownCloud app version: ownCloud server version: Logs Web server error log Insert your webserver log here
 ownCloud log (data/owncloud.log) Insert your ownCloud log here
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="265">
			<summary>Does not work with Android Nougat Samsung Galaxy S7</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1918</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1918</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		When will be working version for Android Nougat On Dans7ng Galaxy S7 does not work upload photos and videos from camera. Expected behaviour -Tell us what should happen I am using stock camera and from Android version 7.0 does not uploading making photos. Now Owncloud apk is totaly useless. On my smartphone there is no problem with Qnap apk qfile. It always send my photos into my owncloud server. Steps to reproduce Can this problem be reproduced with the official owncloud server? (url: https://demo.owncloud.org, user: test, password: test) Environment data Android version: Device model: Stock or customized system: ownCloud app version: ownCloud server version: Logs Web server error log Insert your webserver log here
 ownCloud log (data/owncloud.log) Insert your ownCloud log here
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="266">
			<summary>Does not work with Android Nougat Samsung Galaxy S7</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1920</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1920</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		When will be working version for Android Nougat On Dans7ng Galaxy S7 does not work upload photos and videos from camera. Expected behaviour -Tell us what should happen I am using stock camera and from Android version 7.0 does not uploading making photos. Now Owncloud apk is totaly useless. On my smartphone there is no problem with Qnap apk qfile. It always send my photos into my owncloud server. Steps to reproduce Can this problem be reproduced with the official owncloud server? (url: https://demo.owncloud.org, user: test, password: test) Environment data Android version: Android Nougat 7.0 Device model: Samsung Galaxy S7 Stock or customized system: G930FXXU1DQB7 ownCloud app version: Latest from market 2.3.0 ownCloud server version: 8.0.4 Logs Web server error log Insert your webserver log here
 ownCloud log (data/owncloud.log) Insert your ownCloud log here
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="267">
			<summary>Instant upload does not work any longer</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1924</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1924</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Hi, Actual behaviour Since I have updated my S7 Edge to Nougat 7.0, the auto-instant upload does not work any longer. I mean nothing happens not even the cloud icon appearing and throwing an error, nothing. I have tried reinstalling the app, restoring the phone to factory settings, try to check on wifi only or no, nothing is working. That's a shame considering the role of a cloud application. But it works well on my other phone a Huawei P9 Lite running Android 6.0.1. Steps to reproduce Setup the app to autoupload photos and videos take a photo check that nothing is happening Can this problem be reproduced with the official owncloud server? (url: https://demo.owncloud.org, user: test, password: test) yes Environment data Android version: 7 Device model: Samsung S7 EDGE Stock or customized system: STOCK ownCloud app version: 2.3.0 ownCloud server version: 8.2.10
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="268">
			<summary>Build error in Android Studio 2.3</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1925</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1925</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Hi, I tried to compile android app for the first time but get some errors instead of success ;) The appearing messages look like Error:(5, 21) No resource found that matches the given name: attr 'windowActionBar'. Error:(600) Error retrieving parent for item: No resource found that matches the given name 'Base.Widget.AppCompat.Button'. Error:(604) Error retrieving parent for item: No resource found that matches the given name 'Base.Widget.AppCompat.Button.Borderless'. Android Studio is version 2.3 I also installed SDK Platform 24 additional to version 25. 'compileSdkVersion 24' and 'buildToolsVersion &quot;24.0.2&quot;' are set in build.gradle. Any hint on how to resolve this? regards zeckrich
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="269">
			<summary>AuthenticatorActivity auto connect to server - question</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1932</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1932</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Hi, I am trying to hide editText for server URL I have tried to use setText() method on mHostUrlInput and set server address, so when user change focus to username it will automatically report connection established message. But unfortunately this is not working. Can you please help me to achieve this?
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="270">
			<summary>FileDisplayActivity title change - question</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1933</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1933</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Hello, I am trying to change title &quot;ownCloud&quot; in this activity, but with getSupportActionBar().setTitle(&quot;TEST!@#&quot;); I wasn't able to change it. Screenshot included. Can you please advice me on this.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="271">
			<summary>Add &quot;Go to Folder&quot; action on tapping a completed upload</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1942</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1942</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Actual behaviour Tapping on an upload notification does nothing Expected behaviour Tapping on an upload notification does something :) Steps to reproduce Tap on a completed upload notification in the notification tray, or open the Uploads activity in the Android client Owncloud Android app lists all uploads Tap a (completed) entry I hoped this would do something, like open the folder, as I'd like to: Rename the file Share the file Opening the file isn't necessarily useful by default as I likely already have the file locally, though maybe useful in a long-tail, but the default tap would definitely be if it from opening the target folder, hopefully even showing/selecting the new file. I've already navigated the tree once to upload the file, perhaps useful to not have to do that again to manipulate the uploaded file? Can this problem be reproduced with the official owncloud server? Probably (client issue) Environment data Android version: 7.1.1 Device model: Nexus 9, Nexus 7 Stock or customized system: Both ownCloud app version: Latest Play Store (2.3.0) ownCloud server version: 9.1 Logs Skipped...
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="272">
			<summary>Failure when cloning owncloud/android repository</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1943</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1943</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Actual behaviour &quot;fatal read error: Connection reset by peer&quot; occurs when cloning owncloud/android repository Expected behaviour successful cloning owncloud/android repository Steps to reproduce In a web browser, go to https://github.com/owncloud/android, and click the 'Fork' button near the top right corner Open a terminal and go on with the next steps in it Clone your forked repository: git clone --recursive https://github.com/YOURGITHUBNAME/android.git Git version/OS version: git version 2.7.4, ubuntu 16.04
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="273">
			<summary>Automatic upload?</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1960</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1960</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Hi all. I have just stumbled across this while looking for an alternative to Dropbox camera upload. I have an owncloud server set up and working on Ubuntu 16.04 and I can connect to it find, add, download, delete files etc no problem. I have tried using the &quot;instant upload&quot; option but I just can't seem to figure out how to get it to work. I set the path to my camera folder and take a photo and absolutely nothing happens in the app whatsoever. Nothing gets queued, nothing uploaded, no errors, nothing. Dropbox syncs the same photo fine. I am pulling my hair out trying to figure this out and I can't find anything in the manual while would help. I am using a Galaxy S7 and my camera is set to save to a 64GB microSD card. I tried changing back to phone storage and set that folder in the owncloud app but it makes no difference. PLEASE can someone help?
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="274">
			<summary>(Android 7, BQ Aquaris U Lite) Autoload of images does not start</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1974</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1974</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		My daughter own the phone at subject, with Android 7. I've the latest OwnClud official app, 2.3.0, with OC 9.1 (but it is not a OC trouble, there's not even the start of the upload, nor images in the upload queue). Using filemanager i've verified that images got in correct folder (/storage/emulated/0/DCIM/Camera) that are specified in the OwnClud app as camera folder. I've looked here, there's some bug opened similar to that, but all claimed to be fixed, or at least seems to me so. Sorry if not. Thanks.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="275">
			<summary>Unknown error occured on android app connexion</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/1982</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1982</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Actual behaviour Hi, I have freshly installed the owncloud application (ocloud for OwnCloud) from the PlayStore. But when I enter my URL in the connexion screen, the configuration test is printing &quot;Unknown error occured!&quot; under the URL. This is stranged because it works in the Web Browser. Here is the result of https://owncloud.paul-mesnilgrente.com/status.php : {&quot;installed&quot;:true,&quot;maintenance&quot;:false,&quot;version&quot;:&quot;9.1.6.2&quot;,&quot;versionstring&quot;:&quot;9.1.6&quot;,&quot;edition&quot;:&quot;&quot;} DavDroid synchronizes Contacts and Calendar well, and Thunderbird too. Expected behaviour The connection should work. Steps to reproduce Install the ocloud for OwnCloud app from the PlayStore Enter this URL : https://owncloud.paul-mesnilgrente.com Wait for the test result Normally, &quot;Unknown error occured&quot; is printed Can this problem be reproduced with the official owncloud server? No it works with https://demo.owncloud.org/ Environment data Android version: 7.1.2 LineageOS Condor Device model: Moto E Stock or customized system: Condor ? ownCloud app version: The most updated on the Play Store ownCloud server version: 9.1.6 Logs Web server error log I don't know why, but the logs are not written any more :/ Even when I am connecting with the web browser.
 ownCloud log (data/owncloud.log) I don't know why, but the logs are not written any more :/ Even when I am connecting with the web browser.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="276">
			<summary>[feature request] Implementation of client side certificates</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/2002</url>
			<bugID>Issue #2002</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Actual behaviour No Implementation of client side certificates. Server side certificates are working without an issue. Expected behaviour Implementation of client side certificates on core and android app so clients may be forced to log in with password and certificate. Implementation should allow to clients (or android app) to provide certificate for intermediate validation prior to login on owncloud. Steps to reproduce N/A Can this problem be reproduced with the official owncloud server? (url: https://demo.owncloud.org, user: test, password: test) N/A Environment data Android version: All Device model: All Stock or customized system: N/A ownCloud app version: 2.4.0 ownCloud server version: N/A Logs Web server error log Insert your webserver log here
 ownCloud log (data/owncloud.log) Insert your ownCloud log here
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="277">
			<summary>how to painless rename package from com.owncloud to org.freecloud</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/2012</url>
			<bugID>Issue #2012</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		I have the problem with renaming package. If I rename the package then I run into problem that I have bunch of classes that need to re-import in other classes. How can I easy achieve this? thanks
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="278">
			<summary>issue after refactoring package name - urgent</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/2014</url>
			<bugID>Issue #2014</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Hi I have refactored package of owncloud app. I have changed in manifest and folder names, but run into this problem: Error while executing: am start -n &quot;com.owncloud.android/rs.test.cloudbox.ui.activity.FileDisplayActivity&quot; -a android.intent.action.MAIN -c android.intent.category.LAUNCHER How can I solve this problem?
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="279">
			<summary>SSL initialization failed</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/2029</url>
			<bugID>Issue #2029</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Actual behaviour Working with the Owncloud app stops working suddenly, now I get the error &quot;SSL initialization failed&quot;. I tried to delete my account in the app, now I'm not able to reconnect to my ouwncloud server with the same error: &quot;SSL initialization failed&quot;. The problem came up after an update of the phone's OS (at least I think so). The device is a Blackberry Z10 which is able to run Android apps since there is an special Android layer within the OS called Android Player. Using the web interface of the owncloud server from within the browser on the phone works. I'm pretty sure the problem lies in the server's SSL configuration. But I'm not able to find the cause resp. to adjust the settings. And I haven't access to all config data since it is a shared server. Test on https://www.ssllabs.com/ssltest/ gives A+ Expected behaviour Of course I would like to connect to the server using the app. Steps to reproduce In the app try to add a new account Type in the server address: https://.... The connection will be tested and the tests ends with the mentioned error message Can this problem be reproduced with the official owncloud server? (url: https://demo.owncloud.org, user: test, password: test) No, I'm not able to reproduce the problem with demo.owncloud.org. It works fine. Environment data Android version: Blackberry OS 10.3.3.2163 Device model: Blackberry Z10 Stock or customized system: Stock system ownCloud app version: 2.4.0 ownCloud server version: ownCloud 9.0.10 (stable) Logs Web server error log (It's a snippet of Sep 04 because I've done on this day one connection test only) [Mon Sep 04 09:14:06.393452 2017] [core:info] [pid 2434:tid 139994651911936] [client 114.215.149.183:55807] AH00128: File does not exist: /usr/www/users/epperl/phpMyAdmin/scripts/setup.php
[Mon Sep 04 09:14:16.372147 2017] [core:info] [pid 23727:tid 139995031238400] [client 114.215.149.183:56378] AH00128: File does not exist: /usr/www/users/epperl/pma/scripts/setup.php
[Mon Sep 04 09:14:26.348904 2017] [core:info] [pid 23727:tid 139994685482752] [client 114.215.149.183:56984] AH00128: File does not exist: /usr/www/users/epperl/myadmin/scripts/setup.php
[Mon Sep 04 14:30:50.206051 2017] [cgid:error] [pid 5214:tid 140154913056512] [client 186.207.19.19:60643] AH01262: Options ExecCGI is off in this directory: /usr/www/users/epperl/hndUnblock.cgi
[Mon Sep 04 14:30:53.226046 2017] [cgid:error] [pid 17409:tid 140154723337984] [client 186.207.19.19:60657] AH01262: Options ExecCGI is off in this directory: /usr/www/users/epperl/tmUnblock.cgi
[Mon Sep 04 14:30:56.232938 2017] [core:info] [pid 17565:tid 140154748516096] [client 186.207.19.19:60674] AH00128: File does not exist: /usr/www/users/epperl/moo
[Mon Sep 04 19:11:56.425481 2017] [core:info] [pid 17409:tid 140154756908800] [client 122.154.239.109:55604] AH00128: File does not exist: /usr/www/users/epperl/phpMyAdmin/scripts/setup.php
[Mon Sep 04 19:13:14.624921 2017] [core:info] [pid 17565:tid 140154913056512] [client 122.154.239.109:60436] AH00128: File does not exist: /usr/www/users/epperl/pma/scripts/setup.php
[Mon Sep 04 19:14:32.891888 2017] [core:info] [pid 17565:tid 140154871092992] [client 122.154.239.109:49344] AH00128: File does not exist: /usr/www/users/epperl/myadmin/scripts/setup.php
[Mon Sep 04 20:51:31.187401 2017] [core:info] [pid 17442:tid 140154773694208] [client 163.172.64.133:55514] AH00128: File does not exist: /usr/www/users/epperl/a2billing/admin/Public/index.php
[Mon Sep 04 21:22:53.983987 2017] [core:info] [pid 17442:tid 140154740123392] [client 163.172.64.133:47040] AH00128: File does not exist: /usr/www/users/epperl/a2billing/admin/Public/index.php
[Mon Sep 04 23:50:25.646046 2017] [core:info] [pid 14247:tid 140154862700288] [client 93.65.210.204:33160] AH00128: File does not exist: /usr/www/users/epperl/phpMyAdmin/scripts/setup.php
[Mon Sep 04 23:50:30.732396 2017] [core:info] [pid 14247:tid 140155039278848] [client 93.65.210.204:34045] AH00128: File does not exist: /usr/www/users/epperl/pma/scripts/setup.php
[Mon Sep 04 23:50:35.815685 2017] [core:info] [pid 19423:tid 140154913056512] [client 93.65.210.204:34943] AH00128: File does not exist: /usr/www/users/epperl/myadmin/scripts/setup.php
 Insert your webserver log here You can find it here: https://epperleinberlin.name/owncloud/index.php/s/lEOBBa8bKCcccsN But there isn't any related content, I'm afraid. ownCloud log (data/owncloud.log) There aren't any entries for Sep 04 (see above). This here doesn't seem to be related: {&quot;reqId&quot;:&quot;GViceHXQA+JWwOswSf62&quot;,&quot;remoteAddr&quot;:&quot;87.164.xx.xx&quot;,&quot;app&quot;:&quot;files_versions&quot;,&quot;message&quot;:&quot;Mark to expire \/documents\/Heike\/xxxxxxxxxxxxxxx.odt next version should be 1503083250 or smaller. (prevTimestamp: 1503169650; step: 86400&quot;,&quot;level&quot;:1,&quot;time&quot;:&quot;2017-09-05T18:30:59+00:00&quot;,&quot;method&quot;:&quot;GET&quot;,&quot;url&quot;:&quot;\/owncloud\/cron.php&quot;,&quot;user&quot;:&quot;--&quot;}
{&quot;reqId&quot;:&quot;GViceHXQA+JWwOswSf62&quot;,&quot;remoteAddr&quot;:&quot;87.164.xx.xx&quot;,&quot;app&quot;:&quot;files_versions&quot;,&quot;message&quot;:&quot;Expire: \/documents\/Heike\/xxxxxxxxxxx.odt.v1503169495&quot;,&quot;level&quot;:1,&quot;time&quot;:&quot;2017-09-05T18:30:59+00:00&quot;,&quot;method&quot;:&quot;GET&quot;,&quot;url&quot;:&quot;\/owncloud\/cron.php&quot;,&quot;user&quot;:&quot;--&quot;}
{&quot;reqId&quot;:&quot;Q3MGKJVQALfyM4QRy\/bz&quot;,&quot;remoteAddr&quot;:&quot;87.164.xx.xx&quot;,&quot;app&quot;:&quot;PHP&quot;,&quot;message&quot;:&quot;Automatically populating $HTTP_RAW_POST_DATA is deprecated and will be removed in a future version. To avoid this warning set 'always_populate_raw_post_data' to '-1' in php.ini and use the php:\/\/input stream instead. at Unknown#0&quot;,&quot;level&quot;:3,&quot;time&quot;:&quot;2017-09-05T18:43:12+00:00&quot;,&quot;method&quot;:&quot;POST&quot;,&quot;url&quot;:&quot;\/owncloud\/index.php\/heartbeat&quot;,&quot;user&quot;:&quot;xxxx&quot;}
{&quot;reqId&quot;:&quot;Uh\/rOHJv5T7MPrOvQBGV&quot;,&quot;remoteAddr&quot;:&quot;87.164.xx.xx&quot;,&quot;app&quot;:&quot;PHP&quot;,&quot;message&quot;:&quot;Automatically populating $HTTP_RAW_POST_DATA is deprecated and will be removed in a future version. To avoid this warning set 'always_populate_raw_post_data' to '-1' in php.ini and use the php:\/\/input stream instead. at Unknown#0&quot;,&quot;level&quot;:3,&quot;time&quot;:&quot;2017-09-05T19:02:56+00:00&quot;,&quot;method&quot;:&quot;POST&quot;,&quot;url&quot;:&quot;\/owncloud\/index.php\/heartbeat&quot;,&quot;user&quot;:&quot;xxxx&quot;}
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="280">
			<summary>custom Two provider app can not login from android application</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/2039</url>
			<bugID>Issue #2039</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Actual behaviour i have created two factor app , from this document : https://doc.owncloud.org/server/10.0/developer_manual/app/two-factor-provider.html on web browser , everything is ok , provider works like a charm , but on Android application , it says &quot; wrong username or password &quot; . i read about adding App password , but nothing change , maybe i do wrong , don't know , Expected behaviour i want to show my provider on android application too . user is coming to login , after checking username and password , it shows an extra page , to verify authentication . Environment data Android version: 2.4.0 Logs ownCloud log (data/owncloud.log) HTTP\\\/1.1 401 No 'Authorization: Basic' header found. Either the client didn't send one, or the server is misconfigured, No 'Authorization: Basic' header found. Either the client didn't send one, or the server is misconfigured
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="281">
			<summary>General project structure</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/2044</url>
			<bugID>Issue #2044</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		I see this in build.gradle This project was started in Eclipse and later moved to Android Studio. In the transition, both IDEs were supported. Due to this, the files layout is not the usual in new projects created with Android Studio / gradle. This file merges declarations usually split in two separates build.gradle file, one for global settings of the project in its root folder, another one for the app module in subfolder of root. Guys, Eclipse and Android are no team any more, and this makes no sense since 2015 ! I would like to make an PR to change project structure with an app directory, like most Android apps are, but when I see how much open PR's are there I see no chance doing this. Am I right ?
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="282">
			<summary>Researching Build Breakage</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/2051</url>
			<bugID>Issue #2051</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Dear developers of the owncloud/android project, We are MSc students from the Delft University of Technology doing research on why builds break in open source projects. To do this, we are analyzing Travis build statistics and build history of owncloud/android. By analyzing the build history of owncloud/android, we found the following: The project has 16.1% failing builds in the history The project has a average amount of build failures compared to other similar projects When looking at owncloud/android’s build metrics, we could not find clear factors that are highly correlated with this result. To identify the reasons behind build breakage, we would like to collect developer insights into the reasons why build breakage occurs. If you have five minutes, please answer the survey we have created. Your response will be very useful in our study. Thank you.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="283">
			<summary>CookieSyncManager not needed from 21</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/2052</url>
			<bugID>Issue #2052</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Hi, I found CookieSyncManager is instantiated in WebviewDialog. I understand it was instantiated to avoid crashes when instantiating CookieManager. But from API 21, it is no longer needed and deprecated. CookieManager can work well by itself. (According to the doc)
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="284">
			<summary>Unable to build app on android studio</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/2057</url>
			<bugID>Issue #2057</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Actual behaviour Unable to build the app on Android Studio Expected behaviour There should be no error while building the app Steps to reproduce Import the project in android studio Screenshot of the issue
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="285">
			<summary>Replace hardcoded strings with string resource in the project</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/2058</url>
			<bugID>Issue #2058</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Actual behaviour Hardcore strings are used at some places in the project. It would be great if we replace the strings with string resource. Expected behaviour The strings should be declared in the strings resource
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="286">
			<summary>Error while trying to run the app on my device using android studio</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/2060</url>
			<bugID>Issue #2060</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Actual behaviour Unable to run the app on my device using android studio. Expected behaviour The app should run on my device Steps to reproduce Open Android Studio Click the run button Select their device from the list of available devices Environment data Android version: 7.1.1 Device model: OnePlus 3T
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="287">
			<summary>Activity screen: same info displayed twice</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/2072</url>
			<bugID>Issue #2072</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Hi, See screen shot =&gt; the layout can be optimized without repeating twice the timestamp ...
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="288">
			<summary>Confusing download buttons when mixed</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/2081</url>
			<bugID>Issue #2081</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Steps Enter folder with multiple files where none of the files were ever synced Touch and hold on each file to select them Find the option for &quot;available offline&quot; in the top bar Expected result Easy to distinguish icons with no ambiguity Actual result There are two icons there: an arrow down and another arrow down with an underline. I suspect that many people would not know which one to pick. Maybe find a better icon for available offline. Version 2.5.0
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="289">
			<summary>AS 3.0 with Gradle dependency file</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/2096</url>
			<bugID>Issue #2096</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Actual behaviour -Setting up project for the first time, apologise if this is a &quot;newbie&quot; error and I have not done something I should have. I have followed the setup documentation twice. done a clean and a rebuild of the project. Looked at the gradle dependencies. org.gradle.api.ProjectConfigurationException: A problem occurred configuring root project org.gradle.api.ProjectConfigurationException: A problem occurred configuring root project 'android-master'. at org.gradle.configuration.project.LifecycleProjectEvaluator.addConfigurationFailure(LifecycleProjectEvaluator.java:94) at org.gradle.configuration.project.LifecycleProjectEvaluator.notifyAfterEvaluate(LifecycleProjectEvaluator.java:89) at org.gradle.configuration.project.LifecycleProjectEvaluator.doConfigure(LifecycleProjectEvaluator.java:76) at org.gradle.configuration.project.LifecycleProjectEvaluator.access$000(LifecycleProjectEvaluator.java:33) at org.gradle.configuration.project.LifecycleProjectEvaluator$1.execute(LifecycleProjectEvaluator.java:53) at org.gradle.configuration.project.LifecycleProjectEvaluator$1.execute(LifecycleProjectEvaluator.java:50) at org.gradle.internal.Transformers$4.transform(Transformers.java:169) at org.gradle.internal.progress.DefaultBuildOperationExecutor.run(DefaultBuildOperationExecutor.java:106) at org.gradle.internal.progress.DefaultBuildOperationExecutor.run(DefaultBuildOperationExecutor.java:61) at org.gradle.configuration.project.LifecycleProjectEvaluator.evaluate(LifecycleProjectEvaluator.java:50) at org.gradle.api.internal.project.DefaultProject.evaluate(DefaultProject.java:628) at org.gradle.api.internal.project.DefaultProject.evaluate(DefaultProject.java:129) at org.gradle.execution.TaskPathProjectEvaluator.configure(TaskPathProjectEvaluator.java:35) at org.gradle.configuration.DefaultBuildConfigurer.configure(DefaultBuildConfigurer.java:36) at org.gradle.initialization.DefaultGradleLauncher$1.execute(DefaultGradleLauncher.java:161) at org.gradle.initialization.DefaultGradleLauncher$1.execute(DefaultGradleLauncher.java:158) at org.gradle.internal.Transformers$4.transform(Transformers.java:169) at org.gradle.internal.progress.DefaultBuildOperationExecutor.run(DefaultBuildOperationExecutor.java:106) at org.gradle.internal.progress.DefaultBuildOperationExecutor.run(DefaultBuildOperationExecutor.java:56) at org.gradle.initialization.DefaultGradleLauncher.doBuildStages(DefaultGradleLauncher.java:158) Expected behaviour -with all the dependencies, I'm expecting the external files that the app would be looking for to be in the gradle file Steps to reproduce setup project in AS 2.done a build of the project Can this problem be reproduced with the official owncloud server? (url: https://demo.owncloud.org, user: test, password: test) Environment data Android version: Device model: Stock or customized system: ownCloud app version: ownCloud server version: Logs Web server error log Insert your webserver log here
 ownCloud log (data/owncloud.log) Insert your ownCloud log here
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="290">
			<summary>Feature-Request - &quot;Select All&quot; button in launcher activity.</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/2106</url>
			<bugID>Issue #2106</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Actual behaviour There is no Select All feature in the main activity. Expected behaviour There should be a such option to select all items in one go. It can be done by adding a Select All button in menu of File Display Activity.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="291">
			<summary>The source can't complied successfully.</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/2107</url>
			<bugID>Issue #2107</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Actual behaviour -Tell us what happens I execute the command in terminal &quot; ./gradlew clean build&quot; in the source root path. The error occur! See the below log tiger@:android-1$ ./gradlew clean build File /home/tiger/.android/repositories.cfg could not be loaded. FAILURE: Build failed with an exception. What went wrong: A problem occurred configuring root project 'android-1'. Could not resolve all dependencies for configuration ':_debugApk'. A problem occurred configuring project ':touchImageView'. &gt; Could not resolve all dependencies for configuration ':touchImageView:_debugPublishCopy'. &gt; Could not resolve com.android.support:support-v4:26.1.0. Required by: project :touchImageView &gt; Could not resolve com.android.support:support-v4:26.1.0. &gt; Could not get resource 'https://maven.google.com/com/android/support/support-v4/26.1.0/support-v4-26.1.0.pom'. &gt; Could not GET 'https://maven.google.com/com/android/support/support-v4/26.1.0/support-v4-26.1.0.pom'. &gt; Remote host closed connection during handshake Try: Run with --stacktrace option to get the stack trace. Run with --info or --debug option to get more log output.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="292">
			<summary>Migrate to Gradle 3.1.2 and add Java 8 support</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/2109</url>
			<bugID>Issue #2109</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		We are currently using Android plugin for Gradle 2.3.3, but there is a newer Android plugin for Gradle with version 3.1.2 that could be used along with 4.4 gradle distribution. Following Migrate to Android Plugin for Gradle 3.0.0 and Use Java 8 Language Features Some errors: Cannot set the value of read-only property 'outputFile' -&gt; Use outputFileName InstrumentTest deprecated -&gt; Use androidTest Error:(161, 5) error: invalid parent reference 'style/Widget.AppCompat.ButtonBar.AlertDialog'. -&gt; Use @style instead of style Could not find com.android.tools.lint:lint-gradle Android Studio 3-&gt; Include google() repository Some styles not found -&gt; remove @ before android app_name / other setup.xml variable is not translated -&gt; disable 'MissingTranslation' Some warnings: Warning:Configuration 'compile' is obsolete and has been replaced with 'implementation' and 'api'. Warning:Configuration 'testCompile' is obsolete and has been replaced with 'testImplementation' and 'testApi'. Warning:The specified Android SDK Build Tools version (26.0.2) is ignored, as it is below the minimum supported version (27.0.3) for Android Gradle Plugin 3.1.2. -&gt; remove &quot;buildToolsVersion '26.0.0'&quot; from your build.gradle file, as each version of the Android Gradle Plugin now has a default version of the build tools.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="293">
			<summary>Still no support to save file in SD card -- Bye bye</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/2114</url>
			<bugID>Issue #2114</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Actual behaviour NOTHING happens in more than four years Expected behaviour -Expected feature to be implemented ages ago Steps to reproduce Ask once Ask twice Ask and ask Can this problem be reproduced with the official owncloud server? (url: https://demo.owncloud.org, user: test, password: test) Yes, anywhere, everywhere I'm leaving ownCloud: this forum, the newsletters. It's been many years and this is never done. Better use my time to look for alternative. Maybe when they see that their user base is in the decline that they would wake up to see what is more important for users. BYE BYE
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="294">
			<summary>FR: Adaptive icon</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/2121</url>
			<bugID>Issue #2121</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Api 26 introduced adaptive icons where background and foreground are two different images. https://developer.android.com/guide/practices/ui_guidelines/icon_design_adaptive.html 👍 2
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="295">
			<summary>automatic camera upload fails</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/2122</url>
			<bugID>Issue #2122</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Actual behaviour The new camera upload feature doesn't work. Files are synced properly. Photos can only be uploaded manually. When selecting the default photo folder (/storage/emulated/0/DCIM) it appears empty in the owncloud app but I can see the files when opening with an explorer. Uploads appeared to be starting but failed (Upload failed - device not connected to a network). Expected behaviour automatic camera uploads work like the instant uploads before! :) Environment data Android version: 8.0.0 Device model: OnePlus5 ownCloud app version: 2.6.0 ownCloud server version: 10.0.6
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="296">
			<summary>[2.6.0] Automatically uploads settings are removed after the upgrade.</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/2130</url>
			<bugID>Issue #2130</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		I upgraded from 2.5.0 to 2.6.0 and I had activated automatically upload pictures and video. after the upgrade (over Playstore) the settings are removed and I have to add it manually again. Tested with branded app (damken-cloud) @michaelstingl @davigonz
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="297">
			<summary>[2.7.0] Wizard, include coming features</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/2136</url>
			<bugID>Issue #2136</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Since we are going to include several important features in the coming release, we could include them in our new wizard, but just for the users that update the app from old versions to 2.7.0. Features to include: Pattern lock. Fingerprint lock. Gif support. Upload pictures directly from the camera. CC / @jesmrec TASKS [GIT] Create whatsNew_2.7.0 branch from whatsNew. Create new resources for the different steps to include. [GIT] Merge branch whatsNew_2.7.0 into master.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="298">
			<summary>Upload pictures directly from devices camera, uploads the thumbnail of the image.</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/2141</url>
			<bugID>Issue #2141</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Actual behaviour When using the upload from camera feature the thumbnail of the picture is being uploaded. Expected behaviour The actual picture file should be uploaded instead of the thumbnail. Steps to reproduce Open the main FAB. Select Upload FAB Select &quot;Picture from camera&quot; option in the Bottom Sheet Can this problem be reproduced with the official owncloud server? (url: https://demo.owncloud.org, user: test, password: test) Yes Environment data Android version: 8.0.0 Device model: Oneplus 3T Stock or customized system: ownCloud app version: 2.6.0
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="299">
			<summary>App crashes when trying to access settings</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/2159</url>
			<bugID>Issue #2159</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Actual behaviour After the update to 2.7.0-beta.1 the App crashes when trying to access settings. The App closes and a popup window appears stating &quot;Owncloud stopped&quot; Expected behaviour Settings should be accessible. Steps to reproduce Open the app Go to settings App stops Can this problem be reproduced with the official owncloud server? (url: https://demo.owncloud.org, user: test, password: test) N/A Environment data Android version: 6.0.1 Device model: Samsung Galaxy S5 mini ownCloud app version: 2.7.0-beta.1
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="300">
			<summary>none</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/2193</url>
			<bugID>Issue #2193</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		false
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="301">
			<summary>Option not insta upload on mobile data</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/2201</url>
			<bugID>Issue #2201</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		It's not really a problem, but I find it really annoying having to manually upload my photos because instant upload dosent have the feature to not upload when using mobile data, I still want to have access to my files when on mobile data, so no the fix is not going to options a disabling it.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="302">
			<summary>Android App successfully tests SSL connection but fails to log in 'Unknown error'</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/owncloud/android/issues/2206</url>
			<bugID>Issue #2206</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Actual behaviour When trying to log in using the android application (version 2.7.0) entering https://cloud.chillstice.com yields the message: Secure connection established; however, when logging in with the correct credentials it tries to log in for 3 seconds and fails with the message: Unknown error. The desktop client works fine and the ownCloud panel accessible at cloud.chillstice.com works properly. Expected behaviour The application should log in like I was able to do many times before moving to a subdomain. Steps to reproduce Create a subdomain redirect to the directory ownCloud is installed in. Try to connect using the new address with the android application. Can this problem be reproduced with the official owncloud server? (url: https://demo.owncloud.org, user: test, password: test) NO :C Environment data Android version: 7.0 Device model: Samsung Galaxy S7 Verizon (SM-G930V) Stock or customized system: Stock ownCloud app version: 2.7.0 ownCloud server version: 10.0.7.2 Logs Web server error log No relevant errors ownCloud log (data/owncloud.log) No relevant errors More Info Today I finally figured out how to properly create subdomains and how to set ownCloud to be accessible under the 'cloud' subdomain. I changed the config.php to include the following:   'trusted_domains' =&gt; 
  array (
    0 =&gt; 'chillstice.com',
    1 =&gt; 'cloud.chillstice.com',
  ),
'overwrite.cli.url' =&gt; 'https://cloud.chillstice.com/',
'htaccess.RewriteBase' =&gt; '/',

 Then I ran 'occ maintenance:update:htaccess' The SSL certificates for the subdomain have also successfully been updated and are live. I only started having this problem after setting up the subdomain.
	</description>
		</report>
	</reports>
