<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
	<reports>
		<report Number="0">
			<summary>Rename Application</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/AnimeNeko/Atarashii/issues/4</url>
			<bugID>Issue #4</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		I highly suggest renaming the application, at least externally. &quot;Dreadful&quot; isn't exactly a positive word in English, and &quot;DreadfulMAL&quot; seems, to me at least, to sound more like a really bad application for MAL than something that's actually pretty awesome. Maybe it could be shortened to &quot;DMAL.&quot;
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="1">
			<summary>Make List Selection Items use Radio Buttons instead of Checkboxes</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/AnimeNeko/Atarashii/issues/11</url>
			<bugID>Issue #11</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		As mentioned at this comment, the list switch options should probably be radio buttons rather than checkboxes. Radio buttons clearly indicate a single selection possibility while checkboxes are common for multiple selections. Personally, I think this might be a good use for scrollable tabs as described here.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="2">
			<summary>Software License</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/AnimeNeko/Atarashii/issues/16</url>
			<bugID>Issue #16</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		With more people wanting to contribute, it is important to pick a license for the software. I'm fine with nearly anything, the key is how much control is desired over the code. The field is wide open from the &quot;must keep the source open&quot; of the GPL to the much more loose BSD and Apache licenses. Keep in mind that choosing a license also affects what third-party components can be used within the source as some licenses can conflict. I don't expect a lot of problems, but it is something to consider. Also keep in mind that without copyright assignment, changing the license to the software gets more difficult as the number of contributors climb as every contributor must agree to the change or you'll need to strip out their contributions to make the change. This issue is to discuss licensing and hopefully reach a conclusion on the best license for the project to use.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="3">
			<summary>Write a summary for yourself</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/AnimeNeko/Atarashii/issues/17</url>
			<bugID>Issue #17</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		As of 2089e25 there is now a more detailed contributor screen. Sure it's a stopgap for now, but we can reuse the summary blurb in a less temporary screen later. So: I tentatively filled in the contributor_name_Motokochan and contributor_summary_Motokochan strings for you, but feel free to change them to whatever you'd like, as I would like you to be credited in the app as you would like to be. Also the new setup of name/summary for each contributor means if more people contribute in the future (like the person that is working on search) it's easy to just add a new credit for them.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="4">
			<summary>Deleting entry on MAL does not reflect within the app</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/AnimeNeko/Atarashii/issues/19</url>
			<bugID>Issue #19</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		According to a review that was left, deleting an entry on the MAL site will not reflect within the app, even after a sync. This behaviour does in fact make sense, as we don't currently check against the database to see if anything is missing, only if the entries don't exist or have been updated. Going to fix this for 1.2. Maybe I'll even push a hotfix for 1.1 with this fix.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="5">
			<summary>Details Card Layout</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/AnimeNeko/Atarashii/issues/25</url>
			<bugID>Issue #25</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Though it's nearly done, dropping it here as a reminder to myself. Left to do as of opening: -Better layout for &quot;Progress&quot; -Rating bar for score, possibly as part of &quot;MAL Stats&quot; -Stylize the dialogs to look like the cards
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="6">
			<summary>Save Item Rating</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/AnimeNeko/Atarashii/issues/33</url>
			<bugID>Issue #33</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Adjusting the rating for the anime/manga item should trigger a save action. Consider making the rating adjustment a dialog, as it's way too easy to inadvertently change the rating when scrolling the details. (Implement as radio buttons or dropdown with descriptive text?)
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="7">
			<summary>Activities Not Setting as Root</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/AnimeNeko/Atarashii/issues/42</url>
			<bugID>Issue #42</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Some activities, when called, such as the &quot;first time init&quot; are not being set as the root activity, even when called with flags that should allow this. Because of this situation, you can use the back action to return to the calling activity, which creates a NPE. This needs to be investigated, as there are some NPEs being reported that seem to be from users doing this exact thing. With the new logout feature, this could get to be more of an issue.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="8">
			<summary>Wrong list names</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/AnimeNeko/Atarashii/issues/47</url>
			<bugID>Issue #47</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		In the app there are different names for the same list. These lists are affected: Watching (sometimes called In Progress) Plan To Watch (mostly called Planned) On Hold (sometimes called On-Hold) I suggest you use the same names as on MyAnimelist (the ones I mentioned first), but do what you want :D At least use the same name everywhere.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="9">
			<summary>Being an app for 4.0+ drop usage of ActionBarSherlock</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/AnimeNeko/Atarashii/issues/49</url>
			<bugID>Issue #49</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Jake Wharton him self said that the Library is only for supporting older devices as this app outside of it's target zone anyway why keep it?
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="10">
			<summary>Update ActionBarSherlock and android-numberpicker</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/AnimeNeko/Atarashii/issues/52</url>
			<bugID>Issue #52</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		There have been several updates to our third-party libraries since they were added into the project. Our software should be updated to use the newer versions and the submodules will need to be updated to import the newer code for the build.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="11">
			<summary>Upload Project to Google Code</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/AnimeNeko/Atarashii/issues/64</url>
			<bugID>Issue #64</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		I found this project kind of accidentally while looking for something anime/android related, but it would be a lot easier for people to know about this project and join it if we put it up on Google Code/other open source hosting pages. What do you guys think?
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="12">
			<summary>Need a way to open the item page on MAL from DetailView</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/AnimeNeko/Atarashii/issues/68</url>
			<bugID>Issue #68</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		The DetailView is woefully sparse in 1.3 (and has been since versions immemorial). It's probably a long shot to include more info like reviews, rating stats, OP/ED lists and such in the app (but great if that's possible via API). But it would be very welcome if the action bar gained a button to open the MAL page using the browser.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="13">
			<summary>App theming</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/AnimeNeko/Atarashii/issues/128</url>
			<bugID>Issue #128</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		I'm working on letting users select the app theme. I've got the idea shaped up in my head but it looks like I'll have some questions and things to talk out. First off, would it be planned to have more than just two themes? (dark and light)
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="14">
			<summary>No Up button in settings</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/AnimeNeko/Atarashii/issues/134</url>
			<bugID>Issue #134</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		The second level settings screens don't have an Up button in the Action Bar. Compare the images:
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="15">
			<summary>Notification on sync?</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/AnimeNeko/Atarashii/issues/147</url>
			<bugID>Issue #147</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Is there a reason why we are using a crouton message and the notification message? I don't see a point in it... If the sync starts/completed we are showing the users a crouton message. So what's the point of using the notification in the statusbar?
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="16">
			<summary>Orientation change issues</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/AnimeNeko/Atarashii/issues/153</url>
			<bugID>Issue #153</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Orientation change resets scroll while browsing animelist and breaks top/popular/upcoming/just added lists. It happens on stable and beta versions from google play. Video: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LCPtDS3Qjkk Device: Nexus 7(2012). Selected runtime is Dalvik. btw, I didn't notice any problems with orientation change in &quot;My Profile&quot; and &quot;My Friends&quot; functions.(beta from google play)
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="17">
			<summary>Friendlist username overlaps time when the textsize is on extra large.</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/AnimeNeko/Atarashii/issues/160</url>
			<bugID>Issue #160</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		The username in the friendlist overlaps the other details when the text size is set on extra large. This is probably because the textviews are based on the parent and not the other textviews. Note: bug only applies on the friendlist.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="18">
			<summary>Unknown anime added in all lists</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/AnimeNeko/Atarashii/issues/161</url>
			<bugID>Issue #161</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		I don't really know how it appends, but I just see an anime, and it adds it on my list as nothing. Here a screenshot : https://i.imgur.com/e7eS67n.jpg, the anime Saint Seya is in my list, but has no status, and I don't add it. It seems that @ratan12 has the same bug. A log out/log in correct it.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="19">
			<summary>Overflow when the website is too long (Profile)</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/AnimeNeko/Atarashii/issues/171</url>
			<bugID>Issue #171</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		In some cases when the website url is too long the url will be written over the website text. (messing up the UI.) I tried to fix (by using a scrolling method but It didn't worked great) but it was a dirty fix that worked only one some devices.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="20">
			<summary>Icon redesign</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/AnimeNeko/Atarashii/issues/179</url>
			<bugID>Issue #179</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Since we will do many UI changes the next version I thought: why not redesign the app icon. I know someone who would love to do this. What do you guys think?
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="21">
			<summary>Bug error messages</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/AnimeNeko/Atarashii/issues/195</url>
			<bugID>Issue #195</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		I am quite annoyed by the error messages I get. http://api.atarashiiapp.com/1/mangalist/ratan12 I don't read manga so my list is always empty, due the recent changes I get every time &quot;error could not download Mangalist&quot; when I start the app or when I sync.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="22">
			<summary>Crash on startup (no network connection)</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/AnimeNeko/Atarashii/issues/202</url>
			<bugID>Issue #202</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		The app is crashing when you open it without network connection. It is caused by &quot;list&quot; that still null is. 07-31 00:48:27.215 E/AndroidRuntime(10502): FATAL EXCEPTION: main
07-31 00:48:27.215 E/AndroidRuntime(10502): Process: net.somethingdreadful.MAL, PID: 10502
07-31 00:48:27.215 E/AndroidRuntime(10502): java.lang.RuntimeException: Unable to resume activity {net.somethingdreadful.MAL/net.somethingdreadful.MAL.Home}: java.lang.NullPointerException: Attempt to read from field 'int net.somethingdreadful.MAL.IGF.list' on a null object reference
07-31 00:48:27.215 E/AndroidRuntime(10502):     at android.app.ActivityThread.performResumeActivity(ActivityThread.java:2777)
07-31 00:48:27.215 E/AndroidRuntime(10502):     at android.app.ActivityThread.handleResumeActivity(ActivityThread.java:2806)
07-31 00:48:27.215 E/AndroidRuntime(10502):     at android.app.ActivityThread.handleLaunchActivity(ActivityThread.java:2241)
07-31 00:48:27.215 E/AndroidRuntime(10502):     at android.app.ActivityThread.access$800(ActivityThread.java:138)
07-31 00:48:27.215 E/AndroidRuntime(10502):     at android.app.ActivityThread$H.handleMessage(ActivityThread.java:1199)
07-31 00:48:27.215 E/AndroidRuntime(10502):     at android.os.Handler.dispatchMessage(Handler.java:102)
07-31 00:48:27.215 E/AndroidRuntime(10502):     at android.os.Looper.loop(Looper.java:136)
07-31 00:48:27.215 E/AndroidRuntime(10502):     at android.app.ActivityThread.main(ActivityThread.java:5034)
07-31 00:48:27.215 E/AndroidRuntime(10502):     at java.lang.reflect.Method.invoke(Native Method)
07-31 00:48:27.215 E/AndroidRuntime(10502):     at com.android.internal.os.ZygoteInit$MethodAndArgsCaller.run(ZygoteInit.java:795)
07-31 00:48:27.215 E/AndroidRuntime(10502):     at com.android.internal.os.ZygoteInit.main(ZygoteInit.java:611)
07-31 00:48:27.215 E/AndroidRuntime(10502): Caused by: java.lang.NullPointerException: Attempt to read from field 'int net.somethingdreadful.MAL.IGF.list' on a null object reference
07-31 00:48:27.215 E/AndroidRuntime(10502):     at net.somethingdreadful.MAL.Home.checkNetworkAndDisplayCrouton(Home.java:384)
07-31 00:48:27.215 E/AndroidRuntime(10502):     at net.somethingdreadful.MAL.Home.onResume(Home.java:256)
07-31 00:48:27.215 E/AndroidRuntime(10502):     at android.app.Instrumentation.callActivityOnResume(Instrumentation.java:1192)
07-31 00:48:27.215 E/AndroidRuntime(10502):     at android.app.Activity.performResume(Activity.java:5320)
07-31 00:48:27.215 E/AndroidRuntime(10502):     at android.app.ActivityThread.performResumeActivity(ActivityThread.java:2767)
07-31 00:48:27.215 E/AndroidRuntime(10502):     ... 10 more
07-31 00:48:28.696 I/Process (10502): Sending signal. PID: 10502 SIG: 9
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="23">
			<summary>Horizontalscrollview on layouts?</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/AnimeNeko/Atarashii/issues/209</url>
			<bugID>Issue #209</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		I am kinda thinking why we actually use horizontalscrollviews in landshape. It isn't android behavior, I actually never saw an app using this way of displaying info in landscape. Why don't we use a gridview like the Google + app? That would've make a bit more sense.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="24">
			<summary>Remove credentials in prefManager before 1.5 Beta</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/AnimeNeko/Atarashii/issues/242</url>
			<bugID>Issue #242</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		In the current code we are using account manager which is fine. The only thing that we should do in my opinion is removing the credentials in perfManager. I don't like the feeling that my password is floating in the preference manager for no reason. The best solution would be getting the password and username and create an account in the account manager, after this we should remove it from the preference manager.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="25">
			<summary>Crashlytics policy document</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/AnimeNeko/Atarashii/issues/253</url>
			<bugID>Issue #253</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		In PR #252 we will send some user information to Crashlytics like usernames. We should create a policy document because of that and link it from inside the application about page once it's ready.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="26">
			<summary>Database bugs</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/AnimeNeko/Atarashii/issues/303</url>
			<bugID>Issue #303</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Available in atarashi 2.0 beta 1 What it does : When we see a planned anime description, the anime will change into the status &quot;watching&quot; What it must do : nothing Way to test this bug : 1. Open the detail of a planned anime (and wait the loading) 2. Sync from atarashii 3. See your anime list on MAL ; your anime you have seen is now on watching This bug always occur when I do that.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="27">
			<summary>Menu sometimes not working</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/AnimeNeko/Atarashii/issues/390</url>
			<bugID>Issue #390</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		The menu picker in Home is sometimes not working. It is probably because IGF is sometimes null which the menu than ignores.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="28">
			<summary>manga list not sorting</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/AnimeNeko/Atarashii/issues/475</url>
			<bugID>Issue #475</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		the mangalist is not sorting in the databasemanager
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="29">
			<summary>Cover image don't load when large version isn't available</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/AnimeNeko/Atarashii/issues/486</url>
			<bugID>Issue #486</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		GenericRecord.java always rewrites cover image URL to user large versions. Sometimes (≈ 2% of my list) a large version isn't available, like with Azumanga Daioh, Bokurano, Hidamari Sketch and Sailor Moon. When it happens cover_error.png is shown, instead of fallbacking to the normal, non-large, version.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="30">
			<summary>Settings: Auto-synchronisation misunderstanding</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/AnimeNeko/Atarashii/issues/487</url>
			<bugID>Issue #487</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		BRIEF: There are two &quot;Auto-synchronisation&quot; options in Settings. The difference between them is unclear(I guess the second option means something like &quot;Sync before backup&quot;, but I'm not sure). STEPS_TO_REPRODUCE: Open app. Login (MAL). Open settings. Look at &quot;Sync&quot; and &quot;Backup&quot; sections.
	</description>
		</report>
	</reports>
