<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
	<reports>
		<report Number="0">
			<summary>Test issue</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/1</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		No description provided.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="1">
			<summary>Slack integration test</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/2</url>
			<bugID>Issue #2</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		No description provided.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="2">
			<summary>Notifications automatically dissapear</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/3</url>
			<bugID>Issue #3</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Repro steps Open QKSMS to a specific conversation Leave app, but let it stay open in the background. Locking your phone will work too Receive a message from that conversation Notification will show for a split second and then dissapear
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="3">
			<summary>Testing tracker</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/4</url>
			<bugID>Issue #4</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		No description provided.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="4">
			<summary>Photos taken in Portrait mode are flipped sideways when sending as MMS</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/5</url>
			<bugID>Issue #5</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Repro steps Take picture in portrait mode Share picture with QKSMS (Share Picker) Photo gets inserted sideways in QKSMS
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="5">
			<summary>MMS from gallery to favorite contact with multiple numbers</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/6</url>
			<bugID>Issue #6</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Steps: 1. Browse a gallery app and select a picture to share. 2. Select QKSMS under the share menu 3. QKSMS compose window appears. Select a contact from the &quot;Favorite Contatcs&quot; list. This contact has to have multiple phone numbers associated to the same contact. 4. Send the picture. Expected: QKSMS should ask me which phone number do I want to use to send and then just send the picture without a problem. Reality: QKSMS attempts to send the picture to all phone numbers under the same contact, which is not what I want to do. This doesn't happen if I just type the contact name instead of selecting from Favorites, because I can see the contacts phone number being used. A new conversation is created that has as members all the phone numbers from the same contact. I know that they are all the phone numbers of the same contact because this problem gets pushed to Yappy, and there I can see all the phone numbers under that conversation. The first time this new conversation is created it shows the wrong contact picture. It actually shows the picture of a different contact. I'm attaching a screenshots of the problem so it's easier to understand. The screenshot shows that the second conversation has Jennifer Thomas and somebody else (+1). The contact picture is not of Jennifer Thomas, and the &quot;+1&quot; is the same contact but a different phone number. After restarting QKSMS (removing it from memory) the picture gets updated and now there's no contact picture at all and just the number &quot;2&quot; is displayed. Meaning there's two contacts in that conversation. Another thing that can be see in the screenshot is that the first conversation reads that my message could not be sent, because one of Jennifer's numbers is a land line. One of the problems that arise when you send the MMS to all phone numbers under that contact.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="6">
			<summary>&quot;Null&quot; conversation after receiving an MMS</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/7</url>
			<bugID>Issue #7</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		The February 12 update introduce another bug on MMS. Every time I received a picture, a new Null conversation is created. Notifications are working great, but the subject bug is still present. Any text sent with a picture is repeated as the subject, which is annoying.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="7">
			<summary>MMS subject text shown</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/8</url>
			<bugID>Issue #8</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		When sending or receiving an MMS together with text, QKSMS shows the text as both the message and the subject. I'm attaching a picture that shows the problem with the text &quot;Test&quot; as both the body and Subject. Subject should always be hidden.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="8">
			<summary>Crashed attempting to delete the message during the setup wizard.</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/10</url>
			<bugID>Issue #10</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		During the &quot;Try It&quot; step of the setup wizard click on the elipses menu in the upper right corner of the message and choose &quot;Delete Message&quot;. Notice crash!
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="9">
			<summary>Many of the Settings text are cut off</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/11</url>
			<bugID>Issue #11</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		&quot;Hide sent message ava&quot;.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="10">
			<summary>Can select both the &quot;Split SMS&quot; and &quot;Send long as MMS&quot;.</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/12</url>
			<bugID>Issue #12</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		In General settings it allows me to choose both the &quot;Split SMS&quot; and &quot;Send long as MMS&quot;. These should probably be a radio button option
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="11">
			<summary>Crashed when scrolling through search results</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/13</url>
			<bugID>Issue #13</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Searched for the word &quot;test&quot; and it crashed when I scrolled to the bottom of the results. Approximately 12 conversations were returned.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="12">
			<summary>Contact is removed when adding an attachment</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/14</url>
			<bugID>Issue #14</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Selected a contact and after adding an attachment it changes the contact name to the phone number and when I attempt to send it I'm shown a message stating &quot;Select some contacts to send this message to!&quot;.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="13">
			<summary>Attempting to forward a long message crashes the app.</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/15</url>
			<bugID>Issue #15</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Created a ~600k message and attempted to sent it to myself. Attempted to forward that message and the app crashed.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="14">
			<summary>Sending a ~500k SMS doesn't display the text in the sent message - only displays the time.</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/16</url>
			<bugID>Issue #16</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Sending a ~500k SMS doesn't display the text in the sent message - only displays the time.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="15">
			<summary>Crash when adding another contact to a conversation</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/17</url>
			<bugID>Issue #17</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Responding to a popup message and attempting to add another contact to the conversation causes it to crash.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="16">
			<summary>&quot;This feature has not yet been implemented&quot; in &quot;Try it&quot; feature</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/18</url>
			<bugID>Issue #18</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		During the setup wizard, &quot;Try It&quot; feature, you receive a message stating &quot;This feature has not yet been implemented&quot; when attempting to forward the message.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="17">
			<summary>Enhancement request: More control over color options.</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/21</url>
			<bugID>Issue #21</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		I would like to be able to change the color of... • text for sent messages • text for received messages • contact name • received SMS background • Sent SMS background
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="18">
			<summary>Enhancement request: More control over the font size.</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/23</url>
			<bugID>Issue #23</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		This app would be difficult to read for anyone who wears reading glasses.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="19">
			<summary>Enhancement request: &quot;Awesome extra features&quot; isn't clearly defined.</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/24</url>
			<bugID>Issue #24</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		The QKSMS+ option in the menu displays the text &quot;Unlock some awesome extra features!&quot; but the only feature mentioned is &quot;Automatic night mode&quot;. One feature doesn't count as &quot;awesome extra features&quot;.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="20">
			<summary>Enhancement request: Option to search contacts</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/25</url>
			<bugID>Issue #25</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		There is no way to search the contact list. If I can't remember how I spelled someone's name or what nickname I put them under I'm not going to be able to find them.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="21">
			<summary>User in Play Store screenshots is simultaneously Moez and not Moez</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/27</url>
			<bugID>Issue #27</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		As seen below, either the user is Moez and somehow/for some reason has a SMS conversation with himself, or the user is falsely claiming to be Moez in the conversation with Shane, or Shane is claiming that he is Moez and the user is Shane. If the first possibility was the intent as a joke, then fine, but still.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="22">
			<summary>If the phone number has a internationnal prefix number (+33 or +41)</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/28</url>
			<bugID>Issue #28</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		The bug is if the phone number has a international prefix number (+33 or +41) the name and the picture doesn't appear the program say the number local. Exemple: +41 76 000 00 00 (number swiss) 076 000 00 00 ( local swiss number) same phone number but for the program it is two different number. Sorry for my English, i'm French
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="23">
			<summary>Outgoing group text is not received by recepients</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/29</url>
			<bugID>Issue #29</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		I sent a group text to 5 people, just plain text telling them about something. They reported receiving a blank image frame that they couldn't open and nothing else. I use a Nexus 5 on the Koodo network in Canada..
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="24">
			<summary>MMS image preview is same for all images</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/31</url>
			<bugID>Issue #31</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		The preview shown for all images is the preview of the most recently received image. Clicking on the preview shows the correct image
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="25">
			<summary>Notification Sound</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/34</url>
			<bugID>Issue #34</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Notification sounds seem to be hit or miss when receiving a new SMS. I am using the Nexus 6 Unlocked on Verizon Wireless. I use to not get sound notifications when receiving MMS now it seems to work and SMS seems to not get it all the time when a new message arrives.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="26">
			<summary>Read messages</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/38</url>
			<bugID>Issue #38</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		I cannot get read messages to be marked as read. Other people are having the same problem. I have reported this several times.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="27">
			<summary>sliding side panel</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/39</url>
			<bugID>Issue #39</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		I cannot find the options to hide the side sliding panel. I have had other people tell where it is located but for some reason I cannot find it on mine. I have looked at every options. Thank you.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="28">
			<summary>Bug: &quot;Message expired or not available&quot; toast being shown over and over again</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/40</url>
			<bugID>Issue #40</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Switching from my previous messenger app to QKSMS causes QKSMS to read all of my existing messages. Somewhere, a toast is being re-created/re-shown over and over again saying &quot;Message expired or not available&quot;, so its basically always on the screen (until I kill the app). Restarting the app continues to show the toast. Perhaps a better method would be to write to a log for all messages that are expired/unavailable? Instead of clogging the UI with endless toast's?
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="29">
			<summary>Pictures send horizontally</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/44</url>
			<bugID>Issue #44</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Hey guys, the pictures I take send horizontally. Is this normal, or a bug? This only happens with the pictures I've took.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="30">
			<summary>QKSMS Quick Contact Select Can't Find Contacts with a Number Listed as &quot;Main&quot;</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/47</url>
			<bugID>Issue #47</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		If you go to compose a message and attempt to find a contact by typing their name in the contact field it won't auto populate a contact if they only have a number listed as &quot;Main&quot;
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="31">
			<summary>&quot;This feature has not yet been implemented&quot; when viewing thread details.</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/48</url>
			<bugID>Issue #48</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		I've tried to use this feature a number of times now, hoping to get various details about a message thread and get disappointed every time. Are there plans to implement whatever functionality was intended any time soon?
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="32">
			<summary>Delivery confirmations not constant when texting an iPhone user</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/50</url>
			<bugID>Issue #50</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		DESCRIPTION Delivery confirmations are not constant when texting an iPhone user. You will sometimes get delivery confirmations, but not all the time. STEPS Text a person who has an iPhone EXPECTED When texting an iPhone user you will be receiving constant delivery confirmations REALITY Not constant delivery confirmations when texting an iPhone user
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="33">
			<summary>Conversation isn't marked as read if you have another app for sms.</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/51</url>
			<bugID>Issue #51</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		DESCRIPTION Conversations aren't marked as read when you have another sms app for default. STEPS Set another sms app for default in your phone. Use the app that you have selected for default. Open QKSMS and open one conversation with one new message. EXPECTED The conversation is marked as read. REALITY The conversation isn't marked as read.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="34">
			<summary>Enhancement Request: Add Name Of Sender To Group Messages</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/52</url>
			<bugID>Issue #52</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		One thing that's been bugging me is that in a group message, the only way to tell who sent a message is by looking at the contact picture. I have my contact pictures synced with Facebook, so they change on a regular basis, and I can't always tell who sent a particular message. It would be nice if the sender's name was included in the message, either at the beginning, or as a signature at the end. Loving the app!! I love that the dev is so involved in the community and always working to improve the app.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="35">
			<summary>Deleted failed message appearing in notification</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/53</url>
			<bugID>Issue #53</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		via Sebastian on G+ When my phone fails to send a message, there is always a second message that I deleted a long time ago in the notification &quot;X messages failed&quot; I already deleted the whole conversation but this message is always here.﻿
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="36">
			<summary>Bad MMS message, missing 'ok' button</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/54</url>
			<bugID>Issue #54</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		DESCRIPTION When you are a new user, this message appear, I just think that this is not a bug, it is a usability problem because the 'ok' button never exist. STEPS Make a new instalation. Don't setup the MMS config Open the QKSMS app. EXPECTED The message show 'ok' button REALITY The message don't show 'ok' button
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="37">
			<summary>QK Compose notification icon looks bad on light gray background</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/55</url>
			<bugID>Issue #55</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		On lollipop the icon looks really ugly.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="38">
			<summary>Changing night mode start/end times causes some text's color to become mixed up.</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/58</url>
			<bugID>Issue #58</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		No description provided.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="39">
			<summary>Pressing my phone's menu button causes QKSMS for force close</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/59</url>
			<bugID>Issue #59</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		I have an LG Optimus L9 running Android 4.1.2 and am affected by this bug: https://code.google.com/p/android/issues/detail?id=78154
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="40">
			<summary>Every time I open the app it shows the Success! Dialog box.</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/60</url>
			<bugID>Issue #60</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="41">
			<summary>Status Bar Color</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/61</url>
			<bugID>Issue #61</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Status bar color is a gradient, instead of flat colors. It's using kitkat way of using gradient on status bars. I'm using Android 5.0.2 on Galaxy S6.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="42">
			<summary>Overflow menu items appear as all dots</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/62</url>
			<bugID>Issue #62</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		DESCRIPTION Overflow menu items appear as all dots instead of the menu text. OS: stock 4.4.2 Model: Verizon LG G3 Screenshot
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="43">
			<summary>Call button in conversation calls 6855</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/63</url>
			<bugID>Issue #63</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		DESCRIPTION Pressing the call button in a conversation always dials 6855 rather than the contact number. STEPS Open QKSMS. Navigate to a conversation. Press the call button. EXPECTED The dialer is opened with the contacts phone number. REALITY The dialer is opened and dials &quot;6855&quot; DEVICES Model: LG Optimus G Carrier: Sprint
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="44">
			<summary>Sharing a jpg causes &quot;QKSMS can't access the file you're trying to share!&quot; toast</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/65</url>
			<bugID>Issue #65</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		No description provided.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="45">
			<summary>Contact photo for group messages is wrong</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/66</url>
			<bugID>Issue #66</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		It's a random photo from some other picture instead of the actual person's photo
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="46">
			<summary>App force closes on boot due to Automatic Night Mode</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/67</url>
			<bugID>Issue #67</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		logcat: W/PackageManager(  623): Not granting permission android.permission.CHANGE_CONFIGURATION to package com.moez.QKSMS (protectionLevel=50 flags=0x18be44)
W/PackageManager(  623): Not granting permission android.permission.CHANGE_CONFIGURATION to package com.moez.QKSMS (protectionLevel=50 flags=0x18be44)
I/ActivityManager(  623): Start proc 3203:com.moez.QKSMS/u0a99 for broadcast com.moez.QKSMS/.analytics.AnalyticsReportReceiver
I/ActivityManager(  623): Killing 3203:com.moez.QKSMS/u0a99 (adj 15): empty #17
I/ActivityManager(  623): Start proc 4577:com.moez.QKSMS/u0a99 for broadcast com.moez.QKSMS/.receiver.NightModeAutoReceiver
E/AndroidRuntime( 4577): Process: com.moez.QKSMS, PID: 4577
E/AndroidRuntime( 4577): java.lang.RuntimeException: Unable to start receiver com.moez.QKSMS.receiver.NightModeAutoReceiver: java.lang.NullPointerException: Attempt to invoke virtual method 'int android.content.res.Resources.getColor(int)' on a null object reference
E/AndroidRuntime( 4577):    at com.moez.QKSMS.ui.d.f(ThemeManager.java:347)
E/AndroidRuntime( 4577):    at com.moez.QKSMS.ui.d.a(ThemeManager.java:292)
E/AndroidRuntime( 4577):    at com.moez.QKSMS.receiver.NightModeAutoReceiver.onReceive(NightModeAutoReceiver.java:47)
D/LightFlow:MainRunningService(nowJustAccessibility)( 1424): **************************Package Name: android text: [Unfortunately, QKSMS has stopped., Report, OK]
I/ActivityManager(  623): Process com.moez.QKSMS (pid 4577) has died
W/ActivityManager(  623): Scheduling restart of crashed service com.moez.QKSMS/com.android.mms.transaction.TransactionService in 10942ms
I/ActivityManager(  623): Start proc 4844:com.moez.QKSMS/u0a99 for broadcast com.moez.QKSMS/.receiver.IconColorReceiver
I/ActivityManager(  623): Killing 4844:com.moez.QKSMS/u0a99 (adj 15): empty #17
I/ActivityManager(  623): Start proc 5330:com.moez.QKSMS/u0a99 for broadcast com.moez.QKSMS/.receiver.IconColorReceiver
D/LightFlow:MainRunningService(nowJustAccessibility)( 1424): **************************Package Name: rs.pedjaapps.alogcatroot.app text: [qksms]
D/LightFlow:MainRunningService(nowJustAccessibility)( 1424): **************************Package Name: rs.pedjaapps.alogcatroot.app text: [qksms]
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="47">
			<summary>Unread counter doesn't work on Samsung devices</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/69</url>
			<bugID>Issue #69</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		No description provided.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="48">
			<summary>Can't save MMS</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/70</url>
			<bugID>Issue #70</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		No description provided.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="49">
			<summary>Conversations show the wrong picture</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/71</url>
			<bugID>Issue #71</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		No description provided.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="50">
			<summary>Receiving group chat MMS messages is unreliable</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/72</url>
			<bugID>Issue #72</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		No description provided.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="51">
			<summary>App crashes when going from one thread to another</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/76</url>
			<bugID>Issue #76</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Hi I have been getting this issue on my galaxy s4 running the GPe rom, I submitted a bug report this morning stating that I want sure if it was my phone. If it is let me know and I won't send further logs
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="52">
			<summary>Sometimes the conversation disappears</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/77</url>
			<bugID>Issue #77</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		I'm running a verizon Moto X (2014) and I have noticed that sometimes the conversation that I am currently on when I open the app disappears. I have to select another conversation and then bring it back to get everything to show up. Sending is unaffected as well as notification receiving. I just can't see the past conversation at all. Thanks and keep up the good work!
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="53">
			<summary>Personal LED light setting automatically resets</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/78</url>
			<bugID>Issue #78</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		When trying to set a personal LED for people in my notification list I noticed a bug that meant it reset to the Original LED colour for the app and would not save. Example of how to test Set general LED colour for the app (example blue) Long hold on a conversation to bring up personal settings and then change that notification LED Back out of this conversation so you're back to the default messaging inbox screen Repeat step 2 and you can see that the initial colour of the LED is the default of the app I don't know whether this is an app wide issue or simply a problem related to my phone (Samsung galaxy S5 running 5.0).
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="54">
			<summary>Phone numbers with spaces recognized incorrectly</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/81</url>
			<bugID>Issue #81</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Hello, When you type a phone number in stock dialer, it is formatted to be more easy to read. For example: 123456789 is shown as 123 456 789. The problem is, QKSMS thinks that space is added to put more numbers in one entry at phone book. they are phone numbers
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="55">
			<summary>Phone numbers with spaces recognized incorrectly</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/82</url>
			<bugID>Issue #82</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Hello, When you type a phone number in stock dialer, it is formatted to be more easy to read. For example: 123456789 is shown as 123 456 789. The problem is, QKSMS thinks that space is added to put more numbers in one entry at phone book. Result: 123 as first receiver, 456 second receiver etc. Full info here http://i.imgur.com/gw5Y7EA.png
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="56">
			<summary>Enhancement request: Implement blocker function</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/84</url>
			<bugID>Issue #84</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		It would be great if you can implement a sms blocker function : block by keyword, block by number. Block by keyword is filtering unknown incoming sms by a list of keyword defined by a user. Block by number is filtering incoming sms by a list of phone number defined by a user. Thank you.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="57">
			<summary>QK Reply should not show in active message window</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/86</url>
			<bugID>Issue #86</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		v1.10.4 on Nexus 6. Also occurs on N5 The QK Reply feature is fantastic but it should be disabled if qksms is the currently active application. There's no need to popup an alert for an app you're already using. One idea could be to add an additional option to disable QK Reply if the phone is unlocked or potentially &quot;idle&quot; assuming you can define what idle actually means
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="58">
			<summary>When writing a new text, if switched to landscape, text is no longer here</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/88</url>
			<bugID>Issue #88</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Using version 1.11.3 on HTC ONE M8 with android 5.01 Strange bug, if I begin a text and switch to landscape mode ( from horizontal mode ) the text will be saved as a draft . If saved as a draft, the draft won't appear and so won't be useful.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="59">
			<summary>Can't share to a phone number only</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/90</url>
			<bugID>Issue #90</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		When trying to share content from an app through QKSMS, a toast appears letting me choose from my favorite contacts or letting me type a contact's name or number, but I can't just type a new number that hasn't been saved as a contact previously. Any attempt doesn't even show the number I'm typing and it's completely impossible to share anything to somebody not in your contacts. It's a very annoying bug...
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="60">
			<summary>Quick reply panel showing when it shouldn't</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/91</url>
			<bugID>Issue #91</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		When I dismiss a notification from the lock screen, next time I unlock the phone I get an empty quick-reply panel (no contact, no message). It shouldn't show the panel at all in my humble opinion, but if it does it should'nt be empty ;-)
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="61">
			<summary>Asks for In-App Purchase permission</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/93</url>
			<bugID>Issue #93</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		I just downloaded the app from the Play Store (can't wait to use it) but I noticed that it asked for an in-app purchase permission. In the description there are bullets for &quot;No Ads&quot; and &quot;Completely Free&quot; so I'm assuming the app won't ever really need that permission.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="62">
			<summary>Translations from crowdin</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/100</url>
			<bugID>Issue #100</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		hi, thanks for the app!; now is open source you can create a free account in crowdin for we translate the app to all languages thanks! for all!
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="63">
			<summary>Widget Doesn't Load</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/107</url>
			<bugID>Issue #107</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		After attaching the widget to the home screen, a &quot;Problem loading widget&quot; widget is added instead.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="64">
			<summary>Widget title bar text</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/113</url>
			<bugID>Issue #113</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		In the title bar of the widget, when it is sized to 3x3, the s in &quot;conversations&quot; is bumped to the next line. It's not critical, but it looks horrendous. This may be related to screen size. I can provide screenshot if necessary.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="65">
			<summary>if not allow read sms or read contacts permission, will crash</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/123</url>
			<bugID>Issue #123</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		if not allow read sms or read contacts permission, will crash. Caused by: java.lang.NullPointerException at com.moez.QKSMS.ui.dialog.DefaultSmsHelper.(DefaultSmsHelper.java:37) at com.moez.QKSMS.ui.MainActivity.onActivityResult(MainActivity.java:305) at android.app.Activity.dispatchActivityResult(Activity.java:5423)
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="66">
			<summary>Status bar shows gradient on Samsung devices running Lollipop</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/124</url>
			<bugID>Issue #124</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Instead of showing the flat style for Lollipop, they show the Kitkat gradient which is super ugly. I've had a lot of reports about this, but I'm unable to test this as I have a Nexus 5. Screenshot:
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="67">
			<summary>App doesn't observe locale date format</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/128</url>
			<bugID>Issue #128</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		The date of the messages isn't displayed in the locale format. It is shown as %B %d (month day) whereas it should be, in Europe, %d %B (day month).
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="68">
			<summary>Icon disapear from Launcher</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/141</url>
			<bugID>Issue #141</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Everytime I add the app icon to my launcher it disappears soon or later. This happens even if I drop it to the quick launch or to any screen. I use Google Launcher.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="69">
			<summary>Writting Issue</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/142</url>
			<bugID>Issue #142</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		android ICS When I write it doesn't show suggestions when t9 is on and when I press space it makes the first letter big, like when you start a new sentence.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="70">
			<summary>&quot;Update QKSMS icon color&quot; overrides theming engines and icon packs indefinitely</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/144</url>
			<bugID>Issue #144</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		DESCRIPTION On my Oneplus One, if I use &quot;Update QKSMS icon color&quot; even once, then the QKSMS icon no longer can be skinned by the Cyanogen OS 12 theming engine. QKSMS-picked icon will persist through icon packs and the like. STEPS Use QKSMS's &quot;update icon color&quot; function to change from default app icon Use Cyanogen OS's theming engine to apply an icon pack that would skin the QKSMS icon Return to the app drawer / home screen Observe the QKSMS icon EXPECTED QKSMS's icon is skinned by the icon pack OBSERVATIONS QKSMS's icon remains the one set by QKSMS.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="71">
			<summary>MMS doesn't work when connected to Wifi</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/153</url>
			<bugID>Issue #153</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Subject pretty self-explanatory - after googling it seems that other users were also having this issue: https://www.reddit.com/r/QKSMS/comments/2dv8r6/mms_doesnt_work_when_connected_to_wifi/
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="72">
			<summary>Add option to have dark app bar color in dark mode</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/154</url>
			<bugID>Issue #154</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		I like night mode. I like colored message bubbles, even in night mode. However, I do not like colored app bars in night mode An actual separate app bar color option would be a bit clunky, and clunkier still if there were a separate separate one for the dark theme. A simple switch, though, to make the app use this color only for the app bar in dark mode and actual black in AMOLED mode, is something I think could work quite nicely.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="73">
			<summary>Automatic night mode not working</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/158</url>
			<bugID>Issue #158</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Automatic night mode doesn't work. It was fixed in a previous update (I think 1.7 or something), but it appears to be broken again. It works each time I reset it (check and uncheck the box and reselect the times), but it kind of defeats the purpose of automatic night mode by doing that. I'm running 2.0.1
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="74">
			<summary>Feature list</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/164</url>
			<bugID>Issue #164</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Just found this app on F-Droid. The description was promising: the stock SMS app with extra features. I've been looking for per-contact notification settings - at least different ringtones. Is there a feature list detailing how this fork is different from stock?
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="75">
			<summary>Night mode right after setup is white on gray</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/165</url>
			<bugID>Issue #165</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		I've just run through the setup. Left the default color to teal and chose night mode. The result was white text on gray background - barely visible.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="76">
			<summary>Send Icon doesn't line up/fit</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/169</url>
			<bugID>Issue #169</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Device: OnePlus One (bacon) OS: CM-12.1-20150822-UNOFFICIAL-Sultan-bacon [xda-link] Android Version: 5.1.1 App Version: 2.0.1 Bug: When typing a new message, the &quot;+&quot; turns into a &quot;&gt;&quot; that doesn't fully line up at the point (see screenshot). [full-size] edit: greatly improved report (better wording/spelling)
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="77">
			<summary>Textra gives notification saying QKSMS interferes</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/172</url>
			<bugID>Issue #172</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Is this a known issue? I'm not sure if this is even the right place to post it. This is with Textra set as default sms app, QK just installed and not even opened.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="78">
			<summary>Latest Master: Receiving text toast always &quot;sms desde numero #XXX.. &quot;</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/176</url>
			<bugID>Issue #176</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Using the latest version of master branch, whenever I receive a message, the toast that appears always is the spanish &quot;sms desde numero #xxx-xxx-xxxx&quot; regardless of the language I set through phone settings (specifically tried English, French, Chinese). Testing on a Nexus 5. Anyone able to reproduce this?
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="79">
			<summary>Qk-reply shouldn't open if I'm in the qksms app.</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/179</url>
			<bugID>Issue #179</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		A lot of times, I'll be in a conversation and then lock my phone, and when I unlock it after receiving a message, the qk-reply is there floating overtop of the same exact conversation in the app. Kind of pointless.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="80">
			<summary>Facebook contact photos aren't shown.</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/180</url>
			<bugID>Issue #180</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		If you've got a device that still supports Facebook contact sync, contacts that use photos from Facebook aren't shown. The qksms still recognizes the cotnact from Facebook, it just can't pull the photo properly.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="81">
			<summary>In the version 2.0.1 has disappeared the colored nav bar</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/181</url>
			<bugID>Issue #181</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		In the version 2.0.1 has disappeared the colored nav bar option on Lollipop and this is a very important feature
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="82">
			<summary>No return key on keyboard</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/184</url>
			<bugID>Issue #184</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		When I try to compose a message in the bottom right corner of my keyboard where I typically see a return key to make a new line there is only the button to the emoji keyboard. Why can't I insert a new line into my messages? I am using Google Keyboard on a Samsung Galaxy S4 running Android 5.0.1 (Sometimes on other apps the keyboard has a return key and if you hold it you will find the key to get to the emojis. Even if I hold down the emoji key I can't find a key to make a new line)
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="83">
			<summary>Remaining characters counter not aligned properly when system font size is set to small</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/185</url>
			<bugID>Issue #185</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		The title pretty much sums it up, the remaining characters counter is not aligned properly when system font size is set to small. Nexus 6, Android 5.1.1, QKSMS 2.0.1 Screenshot here: http://i.imgur.com/Q3LGPi8.png
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="84">
			<summary>Smileys sent through the Samsung SMS app show as &quot;??&quot;</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/187</url>
			<bugID>Issue #187</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		The title pretty much sums it all. When I receive an SMS from my mother, who uses a Samsung device (Samsung S4 mini - Up to date) with the original SMS app, smileys are shown in QKSMS as &quot;??&quot; (juste two interrogation points). If 2 smileys are sent it shows &quot;????&quot; (2 times 2 interrogation points) etc. I don't know if this is possible to solve in any way, but seeing the amount of people using Samsung phones everywhere, it might be something to look into.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="85">
			<summary>Description text of pictures in the conversation list is wrong</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/188</url>
			<bugID>Issue #188</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		DESCRIPTION The description text of pictures (MMS) in the conversation list is wrong STEPS Receive or send a MMS (Picture) with a description Go to the conversation view EXPECTED The description text should just say &quot;description&quot; and not &quot;part/text/plain:description&quot; OBSERVATIONS
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="86">
			<summary>MMS having trouble</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/192</url>
			<bugID>Issue #192</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		MMS doesn't work as well as it does in Textra. I don't receive any pictures, and occasionally a group text will sort of work. I always have my data turned off. Textra will tell me when I need data on in order to get a text. QK never tells me, so I end up unable to receive. I can usually send to a group a text. I know this isn't very detailed, I'll give you more info if you ask me.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="87">
			<summary>Notification sound doesn't play when screen off and QKSMS open</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/196</url>
			<bugID>Issue #196</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		The notification sound doesn't play when QKSMS app is open and the screen is off with wake phone enabled. -wake phone: on -notification: enabled -notification led: on -vibration: on -show ticker: on device: Samsung Galaxy S6 - g920T OS: Android 5.1.1
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="88">
			<summary>Received message keeps screen on</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/197</url>
			<bugID>Issue #197</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Whenever I receive a message, the screen turns on and stays that way. It does not turn off after the display timeout. Basically, when I did not hear the notification sound, I have learned to check messages once I feel the phone get hot in my pocket (due to the screen being on). This happens even though I have the &quot;Wake phone&quot; setting disabled both in general settings and in specific contact's settings. Anyone else noticing this unpleasant behaviour? Do you need some additional data to investigate? Nexus 6, Android 5.1.1, QKSMS 2.0.1 EDIT: I noticed I am not alone: https://plus.google.com/u/0/108762715235332764384/posts/FjbgtUP1pvn EDIT 2: This happens only with one specific contact for which I have set separate notification sound, other contacts don't do this. However, as I stated, the &quot;Wake phone&quot; setting is disabled both in general settings and in the specific contact's settings. Also, the contact's notification settings are identical to general notification settings, except for the sound.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="89">
			<summary>new version drains battery very quickly</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/198</url>
			<bugID>Issue #198</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		version 2.1.0 has started eating up my battery life. It has used 25% of my overall battery in the last few hours. LG G3 (Verizon) VS985 - Android 5.0.1
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="90">
			<summary>Replace numbers by contact name</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/199</url>
			<bugID>Issue #199</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Sometimes a number is received from a contact and it is already on contact list. It would be great if QKSMS replace the number by the name of the contact and type of number (mobile, home, ...) This resource is implemented in Chomp SMS and is very useful with cell services that sends SMS messages with missed calls while the phone was unreachable or turned off.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="91">
			<summary>Make this app fast on scrolling; switching contact messages; sending messages; etc</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/200</url>
			<bugID>Issue #200</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		No description provided.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="92">
			<summary>Conversation colors wrong initially for night mode</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/201</url>
			<bugID>Issue #201</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		In the setup after first installing the app, if I select night mode, as soon as I press &quot;Finish Setup&quot;, I see all conversations with light backgrounds and white text. When I exit out of the app and launch it again, this is fixed.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="93">
			<summary>Send button icon looks like a 'T' instead of a '+' after sending a message</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/204</url>
			<bugID>Issue #204</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		The animation seems to fail to come back to its initial position after the cross for canceling sending goes away. Tested on a Oneplus One, 5.1.1.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="94">
			<summary>Issue with notifications</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/206</url>
			<bugID>Issue #206</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		If my phone is locked and screen is off, I get the buzz/notification sound well before I see the notification on my phone. Like a 3-4 second delay.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="95">
			<summary>Need design mocks for audio player</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/212</url>
			<bugID>Issue #212</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Design mockups for audio player and for audio attachments needed. It'd aldo be helpful if i could get one for voice notes. (similiar to whatsapp?) @moezbhatti
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="96">
			<summary>App crashes on first run</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/217</url>
			<bugID>Issue #217</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Hello I use an Alcatel OneTouch Idol 2 Mini L with Android 4.3 and QKSMS 2.10. On the first launch of the app, the one with the small introduction about colors and night mode, when I try to: Use the return key; Use the menu key; Press the terminate area; The app crashes. I can use the home key but the app will crash when I launch it again. The only way to use it is to add the widget then to launch the app with.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="97">
			<summary>scheduled messages</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/218</url>
			<bugID>Issue #218</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		It would be great that scheduled messages were supported! Thanks.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="98">
			<summary>Help My Please</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/221</url>
			<bugID>Issue #221</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		How do I edit the name of package?
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="99">
			<summary>Update Google Play for latest release</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/222</url>
			<bugID>Issue #222</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		In Google play, the latest release is 2.0.1. Can you upload the 2.1 release? Regards
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="100">
			<summary>Clicking &quot;Read&quot; on the lock screen doesn't clear the pop up box when the screen is unlocked</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/223</url>
			<bugID>Issue #223</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Clicking &quot;Read&quot; on the lock screen doesn't clear the pop up box when the screen is unlocked. Instead it clears the message in the box, leaving an empty box. Then, when I get a text from someone else, the new box does not show up, it still shows the empty box from the previous, read text. I'm using an OnePlus One running Exodus. QKSMS version 2.1.0﻿
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="101">
			<summary>Notification disappears if phone locks while in app</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/224</url>
			<bugID>Issue #224</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		If I lock my phone while in the app and I receive a message, the notification quickly pops and disappears again. I also tried to see if being in another conversation to the one that received the message affected it, but it seems the message disappears no matter what conversation I'm in when the phone locks. This is on a Galaxy S6 SM-G920F, Android 5.1.1 and QkSMS 2.0.1
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="102">
			<summary>The &quot;Conversations&quot; label is incorrect after locking and then unlocking my smartphone</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/225</url>
			<bugID>Issue #225</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Basically, if I lock my smartphone after leaving a conversation (leading to the conversation list) and then unlock it, the &quot;Conversations&quot; title will display a contact name (from the conversation I initially left).
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="103">
			<summary>Recieving a message won't wake the smartphone, it will only vibrate it</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/227</url>
			<bugID>Issue #227</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		No description provided.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="104">
			<summary>Not a issue but is v2.2.0 going to be released in Google Play?</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/229</url>
			<bugID>Issue #229</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		No description provided.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="105">
			<summary>Notification ticker text only showing &quot;QKSMS: New message&quot;</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/230</url>
			<bugID>Issue #230</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		App version: 2.2.0 Device: Galaxy S3, 4.4.2 The ticker text when receiving messages no longer shows the message, only &quot;QKSMS: New message.&quot; I do not have private notifications enabled. Expected behaviour: Show sms message in ticker. Steps: Enable ticker text: SMS notifications - enabled; Show ticker - enabled; Private notifications - show all Receive text message Watch status bar
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="106">
			<summary>Orientation changes can cause app to &quot;blank out&quot;</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/233</url>
			<bugID>Issue #233</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		If QKSMS is left as the active application when the phone screen turns off, changing the orientation of the phone before turning the screen back on can cause the conversation window to go blank. Returning to the list of conversations will blank out that list as well. The problem is fixed by clearing the application from the recent applications list. This seems to have started as of the October 21st update. Device: Moto X (2nd Generation) Android version: 5.1 Carrier: U.S. Cellular Steps to reproduce: Open QKSMS Open any conversation While in portrait orientation, press the power button on the phone to turn off the screen Rotate the phone to landscape orientation Turn the screen back on (and unlock the device if necessary) Observe the blank conversation screen Use the back button of the phone or the application to return to the conversation list Observe a lack of converstions Use the Recent Applications list to clear QKSMS Re-open QKSMS. All functionality is restored.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="107">
			<summary>Using 40 permissions. For an SMS app?</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/234</url>
			<bugID>Issue #234</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		I was interested in this application until I saw what permissions are required to run this software. 40 permissions seems rather excessive for an application that essentially reads/writes SMS. There's no detailed info on the additional features this application brings to the party. For instance, why would it need to &quot;Control Near Field Communication&quot;, &quot;Change Wi-Fi state&quot;, &quot;Fine (GPS) location&quot;, &quot;Take pictures and videos&quot;, &quot;Record audio&quot;, &quot;Directly call phone numbers&quot;? Perhaps it would be helpful if more information could be provided about this application. That way people like me could understand the reasons behind such permission requests.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="108">
			<summary>Extreme battery usage with unread message</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/235</url>
			<bugID>Issue #235</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		When I have an unread message waiting for me to read it, QKSMS starts to use an insane amount of battery.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="109">
			<summary>java.lang.NoSuchMethodError</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/236</url>
			<bugID>Issue #236</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		View Crash Report on Crittercism Reported by: Moez Bhatti (moez@qklabs.com) Status: Resolved in Version: Next Release This Crash occured 0 times for 0 users 0 java.lang.NoSuchMethodError: android.provider.Telephony$Sms.getDefaultSmsPackage 1 at com.moez.QKSMS.ui.dialog.DefaultSmsHelper.(DefaultSmsHelper.java:37) 2 at com.moez.QKSMS.ui.MainActivity.onActivityResult(MainActivity.java:338) 3 at android.app.Activity.dispatchActivityResult(Activity.java:5383) 4 at android.app.ActivityThread.deliverResults(ActivityThread.java:3575) 5 at android.app.ActivityThread.handleSendResult(ActivityThread.java:3622) 6 at android.app.ActivityThread.access$1100(ActivityThread.java:169) 7 at android.app.ActivityThread$H.handleMessage(ActivityThread.java:1436) 8 at android.os.Handler.dispatchMessage(Handler.java:107) 9 at android.os.Looper.loop(Looper.java:194) 10 at android.app.ActivityThread.main(ActivityThread.java:5433) 11 at java.lang.reflect.Method.invokeNative(Native Method) 12 at java.lang.reflect.Method.invoke(Method.java:525) 13 at com.android.internal.os.ZygoteInit$MethodAndArgsCaller.run(ZygoteInit.java:924) 14 at com.android.internal.os.ZygoteInit.main(ZygoteInit.java:691) 15 at dalvik.system.NativeStart.main(Native Method)
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="110">
			<summary>Unread messages make QKSMS crash</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/240</url>
			<bugID>Issue #240</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		My system: Android 4.3 and QK 2.2 How to reproduce: When receiving a message, click on notification to open the app. Result: QKSMS crash Expected: QKSMS opened to see sms
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="111">
			<summary>Mark message as unread make app crash</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/241</url>
			<bugID>Issue #241</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		My system: Android 4.3 and QK 2.2 How to reproduce: Open QKSMS, click on a conversation, mark as unread. Result: Immediate crash Expected: Mark conversation as unread Coul be related to qklabs#240?
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="112">
			<summary>Delete conversation make QKSMS crasj</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/242</url>
			<bugID>Issue #242</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		My system: Android 4.3 and QK 2.2 How to reproduce: Open QKSMS, click conversation, delete conversation Result: QKSMS crash Expected: Conversation deleted
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="113">
			<summary>The camera button on the compose message doesn't work</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/243</url>
			<bugID>Issue #243</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		I am on v2.2.1.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="114">
			<summary>Battery Drain is insane on Marshmallow</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/249</url>
			<bugID>Issue #249</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Just installed marshmallow last night, fresh charge going to work. Not even an hour later I have a battery warning at 15%. I wish I had taken a screenshot, but it slipped my mind. QKSMS had used 137% battery over the last 24 hours at that point. 98% active rate in RAM. Perhaps a 6.0 bug with perms or something? Just insane. My phone was practically on fire by the time I noticed.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="115">
			<summary>SMS Scheduler</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/262</url>
			<bugID>Issue #262</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		It'd be nice to have an inbuilt option to delay a message.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="116">
			<summary>java.lang.NullPointerException</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/265</url>
			<bugID>Issue #265</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		View Crash Report on Crittercism Reported by: Moez Bhatti (moez@qklabs.com) Status: Unresolved This Crash occured 1240 times for 866 users 0 java.lang.RuntimeException: An error occured while executing doInBackground() 1 at android.os.AsyncTask$3.done(AsyncTask.java:300) 2 at java.util.concurrent.FutureTask.finishCompletion(FutureTask.java:355) 3 at java.util.concurrent.FutureTask.setException(FutureTask.java:222) 4 at java.util.concurrent.FutureTask.run(FutureTask.java:242) 5 at java.util.concurrent.ThreadPoolExecutor.runWorker(ThreadPoolExecutor.java:1112) 6 at java.util.concurrent.ThreadPoolExecutor$Worker.run(ThreadPoolExecutor.java:587) 7 at java.lang.Thread.run(Thread.java:818) 8 Caused by: java.lang.NullPointerException: Attempt to invoke virtual method 'android.content.ContentResolver android.content.Context.getContentResolver()' on a null object reference 9 at com.moez.QKSMS.data.Conversation.loadFromThreadId(Conversation.java:1286) 10 at com.moez.QKSMS.data.Conversation.(Conversation.java:117) 11 at com.moez.QKSMS.data.Conversation.get(Conversation.java:151) 12 at com.moez.QKSMS.ui.messagelist.MessageListFragment$LoadConversationTask.doInBackground(MessageListFragment.java:1421) 13 at com.moez.QKSMS.ui.messagelist.MessageListFragment$LoadConversationTask.doInBackground(MessageListFragment.java:1412) 14 at android.os.AsyncTask$2.call(AsyncTask.java:288) 15 at java.util.concurrent.FutureTask.run(FutureTask.java:237) 16 ... 3 more 17 java.lang.NullPointerException: Attempt to invoke virtual method 'android.content.ContentResolver android.content.Context.getContentResolver()' on a null object reference 18 at com.moez.QKSMS.data.Conversation.loadFromThreadId(Conversation.java:1286) 19 at com.moez.QKSMS.data.Conversation.(Conversation.java:117) 20 at com.moez.QKSMS.data.Conversation.get(Conversation.java:151) 21 at com.moez.QKSMS.ui.messagelist.MessageListFragment$LoadConversationTask.doInBackground(MessageListFragment.java:1421) 22 at com.moez.QKSMS.ui.messagelist.MessageListFragment$LoadConversationTask.doInBackground(MessageListFragment.java:1412) 23 at android.os.AsyncTask$2.call(AsyncTask.java:288) 24 at java.util.concurrent.FutureTask.run(FutureTask.java:237) 25 at java.util.concurrent.ThreadPoolExecutor.runWorker(ThreadPoolExecutor.java:1112) 26 at java.util.concurrent.ThreadPoolExecutor$Worker.run(ThreadPoolExecutor.java:587) 27 at java.lang.Thread.run(Thread.java:818)
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="117">
			<summary>New Update v2.2.3 crash on first launch</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/268</url>
			<bugID>Issue #268</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		No description provided.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="118">
			<summary>SMS occasionally fails to send</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/270</url>
			<bugID>Issue #270</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		I'm having this issue where sometimes, seemingly random, text messages wont get sent. They're stuck at &quot;sending&quot;. Even if I send another one right after, which gets sent and delivered, the previous on does not go anywhere. All is good when I use the stock messaging app (xperia lollipop 5.1.1) and if I switch back to that, the messages that QKSMS failed to sent off will eventually be sent by the stock app. What on earth can it be? Kind of seems to me like these third party texting apps functioned better back in the day where they were dependent on the stock app...
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="119">
			<summary>MMS attachments seem restricted to photos</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/276</url>
			<bugID>Issue #276</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Just downloaded, testing-out the program; MMS attachments seem restricted to photos. I need to send vcard for work, and other tiny files. Why the limitation?﻿
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="120">
			<summary>[Feature Request) Add a SMS Server</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/280</url>
			<bugID>Issue #280</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Like this App for example: https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=it.giox.wifisms For typing SMS on a PC or Tablet in the same Wifi network. Maybe with a setting to start the server automatic in a specific Wifi network.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="121">
			<summary>Ability to delete multiple messages in a conservation</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/283</url>
			<bugID>Issue #283</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		No description provided.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="122">
			<summary>Action bar tinting issue</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/289</url>
			<bugID>Issue #289</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Action bar in Recent apps panel does not comply the selected theme and remains dark.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="123">
			<summary>Group MMS duplicate messages</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/295</url>
			<bugID>Issue #295</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Have tested with other apps. T-Mobile Sometimes the two messages will arrive at the same time, sometimes significantly delayed.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="124">
			<summary>Add quick reply from notifications</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/296</url>
			<bugID>Issue #296</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		No description provided.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="125">
			<summary>Can't send quick message sms when declining the call.</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/297</url>
			<bugID>Issue #297</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Phone - One Plus One X Oxygen OS 2.1.4 DESCRIPTION Can't send quick message sms when declining the call. STEPS Set Qksms as default message app, Do not pick up call, Select &quot;send quick message&quot;, Choose one of the pre-definied messages, Select &quot;send&quot;, Confirmation &quot;Message Sent&quot; appears but there is no sms in qksms app, and no real sms is sent. EXPECTED Sent sms while not picking the phone up. OBSERVATIONS Everything works fine when the default google message app is selected.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="126">
			<summary>Quickreply mark as read cancels delay message</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/300</url>
			<bugID>Issue #300</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		In version 2.2.4. Steps to repro: set a delay for sending, say 10 seconds get a message while using the phone reply to message in quickreply press send before 10 seconds pass, press mark message as read in quickreply Expected behaviour: Message will be send after the delay Actual behaviour: Message is not sent
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="127">
			<summary>Random colours for contacts without pictures</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/301</url>
			<bugID>Issue #301</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		I'm using qksms, but I don't have any picture for my contacts, unlike in this screen: I only have their first letter in a circle ; it would be great to have a different colour per contact, instead of the same for every one of them.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="128">
			<summary>Every different MMS in thread is showing as same single MMS</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/302</url>
			<bugID>Issue #302</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		So I tried out the app tonight. Sent my gf a few pictures of a new haircut. There's tons of older pictures in the thread. Now, every single picture in our thread is showing as the same haircut picture. When I click on any of the pictures it will show the correct one in the new window. Issue persists upon reboot. Note : it is only the pictures I have sent with the issue. The pictures I have received show the true image. Nexus 5 straight talk
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="129">
			<summary>Conversations load slowly</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/304</url>
			<bugID>Issue #304</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		When I tap a conversation it slides into view but takes some time before the actual conversation loads. I've tested it on other apps and they load instantaneously (on the plus side, the other apps just don't cut it compared to QKSMS).
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="130">
			<summary>Drafts can't be opened back</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/310</url>
			<bugID>Issue #310</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		When I write a message to a contact
And I press back
And I press the contact again
Then I do not see my draft
And I see no way of getting my draft back (or any draft)
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="131">
			<summary>Compose screen doesn't save drafts</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/314</url>
			<bugID>Issue #314</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Especially an issue on rotation
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="132">
			<summary>Remove &quot;Show all/fewer preferences&quot; feature</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/315</url>
			<bugID>Issue #315</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Because it's useless and disturbing
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="133">
			<summary>Fix choppy/wrong gradients animation from the home screen &gt; settings.</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/316</url>
			<bugID>Issue #316</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		https://www.dropbox.com/s/6w0ffs1p61zt98u/2015_12_21_12_57_00.mp4?dl=0
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="134">
			<summary>Black icons on dark background</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/317</url>
			<bugID>Issue #317</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		I have Android 4.4.4 and notifications have black icons on both the icon on the status bar and the on the buttons. You won't cut out we poor Android 4 users, will you? :-)
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="135">
			<summary>Enhancement Request: Random color scheme for each conversation at startup</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/318</url>
			<bugID>Issue #318</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Don't be cruel with this request. You are talking with my girlfriend 😒 Anyway... thanks for this great Free as in Freedom software!
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="136">
			<summary>Enhancement Request: larger or user settable QK Compose size</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/319</url>
			<bugID>Issue #319</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		The window is very small on my 6P. It would be nice if this could be made larger based on screen size, or if the use could configure its size in the QK Compose settings.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="137">
			<summary>When on quickreply window, notification doesn't close when more than one message is received from the same person. Pressing 'Reply' again will result to a blank conversation window.</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/322</url>
			<bugID>Issue #322</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		DESCRIPTION Notification / Heads-up still keeps showing &quot;x new messages&quot; whenever I receive one message, pressed 'Reply', then received another message from the same person. STEPS Receive a message from Contact A Press 'Reply' Receive another message from Contact A while sending a reply EXPECTED Notification will be closed OBSERVATIONS Notification is still there, indicating that there are x number of messages received. When 'Reply' is pressed again, a blank conversation without a contact name will appear.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="138">
			<summary>MMS auto config message like a small dog humping a leg</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/327</url>
			<bugID>Issue #327</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		I checked the box. Some time went by. First pop up about success. OK. Some time went by. Many many more of the same pop up (seconds apart and in bursts). Hard to dismiss due to layering issues in and out of the app. Fresh install likely required to show this.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="139">
			<summary>Popup SMS doesn't extend</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/333</url>
			<bugID>Issue #333</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		I'm running the latest version (from the play store) which is 2.4.1 on a Nexus 5 first gen, running latest android 6.0.1. I'm using QKSMS and I've noticed that, the popup doesn't extend while I try to extend in order to see more thant the new sms. The problem is that when I try to extend the popup, the app shutdown and I have to re-open it again and go through the app to view all the messages.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="140">
			<summary>Android Wear message thread should start at the bottom</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/335</url>
			<bugID>Issue #335</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		When I receive a message and I switch to the thread to see that message on my watch, the thread always starts at the first message ever received which can be very annoying. I have to scroll through hundreds of messages before I can get to the actual last received message from a contact.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="141">
			<summary>Sms scheduling</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/337</url>
			<bugID>Issue #337</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Lack scheduling functionality in sending sms
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="142">
			<summary>Disable phone sound when headphone / headset is connected</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/339</url>
			<bugID>Issue #339</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		When a headphone or headset is connected (either wired or Bluetooth), in sound mode, SMS notification sounds are played by both internal speaker and headphone. Internal speaker should be disabled (or there might be an option to achieve that). Tested in 2.4.1 and 2.2.4 with Android 4.4.2.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="143">
			<summary>Organize MessageUtils class</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/340</url>
			<bugID>Issue #340</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		It's currently a huge mess of helper functions
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="144">
			<summary>Moto Display notifications aren't working</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/343</url>
			<bugID>Issue #343</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		If anyone has a phone that supports Moto Display, let me know and we can work together to fix this one
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="145">
			<summary>Wakelock Battery Drain</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/344</url>
			<bugID>Issue #344</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Hi there, First off, love the app been using it for over a month without any issue. Just recently, QKSMS has been preventing my phone from going into deep sleep. I must force close the app and then the CPU will go into deep sleep. I've tried clearing app cache, app data, uninstalling, and wiping the cache all to no avail. I've since switched to Textra (really don't want to) and its no longer happening. If there's any more information I can provide, please let me know. Oxygen OS 2.1.3x OnePlus X
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="146">
			<summary>Sliding panel tab no longer works</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/346</url>
			<bugID>Issue #346</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Seem to have lost a working sliding panel tab after version 2.4.1. I can see the panel on the right and it scrolls up and down, but I can't get it to slide open in version 2.5.0 or 2.5.1.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="147">
			<summary>MMS doesn't work on Project FI</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/347</url>
			<bugID>Issue #347</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Can't receive any pictures on Project Fi (haven't tested group MMS). From what I've been able to find it seems like it's because Project Fi uses the new (5.0?) version of APN that QKSMS doesn't use yet, because service switches between providers.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="148">
			<summary>The input text disappears upon rotation</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/353</url>
			<bugID>Issue #353</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		If I write a long text and unfortunately the toggle screen (rotation) all the entered text disappears. QKSMS V2.5.1 On Honor 7 Android 5.0.2
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="149">
			<summary>Text input box does not grow with typing</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/354</url>
			<bugID>Issue #354</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Which makes it impossible to read and review large messages while authoring. 👍 1
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="150">
			<summary>Menu not reachable from body of last message if last one is incoming</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/359</url>
			<bugID>Issue #359</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		On most messages tap anywhere for the menu (required to get details for time stamps that I feel should be visible in the first place, but I digress), however if the last one is from the other person, you can't tap the message to get this menu, and can only tap the timestamp below it, which is a small finger target.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="151">
			<summary>Back button in top bar appears when in base list screen</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/360</url>
			<bugID>Issue #360</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		I'll have to update this on when/how this happens, but you press it intuitively and exit the app. It shouldn't be shown when not in a message or config screen or something...
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="152">
			<summary>Base screen spends too much space on circles with letters</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/361</url>
			<bugID>Issue #361</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		And insufficient on name, draft, message start/teaser, time. I know this is on purpose, as are some other bugs I've filed, but it feels like there could be a bit less grey around the sides of the circles?
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="153">
			<summary>Can't donate through Google</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/363</url>
			<bugID>Issue #363</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Hi! I just want to say that QKSMS is absolutely amazing! I just started using it, and tyvm for such a great FOSS messaging app! I downloaded the app from F-Droid, and when I go to donate through Google it tells me that this version of the app is not configured for billing through Google Play. Does this mean I have to install through the Play Store, or is something just not set up yet? Thanks again for all your hard work, awesome job devs!
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="154">
			<summary>[FEATURE REQUEST] Fetch from multiple MMSC</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/367</url>
			<bugID>Issue #367</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Is it possible to fetch MMS from more than one server?
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="155">
			<summary>[Feature] Differ between send to MSC and recipient</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/370</url>
			<bugID>Issue #370</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		It would be nice, if there would be one check mark when the SMS has been delivered to the MSC and a second one when it has been delivered to the device of the recipient. Thanks in advance!
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="156">
			<summary>MMS Configuration Layout Improvements</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/375</url>
			<bugID>Issue #375</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		The current MMS Configuration tool is awkward and not clear about QK SMS requires the user to do. I have MMS settings correctly set under my APN configuration. Do I need to re-do the settings again? If QK MMS settings don't match my APN settings, what are the ramifications? If I choose not to set MMS settings under QK, will QK still work correctly? If I use system settings, how do I make the MMS setup reminders go away? Can I view what QK has determined my settings should be, without seperately entering MMSC, MMS proxy, and MMS port to verify that they are correct? I propose the following layout for QK MMS configuration: Current MMS configuration layout: MMS Configuration Automatically Configure MMS MMSC MMS proxy MMS port Suggested layout: MMS Configuration MMS Configuration Preference (selected preference in small text) MMSC (&quot;Default&quot; or MMSC setting in small text) MMS proxy (&quot;Default&quot; or proxy setting in small text) MMS port (&quot;Default&quot; or port setting in small text) &quot;MMS Configuration Preference&quot; would bring up a dialog with three options: Use device MMS settings QK automatic MMS configuration Manual MMS configuration For the &quot;Use device MMS settings&quot; option: &quot;Use device MMS settings&quot; would be listed in small text under &quot;MMS Configuration Preference&quot; &quot;Default&quot; would be listed under (each, in small text) MMSC, MMS proxy, and MMS port MMSC, MMS proxy, and MMS port would all be ghosted, and not edit-able This should be the default preference For the &quot;QK automatic MMS configuration&quot; option: &quot;QK automatic MMS configuration&quot; would be listed in small text under &quot;MMS Configuration Preference&quot; Auto-populated field settings would be listed under (each, in small text) MMSC, MMS proxy, and MMS port MMSC, MMS proxy, and MMS port would all be ghosted, and not edit-able For the &quot;Manual MMS configuration&quot; option: &quot;Manual MMS configuration&quot; would be listed in small text under &quot;MMS Configuration Preference&quot; MMSC, MMS proxy, and MMS port would each be edit-able User-defined field settings would be listed under (each, in small text) MMSC, MMS proxy, and MMS port The QK SMS dialog that asks the user to &quot;Set up MMS?&quot; should give the following options: Use my device's MMS settings (save and go to QK) Let QK SMS automatically configure my MMS settings (bring up list of networks, save, go to QK) I want to manually configure my MMS settings (bring up dialog with MMSC, proxy, and port) 👍 1
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="157">
			<summary>QK Reply showing wrong contact and no message</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/376</url>
			<bugID>Issue #376</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Most of the time when I receive a message, QK Reply shows a wrong contact and no message inside the popup. I did not dare to enter something in the reply field, but when clicking outside of the popup or ... &gt; &quot;Open conversation&quot; shows the wrong message thread too. This has been happening for about 6 months. The reason I did not report this before is because I was trying to discover what triggered this. It happens about 80% of the time, so makes QK Reply really useless actually. QKSMS version: 2.5.1 Android version: 6.0.1 (build number MMB29S)
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="158">
			<summary>Dual Sim Support</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/381</url>
			<bugID>Issue #381</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Please add dual sim capability it would be helpful for most of the user i guess
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="159">
			<summary>Add ability to open phone number in contacts</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/390</url>
			<bugID>Issue #390</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Currently the only option is to call a contract or phone number from the app. It should be possible to save an unknown number as a contact, or at least open a number in contacts somehow.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="160">
			<summary>Can't select sms with numbers inside bug</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/392</url>
			<bugID>Issue #392</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		When I try to select an sms to open &quot;Option message&quot; view, if there is a number, like a telephone number or something like that, which is highlighted, the &quot;Option message&quot; view doesn't appear! It appears only if I select the row but outside the window of the message. This is surely a problem if the message is very long and there isn't the contact icon so there's not a lot of place to select the row!
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="161">
			<summary>Crash when sending MMS to self</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/393</url>
			<bugID>Issue #393</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Using QKSMS 2.5.2 on Android 5.1.1. Here's how the bug happened: Created a new contact named &quot;127.0.0.1&quot; the phone number of which is mine. Took a picture (res: 3840*2160, file size: 2,67MO) with my stock phone app. Used the &quot;share&quot; button, selected QKSMS which brought up the Quick Reply interface with the picture embedded. Sent the picture to the &quot;127.0.0.1&quot; contact with the word &quot;test&quot; attached. Now, whenever I try to open my conversation with &quot;127.0.0.1&quot;, the app crashes everytime.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="162">
			<summary>Reset &quot;Update QKSMS icon color&quot; feature</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/395</url>
			<bugID>Issue #395</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Because it break custom icon packs
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="163">
			<summary>[BUG?] Message vanishs if composed throughout a message search</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/398</url>
			<bugID>Issue #398</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Today I used the search function to find a message with a contact. (basically I looked only for the contact-history of this contact, but the search for contacts is still missing in qksms...), Anyway: I selected one message of the search results of the desired contacts and could compose a new message to this contact. In this normal compose window only the last message was displayed, but the contacts name was in the title - so everything seemed OK. I hit send and the message seemed to be sent. But: I can't find this message anymore, neither in the conctac's conversation, nor in the message-overview, nor in the standard Android SMS-App, nor with the search function. So, where is it? Was is sent? Why I cant find it anymore? I did not get any error message.... What's happening here? Can anybody reproduce this?
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="164">
			<summary>Tapping a notification takes you to wrong conversation</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/405</url>
			<bugID>Issue #405</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		DESCRIPTION A notification does not take the user to the corresponding conversation. STEPS Open up a conversation with person A in QKSMS Wait until your display switches off and your phone becomes locked Wait until a new SMS from person B arrives Tap on the body of the notification (not the buttons) or drag down the notification to open it EXPECTED You're taken to the conversation with person B OBSERVATIONS The conversation with person A is displayed instead. Maybe related to #73. 👍 1
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="165">
			<summary>[BUG] After sending a new message with &quot;+&quot;, screen turns empty (but should show history or main screen)</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/411</url>
			<bugID>Issue #411</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		DESCRIPTION If composing a new message for an existing contact, after the message was sent qksms stays in the composing window but it is completely empty. Could be connected to #396 and #397 STEPS Click &quot;+&quot; to compose a new SMS select a contact (from which a history should be available, but is not loaded, reported in #397) type a message + click send EXPECTED qksms should either load and display the history of the contact's conversation after sending (#397) OR qksms should switch to the message main screen OBSERVATIONS The screen becomes completely empty. Only the contact's name is displayed, but neither the conversation history, nor even the recently sent message is visible! Tested with v2.5.2
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="166">
			<summary>[IMPROVEMENT] Changelog-Screen + Why there is no CHANGELOG on Github (and F-Droid), but only at google?</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/412</url>
			<bugID>Issue #412</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		I can't find any changelog in Github or F-droid, only at google (more or less). Why? It should be included in the &quot;readme&quot; file or better in a separate changelog file, shouldn't it? And by using the &quot;changelog&quot; function in qksms itself I never know if this content is gathered from any server (thus is beeing up-to-date) or if it is only the date of the app included? Furthermore in the changelog-screen there should be noted, which version currently is installed. Otherwise I then have to go to settings--&gt;About to see the current version, have to remeber what the &quot;changelog-screen&quot; told me and not really know, If already any new version is out, as there is no timestamp in the changelog-screen, when it was updated.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="167">
			<summary>[bug] app Force Closes when setting a conversation on silent.</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/414</url>
			<bugID>Issue #414</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Recorded the crash here: https://gfycat.com/MintyFineAdder This happens to any conversation I try to set &quot;Silent&quot; to, and only Silent, any other kind of sound works. Android version : 5.1.1 Galaxy S6 (SM-G920F) 😕 1
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="168">
			<summary>[BUG] empty screen after: new SMS --&gt; Click at lockscreen notification --&gt; read SMS --&gt; tap &quot;back&quot; arrow</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/415</url>
			<bugID>Issue #415</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		DESCRIPTION --&gt; Receiving a new SMS --&gt; Clicking at the lockscreen notification --&gt; reading SMS --&gt; go &quot;back&quot; with the app-intern or system-back arrow --&gt; empty screen appears with &quot;conversations&quot; in the title, nothing more --&gt; qksms needs to be killed in the android task manager and to be restartet Just noticed for current v2.5.3 (at Android 5.1)
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="169">
			<summary>Message Options not accessible</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/417</url>
			<bugID>Issue #417</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		DESCRIPTION Message options are not a accessible when message SMS message contains a hyperlink or a phone number. STEPS Open a conversation. Long press a message containing a hyperlink or phone number. EXPECTED Popup box containing message options should appear. OBSERVATIONS No message option dialog appears. No indication that it is accessible.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="170">
			<summary>Conversation is blank after selecting from the search Result</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/419</url>
			<bugID>Issue #419</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		DESCRIPTION Conversation is blank after selecting from the search Result. STEPS Search a message Select from any of the result EXPECTED After selecting the conversation is blank OBSERVATIONS It looks like the conversation wasn't selected because if you try to reply it will tell you that you need some contacts to send the message..
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="171">
			<summary>Telephone number link to contact with different format</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/423</url>
			<bugID>Issue #423</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		DESCRIPTION Using different format for number (#) when sending a SMS create different conversations and won't display contact (name and picture). (french number format) STEPS French gsm number looks like: +33 6 XX XX XX XX Register a contact (yourself for example) with in this format: +33 6 XX XX XX XX and set a contact picture. Send a sms to 06 XX XX XX XX Send a sms to 33 6 XX XX XX XX (without &quot;+&quot;) Send a sms to the contact by choosing him directly EXPECTED Only one conversation with the name of the contact and his picture. OBSERVATIONS The result is one conversation without picture and named with the number 06XXXXXXXX containing SMS from step 1 and 3. And another conversation without picture and with named with the number 336XXXXXXXX containing the sms from step 2. When clicking on conversation picture, both are well linked to the contact.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="172">
			<summary>Upload latest source files to crowdin</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/425</url>
			<bugID>Issue #425</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		@moezbhatti Hi moez Can you please upload latest source file to crowdin? I´ve seen some changes in source file that were not uploaded to crowdin. And subsequently merge latest changes to source code. I´ts been a while since you merged strings. As you stated in readme file, pull requests will not be accepted so please before any release do a merge with source code.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="173">
			<summary>Sent message is described as &quot;sending...&quot;</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/431</url>
			<bugID>Issue #431</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Hello, all my messages keep &quot;sending...&quot;, even after delivery do recipent see attached picture if you know how to fix it, please let me know regards Bartek
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="174">
			<summary>Test issue</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/434</url>
			<bugID>Issue #434</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		DESCRIPTION A short description of the issue. Example: Conversations aren't marked as read when they are opened from a notification. STEPS Steps to reproduce the issue. EXPECTED Describe the expected behaviour. OBSERVATIONS Describe what happens instead of the expected behaviour.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="175">
			<summary>Switching conversation after orientation switch</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/437</url>
			<bugID>Issue #437</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		DESCRIPTION This looks like two orientation modes are independent: qksms remember last opened conversation is landscape mode and returns to it from any other conversation when rotating from portrait mode also: after this switch conversations have wrong title (from another conversation) STEPS rotate to landscape mode open a conversation A http://i.imgur.com/K4vfZw9.jpg close conversation A rotate to portrait mode open conversation B (http://i.imgur.com/6HMd1ml.jpg) rotate to landscape mode -- u can see conversation A with wrong title: http://i.imgur.com/g10Pmxr.jpg rotate back to portrait mode. Here we have again conversation B, but with same wrong title: http://i.imgur.com/a1u11hl.jpg EXPECTED No changes between landscape and portrait modes OBSERVATIONS conversation switches to another and changes conversation title (from some another conversation) I have 2.5.4 version of qksms from f-droid repo
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="176">
			<summary>Sending group messages while connected to wifi not working</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/440</url>
			<bugID>Issue #440</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		DESCRIPTION When sending group messages while I am connected to Wifi the messages just get stuck on &quot;sending&quot;. I have the &quot;Automatic data&quot; option turned on. This happened on my Galaxy S4 (5.0.1) and now my new Galaxy S7 (Marshmallow). I am on Verizon Wireless. STEPS Connect to Wifi Send group message Turning off wifi before sending the message or rebooting after trying usually gets the message to go through. EXPECTED The message to go through immediately without any problems. OBSERVATIONS The message hangs on &quot;sending&quot;. I usually then try turning off my wifi and waiting to see if it goes through. If it doesn't I will reboot my phone then it usually goes.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="177">
			<summary>Update translations</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/441</url>
			<bugID>Issue #441</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		No description provided.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="178">
			<summary>Update to new version of Travis</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/442</url>
			<bugID>Issue #442</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		https://blog.travis-ci.com/2014-12-17-faster-builds-with-container-based-infrastructure/
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="179">
			<summary>Marking conversations as read from notification doesn't dismiss notifications.</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/444</url>
			<bugID>Issue #444</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		DESCRIPTION Marking conversations as read via &quot;Read&quot; button in a notification sometimes doesn't dismiss the notification. todo: this only doesn't work sometimes. need to figure out when it doesn't work. it does work, for example, if i send a message to myself and mark that message as read from a notification. possible cases: if there was an unread message above the new message if the message above the new message wasn't from you STEPS Have Android 5.0 Lollipop Get a notification for an SMS Press &quot;Read&quot; EXPECTED The messaged is marked as read and the notification is dismissed. OBSERVATIONS The notification isn't dismissed.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="180">
			<summary>[Request] Show name under messages in group texts</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/445</url>
			<bugID>Issue #445</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Hi, I've noticed that in group texts it doesn't show the name of the person who sent the message most of the time (it seems like it's normally just the last message received). If I click on the message to view more details it will show the number of who it is from but not their name. Sometimes under the message it will show the time it was received and the contact who sent it (again, I think it's just the last received message). Would it be possible to make this show up for all messages in group texts? Sometimes I will receive multiple messages so I wont know who sent what. Thank you and keep up the good word! This is by far my favorite messaging app I've ever used!
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="181">
			<summary>[BUG] Not possible to select message with a URL or phone number</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/448</url>
			<bugID>Issue #448</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		DESCRIPTION I'm not able to select with long press an SMS with a URL link or a phone number inside. STEPS Check a SMS with a link or phone number in the content. Example: SMS Content = &quot;Check this https://www.reddit.com/r/QKSMS/&quot;. Pressing the message open the link (OK). Long press on the message doesn't have any effect (KO). EXPECTED A long press on the message should open the classic &quot;Message option&quot; menu. OBSERVATIONS A long press on a message with a link or phone number in content doesn't have any effect. (sorry if duplicated or not a bug, I'm new here)
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="182">
			<summary>QKSMS calling last conversation opened by itself</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/452</url>
			<bugID>Issue #452</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		DESCRIPTION When app is left in a conversation and screen is turned off, QKSMS often calls the person of the conversation. A reboot seems to fix this issue temporarily STEPS Open a conversation Send or receive message (Not sure if necessary step) Lock your phone with the conversation still opened With screen turned off, sometimes the phone starts to call the person by itself EXPECTED Not calling anyone without pressing the call button OBSERVATIONS Phone is calling people while in pocket, on desk, etc... (Without touching it)
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="183">
			<summary>Battery drain/wakelock from MMS</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/456</url>
			<bugID>Issue #456</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Android 5.1.1 (stock Nexus6) QKSMS 2.5.4 http://imgur.com/a/H4YpD Not sure what exactly is causing it but I've included screenshots of: Battery stats page Detailed battery stats for QKSMS App Info WLD info page showing MMS Connectivity being the culprit MMS settings page I can't be certain of when this started. I don't pay too close attention to these things and just happened to notice that QKSMS was riding pretty high on the battery usage when I happened to look today. I get MMS messages just fine and rarely ever send them myself but I have had ZERO issues sending or receiving MMS. I'm on wifi usually. Things I will try in the mean time while you look into the issue... Disable AFWall Reset all QKSMS settings and user data Beyond that, I don't know what else externally would be affecting it.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="184">
			<summary>[Idea] make an API to send sms</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/459</url>
			<bugID>Issue #459</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Hi, What i want to do ? I want to sync my sms and send some with a 3rd party open source website. How ? I see that you already support the Yappi API. So we can use this API and just change the URL that you use to sync. You can defined anything you want and be a standard. (The easiest) You can make something to authorize local app to send sms. Because they can access to other info. Regards,
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="185">
			<summary>Message details miss spaces in italian</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/466</url>
			<bugID>Issue #466</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		DESCRIPTION Message details miss spaces in italian so they result bad formatted. STEPS You must have italian language on your phone. Enter in a conversation Press long a message Choose &quot;view details&quot; (obviously, in italian is &quot;mostra dettagli&quot;) EXPECTED Message details have spaces between the type of informations and the informations. ITA (the wrong one) ENG (the right one) OBSERVATIONS Must add a space.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="186">
			<summary>Long Messages not sending as MMS</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/467</url>
			<bugID>Issue #467</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		DESCRIPTION When I send long messages, I had been under the idea that they were sending as MMS, but as SMS. STEPS Make a message longer than 160 characters (I sent a message that had as many characters as 4 individual SMS messages. Hit send Check recipient phone The messages sent as individual SMS messages. EXPECTED I expected to see the messages sent as one long MMS, but instead it sent as individual messages. OBSERVATIONS I made sure that all settings pertaining to long messages were enabled (under general, and MMS) and unlimited MMS attachment. I'm willing to give more information if you would like to know anything.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="187">
			<summary>show timestamps for all messages</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/468</url>
			<bugID>Issue #468</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		A lot of messages don't show timestamps. It's quite randomly. Some just show a timestamp and some don't. I can always get the timestamp via long-press -&gt; details. But I'd prefer to see the timestamp for every message directly.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="188">
			<summary>Threat of cash with NoClassDefFoundError on Samsung devices</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/474</url>
			<bugID>Issue #474</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Dear developers of qksms, I am a student majoring in Computer Science. We are trying to use existing bug reports and fixes of bugs caused by specific devices to help detect and fix similar bugs of other active applications. We have detected that in your app, method setSupportActionBar of android support library v7 is used in com.moez.QKSMS.ui.base.QKActivity: void reloadToolbar(). However, we have observed that invoking this method on some Samsung devices running 4.2 system will crash your app. We have found discussions in in the bug tracking system of Android: here. as well as a stack overflow question: appcompat-v7 v21.0.0 causing crash on Samsung devices with Android v4.2.2 A suggested fix for it is to add -keep class !android.support.v7.internal.view.menu.**,** {*;} to the proguard rules. Thank you vey much. Hope this information is useful for you.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="189">
			<summary>mistake</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/479</url>
			<bugID>Issue #479</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		No description provided.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="190">
			<summary>Dual SIM Support</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/480</url>
			<bugID>Issue #480</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		This is a very beautiful app and i hope dual sim support will come out soon...
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="191">
			<summary>noAnalytics now requires crashlytics</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/484</url>
			<bugID>Issue #484</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		See https://f-droid.org/wiki/page/com.moez.QKSMS/lastbuild_128: QKSMS/src/main/java/com/moez/QKSMS/ui/messagelist/MessageListActivity.java:11: error: package com.crashlytics.android does not exist
import com.crashlytics.android.Crashlytics;
                              ^
 This was when building the noAnalytics flavour, with all the analytics dependency lines from build.gradle removed. Seems pretty obvious, as this file is in src/main/java.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="192">
			<summary>Option to forward SMS</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/486</url>
			<bugID>Issue #486</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		As in topic. Could you please try to add forward option on holding the message for example?
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="193">
			<summary>Crash when receiving delivery report</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/496</url>
			<bugID>Issue #496</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		DESCRIPTION Crash when receiving delivery report STEPS Sent SMS. ... waiting delivery confirmation ... BANG ! EXPECTED Simple: show the mark whithout crashing, done ! :-) OBSERVATIONS My english is not so good, sorry. &quot;I think&quot; when receiving SMS delivery reports app crash and stop. Said before &quot;I think&quot; cause precisely app crash at that moment, but when check the SMS shows the mark as delivered.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="194">
			<summary>Wrong visual effect going from MessageList to ConversationList</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/497</url>
			<bugID>Issue #497</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		DESCRIPTION Wrong visual effect when returning to conversations list. The windows rolls to the right but under shows desktop wallpapers, not conversation list, after conversation windows left the screen space it shows up conversation list again. STEPS Open conversation Return to conversation list. EXPECTED When rolling to the right the conversation windows (visual effect), it should show conversation list, not desktop wallpaper. OBSERVATIONS Wrong visual effect when returning to conversations list. The windows rolls to the right but under shows desktop wallpapers, not conversation list, after conversation windows left the screen space it shows up conversation list again.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="195">
			<summary>[Suggestion] The option &quot;Read&quot; in the popup should read &quot;Mark as read&quot;</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/504</url>
			<bugID>Issue #504</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		I'm not sure if it's because of me being weird or because I'm not a native English speaker. But I often press &quot;Read&quot; when I want to reply to the message, thinking &quot;read&quot; as in &quot;read the message&quot; not &quot;mark it as read&quot;. As a right handed person I naturally read the option closes to my thumb and not the first option to the left. If the option read &quot;Mark as read&quot; this wouldn't be a problem, at least not for me. :)
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="196">
			<summary>Random message receiver</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/509</url>
			<bugID>Issue #509</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		DESCRIPTION QKSMS 2.5.1 conversations are not always sent to the selected receiver. Sometimes they are send to someone else on the contact list. Have this been fixed (is this a duplicated issue then)? STEPS Use QKSMS for a longer period of time and you perhaps will notice this bug. EXPECTED The messages should go to the intended receiver only, of course. OBSERVATIONS Sometimes they are send to someone else on the contact list.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="197">
			<summary>Blocked conversations re-appear in Inbox</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/517</url>
			<bugID>Issue #517</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		DESCRIPTION Many times blocked conversations re-appear in the Inbox. I block the conversations, and they move from Inbox to &quot;Blocked&quot; view, and when I check again (after getting new SMS) they seem to be back in Inbox. Update: Just checked Qksms again, when there is no new SMS, and they are all back. STEPS Select a Conversation Select &quot;Block&quot; from top menu Conversation hides from Inbox EXPECTED Blocked conversation should never show up in Inbox again. OBSERVATIONS Some of the the blocked conversations creep back in Inbox.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="198">
			<summary>Contact pop-up opened by contact icon</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/518</url>
			<bugID>Issue #518</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		DESCRIPTION Open contact information from the contact icon STEPS Click on the icon contact (in QKSM home or in conversation) Click outside of the pop-up or on the android return button Now, for example, try to open another contact OBSERVATIONS Click outside of the contact pop-up makes QKSMS buggy until you do not close it (or stop focusing the app).Sometimes, when you use the return button to exit the app, contact pop-up appears
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="199">
			<summary>Delayed submission doesn't delay at all</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/520</url>
			<bugID>Issue #520</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		DESCRIPTION I have configured delayed submission for SMSes but they get submitted as soon as I hit the submission button (-&gt;). STEPS Go to settings--&gt;General Enable Delayed messages (wording could be different as I use Italian) Set delay in seconds to 5 or whatever else you want Go back to application main screen Type and Send an SMS to someone EXPECTED A delay to occur before the SMS submission is done OBSERVATIONS The SMS is sumbitted immediately I am running CyanogenMod 13.1-ZNK2K .
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="200">
			<summary>No notifications for Group Messages</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/521</url>
			<bugID>Issue #521</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		The text info is there, but there is no notification letting me know something new has come in. Everything is fine and normal with regular texts. This just seems to be a group text issue.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="201">
			<summary>No resource for '@integer/google_play_services_version'</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/523</url>
			<bugID>Issue #523</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Project is not build When trying to execute gradle build the project failed with this error &quot;:QKSMS:processNoAnalyticsDebugResources FAILED com.android.ide.common.process.ProcessException: org.gradle.process.internal.ExecException: Process 'command '/home/tomer/Android/sdk/build-tools/23.0.3/aapt'' finished with non-zero exit value 1&quot; /home/tomer/Downloads/qksms-master/QKSMS/build/intermediates/manifests/full/noAnalytics/debug/AndroidManifest.xml:528:28-65: AAPT: No resource found that matches the given name (at 'value' with value '')
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="202">
			<summary>**Feature** Emoticon Support</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/524</url>
			<bugID>Issue #524</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Are emoticons currently supported or is this a missing feature? It would be nice to have emoticon support like this : 😄 👍
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="203">
			<summary>[Feature Request] Batch edit a conversation</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/525</url>
			<bugID>Issue #525</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Hello, In top menu of a specific conversation, I think it could be use full to add an opion to batch edit. It would be easier to delete or lock multiple sms at once. When activating this 'mode' a check box need to appear in the same line of each sms/mms to allow to select or no this sms/mms At the bottom there could be other option like: invert selection, select all, unselect all and apply to selection with 2 options : lock or delete. In both case a popup should appear to ask confirmation (in case of deletion, you need to add a warning to prevent that it is irreversible) If locked sms are selected to be deleted add in the warning that x sms are locked and will be deleted. Thank you for QKsms :)
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="204">
			<summary>*UPDATE* Emoticons and test for skin tone support</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/526</url>
			<bugID>Issue #526</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Working on update to EmojiconHandler.java to match updated source file @ https://github.com/rockerhieu/emojicon/blob/master/library/src/main/java/com/rockerhieu/emojicon/EmojiconHandler.java Testing configuration to check for skin tone support. If not supported, work on implementing feature.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="205">
			<summary>Weird Transition from conversation to Message list / Inbox</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/529</url>
			<bugID>Issue #529</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		DESCRIPTION I tested on my Android 4.4.3 device and there is a weird transition when you exit(press back button) after reading a message it will show first the phone desktop/home page before going back to your inbox/message list This is the play store release recently.. STEPS Open a message then press back button Check this short video to see it clearly - https://s3.amazonaws.com/uploads.hipchat.com/191793/1367990/zaA37Ol78GsdwXS/VID_20160619_035153.mp4 EXPECTED It should go back smoothly to the inbox without showing the desktop screen for few seconds. OBSERVATIONS Transition is okay so for on other devices like Samsung Galaxy S3 and Nexus 6P
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="206">
			<summary>Notification coloring is hard to read.</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/532</url>
			<bugID>Issue #532</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Nexus 6, 5.1.1, stock, no funky fonts or anything. QKSMS v2.6.1 The icon, title of QKSMS, and the read/reply/call text are all difficult to read due to being white. Hangouts for example, uses a green icon, with green text. Gmail is red. Also, just as a visual improvement... if the contact does not have an icon associated or a number has no contact, I don't see why an icon should be displayed to the right (the blank white circle). Is it not possible to show a transparent icon there so as to look empty?
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="207">
			<summary>QK don't check Telephony.Sms.SEEN to display Notifications and ignore if it's the default SMS App</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/533</url>
			<bugID>Issue #533</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		DESCRIPTION QK don't check Telephony.Sms.SEEN column in order to display sms notifications QK it's not the default SMS App and an SMS arrive the device will display 2 notifications one for the Default SMS App and one for QK. Also if Default App mark as seen the SMS QK ignore that and display the notification. STEPS Use as Default SMS App one that mark as seen SMS (very simple demo will be enough) QK should NOT be the Default SMS App Receive an SMS Duplicated notifications in the device, one for Default SMS App and one for QK EXPECTED QK should take care of SEEN Sms value in order to display notifications OBSERVATIONS Not sure if an SMS app it's not the default one, should display any notification at all, but for sure should check seen value. Other SMS App Like native one(LG, Samsung, etc...) don't display notifications if they are not the default SMS App
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="208">
			<summary>long messages are always splitted</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/535</url>
			<bugID>Issue #535</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		DESCRIPTION Long messages are splitted even if &quot;Split SMS&quot; option is disabled For information: I use a GS4 on KitKat (4.4.2) issue is not observed on A5 Lollipop (5.1.1) STEPS Ensure that &quot;Split SMS&quot; is disabled Send a long sms from a GS4 Kitakt to a GS4mini GS4mini receives the long sms as one chunk Send again a long sms from A5 Lollipop to the same GS4mini GS4mini receives 4 sms (1/4, 2/4, ...) EXPECTED Sending long SMS as one chunk OBSERVATIONS long SMS is splitted when sent from a GS4 Kitkat long SMS is not splitted when sent from A5 Lollipop (5.1.1)
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="209">
			<summary>Auto delete old messages</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/537</url>
			<bugID>Issue #537</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		DESCRIPTION This is an enhancement suggestion to implement a function which automatically deletes messages which are too old (the threshold should be settable) or if message count threshold is reached in a conversation (&quot;only keep last X messages&quot;).
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="210">
			<summary>Stage fright?</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/551</url>
			<bugID>Issue #551</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		When receiving videos, I get a message about stage fright. I understand this is an exploit in the stage fright lib, and has to do with automatic rendering of videos in messages. So what exactly should I do? Just not play any videos I receive? Can we detect whether the message contains the stage fright though?
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="211">
			<summary>It'd be great if QKSMS had an option to keep resending failed SMSs</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/552</url>
			<bugID>Issue #552</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		A feature request, because the signal in my flat can be very temperamental!
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="212">
			<summary>Enter button Not working when set to 'send message' function</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/554</url>
			<bugID>Issue #554</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		DESCRIPTION Enter button always function as &quot;new line&quot; even if you set it to &quot;send&quot; STEPS Change function of 'enter button' of the keyboard from 'new line' to 'send message'. Type message and send your messsage via enter button of the keyboard it will give you new line instead of sending. EXPECTED It should send the message if you set it to send OBSERVATIONS The function of enter button is always new line whatever setting you choose.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="213">
			<summary>change deprecated setOnPageChangeListener</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/556</url>
			<bugID>Issue #556</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		DESCRIPTION hi in WelcomeActivity you can change deprecated mPager.setOnPageChangeListener(this); to mPager.addOnPageChangeListener(this); also in every textview you can change android:singleLine=&quot;true&quot; to android:lines=&quot;1&quot; reference link: http://stackoverflow.com/questions/30867852/viewpager-setonpagechangelistener-deprecated
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="214">
			<summary>Option to update QKSMS icon to theme color</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/558</url>
			<bugID>Issue #558</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		This is a feature request. I do like the new design but I feel there is much more potential of it. Is it at all possible to add an option to do this please? Also I have noticed that on the dark icon it appears black on my home screen but in my app drawer it is a dark grey and is pretty hard to catch my attention to it. Thanks.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="215">
			<summary>QKSMS 3.0</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/565</url>
			<bugID>Issue #565</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		No description provided.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="216">
			<summary>Finish migrating preference constants to QKPreference enum</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/566</url>
			<bugID>Issue #566</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		No description provided.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="217">
			<summary>TransactionService.java , UnsupportedOperationException Exception</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/567</url>
			<bugID>Issue #567</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		In the file TransactionService.java, UnsupportedOperationException Exception occurs in the following method protected void endMmsConnectivity() { try { if (LOCAL_LOGV) Log.v(TAG, &quot;endMmsConnectivity&quot;);         // cancel timer for renewal of lease
        mServiceHandler.removeMessages(EVENT_CONTINUE_MMS_CONNECTIVITY);
        if (mConnMgr != null) {
            mConnMgr.stopUsingNetworkFeature(
                    ConnectivityManager.TYPE_MOBILE,
                    &quot;enableMMS&quot;);
        }
    }
        catch(UnsupportedOperationException hh)
        {

        }
    finally {
        releaseWakeLock();
    }
}
 mConnMgr.stopUsingNetworkFeature() is depricated as per android docs https://developer.android.com/reference/android/net/ConnectivityManager.html i Managed to workaround using catch the UnsupportedOperationException, but didn't handled the exception. My doubts is how to properly handle this exception.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="218">
			<summary>duplicate messages recieved on lg devices</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/568</url>
			<bugID>Issue #568</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		DESCRIPTION: with any message I have recived, two appear in the thread STEPS: try installing QK on an lg device to see if the bug happens with all lgs EXPECTED: Normally, when one recives a message, only one notification appears, and only one message appears in the thread. OBSERVATIONS: Instead of one message recieved, two appear, regardless of signal strength
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="219">
			<summary>Encoding UTF-8 has no effect</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/569</url>
			<bugID>Issue #569</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		DESCRIPTION build.gradle try to set encoding to UTF-8. But a mistake is in gradle file: compileOptions { compileOptions.encoding = &quot;UTF-8&quot; [...] } compileOptions is specified two times. Moreover, UTF-8 is the default encoding charset, so it is not usefull to specify it.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="220">
			<summary>为什么我不能Fork 代码</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/570</url>
			<bugID>Issue #570</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		我有个想法,想添加一个功能,但是代码下载下来不能用,一直编译不能通过,这时为什么
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="221">
			<summary>Sometimes crashes when opening physical keyboard</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/571</url>
			<bugID>Issue #571</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		DESCRIPTION My device is the HTC Desire Z which has a physical keyboard, and I'm running CM11 (Android 4.4.4). QKSMS has been a welcome upgrade to the standard SMS app. My only real issue is that when I run the app with the keyboard closed, and open the keyboard at any time, QKSMS sometimes crashes. STEPS Start QKSMS on a phone with a physical keyboard with the keyboard closed. Open the keyboard at any subscreen (the main message list, a conversation, etc) EXPECTED I hope that it would not crash. OBSERVATIONS QKSMS hesitates to shift from portrait to landscape, and then crashes. It does not always happen, and I've found that I encounter the issue more &quot;in the wild&quot; than when I try to randomly test it by opening and closing.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="222">
			<summary>Permissions FLASHLIGHT and CAMERA seem not used</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/593</url>
			<bugID>Issue #593</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		DESCRIPTION The Intent MediaStore.ACTION_IMAGE_CAPTURE (android.media.action.IMAGE_CAPTURE) already does taking-photo when user wants to send a photo MMS. Permissions android.permission.CAMERA and android.permission.FLASHLIGHT seem not necessary. To be removed perhaps. STEPS EXPECTED OBSERVATIONS
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="223">
			<summary>Chat history doesn't show up on Android Wear</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/595</url>
			<bugID>Issue #595</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		DESCRIPTION When a new message comes, chat history does not show up on the watch. STEPS Connect an Android Wear watch to the phone. Send a message to the phone. EXPECTED The chat history is shown on the second page of the notification on watch. OBSERVATIONS An empty page.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="224">
			<summary>chat history does not show up on Android Wear</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/596</url>
			<bugID>Issue #596</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		DESCRIPTION When a new message comes, chat history does not show up on the watch. STEPS Connect an Android Wear watch to the phone. Send a message to the phone. EXPECTED The chat history is shown on the second page of the notification on watch. OBSERVATIONS An empty page.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="225">
			<summary>REQUEST: Ability to send SMS and MMS over Wifi to other QKSMS users</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/597</url>
			<bugID>Issue #597</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		A feature request: I would like the ability to send SMS and MMS over Wifi to other QKSMS users. This would be especially useful for tablets with no telephony connection.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="226">
			<summary>I always receive two same message at one time when i set qksms as my default sms app.</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/600</url>
			<bugID>Issue #600</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		DESCRIPTION A short description of the issue. Example: Conversations aren't marked as read when they are opened from a notification. STEPS Steps to reproduce the issue. EXPECTED Describe the expected behaviour. OBSERVATIONS Describe what happens instead of the expected behaviour.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="227">
			<summary>DrmUtils' utility? (aka what does it do)</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/601</url>
			<bugID>Issue #601</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		DrmUtils is evoked in MessageUtils and deals with Ringtones. Guess is it is a remnant of when carriers controlled Ringtones. Is ringtone DRM still used/necessary in 2016? Please update as to what DRM does in an SMS application. Thank you!
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="228">
			<summary>The attached images will not be displayed</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/603</url>
			<bugID>Issue #603</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		When editing a new message, attached images are not displayed.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="229">
			<summary>Remove messages by quantity</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/606</url>
			<bugID>Issue #606</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Add enhancement to have messages auto deleted by quantity as opposed to by date.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="230">
			<summary>Request: SIP SIMPLE message</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/624</url>
			<bugID>Issue #624</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		In addition to #207 it is best to add SIP message as well. Only voip.ms from playstore that have apps only for SIP text. But it tight to only voip.ms service. Maybe if you kind enough to add SIP message support it would be wonderful. There are lot of voip apps that can do SIP messaging but it is not focus on message. Like csipsimple and zoiper for an example, it is bad for organizing message. A lot of people love the built-in android SIP, but limited only to SIP call. As more people use SIP, the need of android SIP SIMPLE companion is rise. The SIP address can be taken from &quot;Internet Call&quot; field in contacts, and SIP settings can be taken from android SIP settings. No need for presence or file transfer or whatever fancy text like WA. But pure Text like SMS.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="231">
			<summary>MMS taken from Camera does not take into account MAX_MMS_ATTACHMENT_SIZE</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/628</url>
			<bugID>Issue #628</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		DESCRIPTION MMS taken from Camera does not take into account MAX_MMS_ATTACHMENT_SIZE. While MMS picked from Gallery takes into account MAX_MMS_ATTACHMENT_SIZE. This causes sending MMS taken from Camera to fail when the size is too big. In QKSMS 2.7.3 STEPS Launch QKSMS Set MAX_MMS_ATTACHMENT_SIZE to 300KB (default value) in Settings Send MMS from taking from Camera MMS not sent, failed EXPECTED MMS taken from Camera takes into account MAX_MMS_ATTACHMENT_SIZE. And MMS can be sent successfully. OBSERVATIONS Described above.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="232">
			<summary>Marking one message as read causes all QKSMS notifications to disappear</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/631</url>
			<bugID>Issue #631</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		DESCRIPTION When having notifications for more than one thread/message/contact, marking one of them as read from notification causes all notifications to disappear. STEPS receive &gt;2 messages from separate contacts; 2 notifications are displayed; select one of them in the notifications and from the expanded actions choose 'mark as read' EXPECTED Single message is marked as read and other notifications persists; OBSERVATIONS All notifications from QKSMS are gone
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="233">
			<summary>Notification Reply Sent to incorrect recipient Android Nougat</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/639</url>
			<bugID>Issue #639</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		DESCRIPTION When you receive SMS messages from a lot of persons and they stack up in your notifications (on your lock screen). If you answer to the last visible SMS through the lock screen notification, the SMS will be sent to the incorrect person (i.e. the last received SMS) STEPS Receive a lot of SMS messages. Lock your device. Try to answer the last visible SMS received. Unlock your device. Go see in the QKSMS app to view the SMS sent to the incorrect person. This happens on Android Nougat (7.0). Not sure if it happens with the other versions EXPECTED The SMS should be sent to the correct person. OBSERVATIONS The SMS answer is sent to the last SMS received instead of the last visible SMS.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="234">
			<summary>Enter button: when send 2 sending indicator shown</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/643</url>
			<bugID>Issue #643</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		DESCRIPTION Enter button set to send message. When you send using keyboard enter button, 2 &quot;sending..&quot; indicator are shown. STEPS Go to Settings&gt; General&gt; Enter button &gt; Send message Go to any conversation and try to send message but send using the keyboard enter button. EXPECTED Only 1 sending indicator.. OBSERVATIONS When you send message using keyboard enter button two message will send. First one is your real message and second one is just a empty message.. It shows 2 sending... indicator. QKSMS APP MESSAGING APP
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="235">
			<summary>High MB pictures not sending</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/647</url>
			<bugID>Issue #647</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		DESCRIPTION I am using a Verison Moto X Pure, MMS will not send on 21mp setting STEPS Take photo full resolution try and send it EXPECTED hangings in &quot;sending&quot; OBSERVATIONS hangs in &quot;sending&quot; and never sends photo
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="236">
			<summary>[Bug] Notification LED color keep changing back to purple</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/651</url>
			<bugID>Issue #651</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Is it happen to anyone? I set my notification LED color to blue but somehow QKSMS keep changing it back to purple after few days.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="237">
			<summary>Random texts sent</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/652</url>
			<bugID>Issue #652</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Turned off airplane mode this morning and 3 very old texts were resent to 3 different people (2 starred, 1 not starred) Tried to reproduce the issue but couldn't... Just don't want it to keep happening as it was very early in the morning. Just installed QKSMS yesterday. Love it other than this issue happening.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="238">
			<summary>Crash when opening new SMS or scroll in widget</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/662</url>
			<bugID>Issue #662</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Hi, Today, QKSMS crashed, and since this it crashes if I open a conversation with a new SMS received (or when receiving an SMS with the conversation already opened), or when I scroll down/up on the widget. I rebooted the phone multiple times but it persists. Tried to clear the cache of the application. I have no idea why it crashed in the first place, so I don't know how to reproduce it. I'm gonna reinstall it. I copied the /data/data/com.moez.QKSMS directory just in case it could be useful. I use the latest version from F-droid (2.7.3). (Reinstall &quot;corrected&quot; the bug, just lost the custom color for app icon)
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="239">
			<summary>Multi-line message should be aligned right</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/663</url>
			<bugID>Issue #663</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		If a messages takes only one line, the container doesn't fill width and is aligned right. If a message takes more than one line, the container takes full width and the text is aligned left. It should be aligned right in the container. If you give me some hint, I can make a pull request. I don't have much experience with the Android platform but have programmed a little in JavaFX.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="240">
			<summary>Does QKSMS support TeslaUnread API?</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/666</url>
			<bugID>Issue #666</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Does QKSMS support the TeslaUnread API? - http://novalauncher.com/teslaunread-api/
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="241">
			<summary>Capturing an image from app directly does not attach</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/667</url>
			<bugID>Issue #667</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		DESCRIPTION I have the same issue on two phones. Both are using the latest version of qksms from the app store. The picture seems to take but I'm returned to a blank text message box STEPS Open an existing conversation Click the arrow button on the blank message Click the camera icon Take a picture You are returned to a blank message with no attachment EXPECTED The image taken with your default camera application should be attached to the new mms message OBSERVATIONS Absolutely nothing happens. The image isn't vanishes.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="242">
			<summary>Wrong Identified Phone Number</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/668</url>
			<bugID>Issue #668</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		DESCRIPTION I received a SMS caontainig: &quot;18h45-19h&quot; And &quot;45-19&quot; is show as a phone number wich is not the case. The first Idea could be a phone number is always beetween 2 spaces &quot; &quot; (e.g. &quot;Please contact 202-555-0191 around 18h45-19h) Spaces could be replace by linebreak or non litteral chars as &quot;(&quot;, &quot;[&quot; etc... Note that looking for a solution I found this topic; http://stackoverflow.com/questions/123559/a-comprehensive-regex-for-phone-number-validation wich make me check https://github.com/googlei18n/libphonenumber I think this could be a valid alternative to the current system: check all list of number and then ask for isPossibleNumber or isValidNumber Ideally people could (in preference) select which country number they want to use (but maybe this is a bit useless) STEPS Send yoursel a SMS containing &quot;18h45-19h&quot; EXPECTED No one number format should be observable (and no clickable action) OBSERVATIONS &quot;45-19&quot; is interpreted as a phone number
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="243">
			<summary>How to remove the sms and mms filelds in andriod studio</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/675</url>
			<bugID>Issue #675</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		i want to make my own app using this open....i don't have much knowledge about the apps,,, can you please tell me hoe to remove the messages place and keep as blank.So that i can build it different as i want.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="244">
			<summary>Wish: another icon for this app</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/676</url>
			<bugID>Issue #676</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		I configure Android-phones for other people. And install QKSMS, But everytime, I give them their phone back, they complain about that Q-icon, which does not tell them anything about an SMS-app ....
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="245">
			<summary>Previous Message Windows Don't Close</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/680</url>
			<bugID>Issue #680</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		DESCRIPTION All pervious message windows stay open. After you are done replying hitting the back button takes you to the last person or persons you have been texting, not the main list. You must keep hitting back until you close out all previous recent replies to get to message list. STEPS Reply to mutiple different people from the notification pull down. Hit home button Open qksms EXPECTED The last message window you sent should now be displayed. Hit back once and it should take you to the main messges list. OBSERVATIONS The last message window you sent should now be displayed. Hit back until you get to the message list. The first back press will open the second to last person you sent to, the 2nd press will take you to the third person you sent to etc. Until you get to message list. 👍 2
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="246">
			<summary>Auto append short code link to sent sms</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/683</url>
			<bugID>Issue #683</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Hi I would like to auto append a short code link to all sent messages. Could someone help me with this please? Thank you all in advance Eric
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="247">
			<summary>Unable to view old messages</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/684</url>
			<bugID>Issue #684</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		DESCRIPTION I am using the APP on Moto E3 POWER, though everything is working fine but I am unable to see old messages in the conversation. For example, at the home screen it is shown 11 messages in the conversation, but if I open the conversation I only get to see 4 messages. I have tried to search for options in setting but couldn't get anything. STEPS Messeage counter shows 11 messages in conversation But only 4 are shown if conversation is opened EXPECTED All the conversations should be shown. OBSERVATIONS Only a few recent dated conversations are show, and old messages are not shown
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="248">
			<summary>Feature: configure number of lines displayed when writing text</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/686</url>
			<bugID>Issue #686</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		DESCRIPTION When I write a text, only three lines of text are displayed. EXPECTED When I write a long text, this happens frequently with my so, I would like to be able to see more than three lines. As an example, chompSMS is displaying 8 lines of text. chompSMS is not open source. Now I have a 5.5 inches screen, and 3 lines are too small on my screen, even when keyboard is displayed, there is plenty of space to display more than 3 lines. I would love to be able to see more, whatever the way it is implemented, either an option stating the number of lines, or an option saying 50% lines from past messages and 50% for the message I am currently writing.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="249">
			<summary>MMS can not be sent or received on version 2.7.3</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/687</url>
			<bugID>Issue #687</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		DESCRIPTION MMS can not be sent or received STEPS Download version 2.7.3 of QKSMS from Google Play Try to send or receive MMS EXPECTED MMS can be sent and received correctly OBSERVATIONS MMS can not be sent or received.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="250">
			<summary>Flashing &quot;Recent Apps&quot; Screen bug</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/688</url>
			<bugID>Issue #688</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		DESCRIPTION When the &quot;Home Screen&quot; button (circle) is pressed, the animation stutters and briefly flashes the &quot;Recent Apps&quot; screen. STEPS From any screen in the QKSMS app, press the &quot;Recent Apps&quot; button (square) From the &quot;Recent Apps&quot; screen, go back into the QKSMS app Now press the &quot;Home Screen&quot; button (circle) You will see the animation stutter and the &quot;Recent Apps&quot; screen briefly flash before going home (really brief!) EXPECTED A fluid animation back to the home screen OBSERVATIONS The animation to go back home is jerky due to a bug that briefly flashes the &quot;Recent Apps&quot; screen
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="251">
			<summary>Travis build for the app is failing.</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/692</url>
			<bugID>Issue #692</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		DESCRIPTION The travis build for the app is failing even if the PR is fine. This is because google has changed the names of certain ABIs. STEPS Create a PR and it will fail. EXPECTED The build should not fail for legitimate PRs. I suggest updating the travis.yml file. If that is done the travis build will not fail for legitimate PRs.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="252">
			<summary>Cannot select who to send message to when started from &quot;new text message&quot; Intent</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/695</url>
			<bugID>Issue #695</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		When I pick a shortcut on my home screen or come from an app (such as blackberry hub for android) for &quot;new text message&quot; it open QKSMS (since it is my default SMS app) and lets me type a message, but the box for selecting who to send the message to is not shown so I cannot actually send the message.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="253">
			<summary>Dual Sim support</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/696</url>
			<bugID>Issue #696</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		DESCRIPTION I wish there was an option to select the sim on long press on send button so that user can select the sim to send as in Stock messaging app.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="254">
			<summary>Delete in Notification</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/697</url>
			<bugID>Issue #697</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Hello, It would be possible to add a &quot;DELETE&quot; button in the notification instead of &quot;Mark as read&quot; or &quot;Open&quot;. Thank you!
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="255">
			<summary>Messages can't be send</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/698</url>
			<bugID>Issue #698</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		DESCRIPTION Replies to received messages &quot;fail to send&quot;. On wifi. 5 bars mobile 3G reception. STEPS Write reply to received message Push &quot;Send&quot; Pop up: &quot;Failed to send&quot; Exclamation mark next to failed message Retry x times EXPECTED The message should go out. When staying put (same location) and Copying the message text in the Android stock messenger app the SMS gets send without any issue first time. OBSERVATIONS See supra Samsung S6 - all up to date
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="256">
			<summary>SMS Deletion problems</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/700</url>
			<bugID>Issue #700</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		When i try to delete message the app display the notification for &quot;set app to default app&quot; for deleting messages. Its worst thing i seen on the app. I suggest you to fix this issue. The app allows to send, receive messages but not deletion.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="257">
			<summary>Backup and Restore</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/701</url>
			<bugID>Issue #701</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Add backup and restore option in app. Now days mostly all apps provide the backup and restore feature. Add a feature to allow user to backup messages on Google account, G Drive, External Storage or Email.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="258">
			<summary>Show sender images with messages</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/702</url>
			<bugID>Issue #702</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Add feature to show images of senders with messages. For Eg:
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="259">
			<summary>change app icons</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/704</url>
			<bugID>Issue #704</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		DESCRIPTION The current icons of app are relates with Q but i think there is need to change the icons. EXPECTED Design and add new material designed icons for app.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="260">
			<summary>Feature request: Mark message as unread</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/706</url>
			<bugID>Issue #706</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Honestly why doesn't any sms application have this? This is super important. I don't want to forget messages that I want to read but can't answer at the moment. I want other people to have this feature so they don't forget about my messages. This should be priority one to implement. 👍 1
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="261">
			<summary>&quot;enter&quot; sends sms doesnt work</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/711</url>
			<bugID>Issue #711</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		DESCRIPTION Changing the enter button behaviour to &quot;send message&quot; directly after installing the app worked. However after using the app for x days this funtionality vanished even if the setting didn't change. So even when &quot;send&quot; is selected pressing enter just will result in a new line. STEPS Steps to reproduce the issue. EXPECTED Describe the expected behaviour. OBSERVATIONS Describe what happens instead of the expected behaviour.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="262">
			<summary>Wishlist: &quot;Convert&quot; SMS to MMS</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/712</url>
			<bugID>Issue #712</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Sprint is a terrible carrier, and the latest wave of issues affecting certain customers prevents the sending of SMS messages, but not MMS messages, when on connected to LTE. Receipt works correctly, though. Certain proprietary messaging applications (e.g. &quot;YAATA&quot;) allow you to send an &quot;empty&quot; MMS message containing the text that would otherwise be sent as an SMS message.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="263">
			<summary>Performance improvement suggestion</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/718</url>
			<bugID>Issue #718</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Dear developers, When loading images, Google suggests us to cache the bitmaps that can be reused, so as to keep a fluid and fast-loading UI. https://developer.android.com/topic/performance/graphics/cache-bitmap.html &quot;...... in order to keep a fluid and fast-loading UI you want to avoid continually processing these images each time they come back on-screen. A memory and disk cache can often help here, allowing components to quickly reload processed images.&quot; However, in the code of QKSMS, bitmap caching is not applied: (1) com.moez.QKSMS.data.Contact.java getAvatar() https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/blob/master/QKSMS/src/main/java/com/moez/QKSMS/data/Contact.java#L352 I found getAvatar() is invoked directly by: com.moez.QKSMS.ui.dialog.conversationdetails.ConversationDetailsContactListAdapter.java getView() https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/blob/master/QKSMS/src/main/java/com/moez/QKSMS/ui/dialog/conversationdetails/ConversationDetailsContactListAdapter.java#L38 (2) com.moez.QKSMS.common.utils.ImageUtils.java getCircleBitmap() https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/blob/master/QKSMS/src/main/java/com/moez/QKSMS/common/utils/ImageUtils.java#L47 I found getCircleBitmap() is invoked by: com.moez.QKSMS.ui.view.AvatarView.java setImageWhenReady() and setImageDrawable() is invoked by: com.moez.QKSMS.ui.view.AvatarView.java setImageDrawable() setImageDrawable() is invoked by: com.moez.QKSMS.ui.dialog.conversationdetails.ConversationDetailsContactListAdapter.java getView() getView() callbacks are frequently invoked in the UI thread and this means that there will be many bitmap objects being created if we not define a cache to store them. For performance considerations, maybe we can define memory cache and disk memory cache to store the bitmap objects. Then app can reuse them instead of creating new bitmap objects continuously. In addition, since image decoding is slow, we can perform these operations in worker threads (e.g., via AsyncTask). Thanks.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="264">
			<summary>Decoding image without resizing</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/719</url>
			<bugID>Issue #719</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Dear developers, When loading an image, Google suggests us to resize the image before decoding them, so as to save memory resource and avoid OutOfMemory exception. https://developer.android.com/topic/performance/graphics/load-bitmap.html &quot; To avoid java.lang.OutOfMemory exceptions, check the dimensions of a bitmap before decoding it, unless you absolutely trust the source to provide you with predictably sized image data that comfortably fits within the available memory &quot; I noticed that in the following code of QKSMS, image resizing is correctly applied: com.moez.QKSMS.common.google.ThumbnailManager.java requestDecode() (line number:) https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/blob/master/QKSMS/src/main/java/com/moez/QKSMS/common/google/ThumbnailManager.java#L474 com.moez.QKSMS.ui.view.ComposeView.java doInBackground() (line number: 919) https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/blob/master/QKSMS/src/main/java/com/moez/QKSMS/ui/view/ComposeView.java#L919 However, in the code below, images are decoded directly without resizing: (1) com.moez.QKSMS.data.Contact: android.graphics.drawable.Drawable.java getAvatar() (line number: 352) https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/blob/master/QKSMS/src/main/java/com/moez/QKSMS/data/Contact.java#L352 (2) com.moez.QKSMS.data.ContactHelper.java getBitmap() (line number: 186) https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/blob/master/QKSMS/src/main/java/com/moez/QKSMS/data/ContactHelper.java#L186 I am curious about the latter cases. Why these methods do not resize images? Are these images all of small sizes? Do you think they will affect QKSMS's performance? For the images to be displayed, in many cases, they are larger than required. Because the bitmap display in an app is memory consumption, maybe we should resize the images before decoding them, which can reduce memory overhead and help make app more smooth in user interaction. Thanks.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="265">
			<summary>Receiving each SMS twice</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/720</url>
			<bugID>Issue #720</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		DESCRIPTION Each SMS appears twice with version 2-7-3. Same thing on version 2-7-1 from fdroid like here #600
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="266">
			<summary>Back button</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/721</url>
			<bugID>Issue #721</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		It displays the desktop for a few seconds. When you press the back button (top left corner).
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="267">
			<summary>Call from conversation calls to &quot;null&quot;</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/723</url>
			<bugID>Issue #723</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		DESCRIPTION Call from conversation calls to incorrect number and contact called &quot;null&quot;. EXAMPLE Call from conversation does not go through because number is either incorrect or empty. This happens for some contacts, calling from some contacts works ok. STEPS Open conversation Press call/phone button Observe EXPECTED Calling to the conversation contact
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="268">
			<summary>MMS picture quality very poor</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/724</url>
			<bugID>Issue #724</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		DESCRIPTION Every MMS image I received is compressed to very low quality. I've gone into settings and set the Maximum MMS attachment size to unlimited which did not resolve it. STEPS Send picture message to my phone Examine quality of said picture message EXPECTED High quality or slightly lower quality images than the original. OBSERVATIONS Very low quality images. Image received through QKSMS image Image received through Samsungs sms app image
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="269">
			<summary>Removing other notifications</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/725</url>
			<bugID>Issue #725</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		DESCRIPTION All message notification get cleared when even one of them is swiped STEPS Receive a message from sender X Receive a message from sender Y Don't open the app Swipe the message notification from the notification shade for sender X to clear it Message from both the sender gets cleared from notification shade EXPECTED Notification from the person whose notification is swiped should be cleared only OBSERVATIONS Notification for all the message gets cleared
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="270">
			<summary>Back buttons doesn't always go back to conversation list</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/727</url>
			<bugID>Issue #727</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		DESCRIPTION When I press the built-in back button on my galaxy s5, it often goes to a different conversation rather than going back to the conversations list. I would imagine this is a bug, but if not, its not very intuitive behavior. STEPS Go to a conversation Press the built-in back button It seems like conversations are being put into a queue and popped off when you press the back button, but the behavior isn't clear enough to me to find a consistent repro. EXPECTED Pressing the built-in back button should go back to the conversations list. OBSERVATIONS It instead goes to some other conversation sometimes. This is version 2.7.3 👍 1
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="271">
			<summary>Can't send/receive MMS</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/731</url>
			<bugID>Issue #731</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		DESCRIPTION I have a S7 edge on Verizon Nougat 7.0. I can't receive/send group messages. I have clicked on the message to auto configure based on VZW configuration but it doesn't appear to do anything. STEPS See OBSERVATIONS EXPECTED I expect the message to go to the group and I expect to receive group messages. OBSERVATIONS When I start a group conversation from another phone (adding myself as a recipient) I don't receive the message. If I start a group conversation, none of the recipients receive the message.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="272">
			<summary>Clicking the Call icone do nothing</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/732</url>
			<bugID>Issue #732</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		I've Huawei p9 nougat stock firmware unroot when i try to Call from qksms clicking on the Phone button in the messages view the app open the phone app, do not even paste the phone, just open the phone app,exdialer, don't start the call nor even paste the phone so i have to close exdialer go back to qksms read the phone number open exdialer and write it manually to call
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="273">
			<summary>Notification disappears when locked</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/735</url>
			<bugID>Issue #735</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		DESCRIPTION When the phone is locked or the screen turns off while QKSMS is open, the app still thinks it's visible and thus immediately removes the new notification. This can very easily cause messages to not be seen for some time if one isn't constantly checking their device. STEPS Open QKSMS and lock the phone (does not have to be in a conversation) From another device, send a text message to the locked phone Possibly observe a new message notification briefly pop up, then disappear EXPECTED When the screen is off, new message notifications should not disappear. OBSERVATIONS A new message notification will pop up, then disappear a second later. Upon unlocking the phone, there is no notification, but a quick-reply popup is on the screen and the message shows as unread in the conversation list.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="274">
			<summary>Can't send/receive MMS with Viettel mobile</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/739</url>
			<bugID>Issue #739</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		I don't known on your telecom that can active. I'm try with my telecom network in my country, it not active.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="275">
			<summary>Support MMS please</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/740</url>
			<bugID>Issue #740</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		DESCRIPTION I don't send and receive MMS, and when I open source, I see source is commented.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="276">
			<summary>QKSMS does not fill the screen on the Samsung Galaxy S8</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/743</url>
			<bugID>Issue #743</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		DESCRIPTION QKSMS does not fill the screen on the Samsung Galaxy S8 STEPS Have a Samsung Galaxy S8 Open or switch to QKSMS EXPECTED The app should fill the screen except for the Android navigation buttons at the bottom of the screen OBSERVATIONS There is a small strip across the top and bottom of the app where you can see the the last thing on the screen before opening or switching to QKSMS. Here you can see the top and bottom edge of my home-screen, including cut off labels for the bottom-most apps: 👍 2
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="277">
			<summary>QKReply not working at all.</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/744</url>
			<bugID>Issue #744</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		I'm not getting the QK Reply popup at all (or it disappears instantly, hard to tell) when I receive a message. It doesn't matter whether my screen is on/off or what I'm doing. I have Huawei Nova, with the new EMUI 5.0/Android 7.0 update.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="278">
			<summary>Misschalaneous issues</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/746</url>
			<bugID>Issue #746</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		DESCRIPTION A short description of the issue. Example: Conversations aren't marked as read when they are opened from a notification. STEPS Steps to reproduce the issue. EXPECTED Describe the expected behaviour. OBSERVATIONS Describe what happens instead of the expected behaviour.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="279">
			<summary>QKSMS requests that the application be set as the default. Continuously</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/748</url>
			<bugID>Issue #748</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		DESCRIPTION Hi i have huawei honor 7 lite (proably is called huawei P9 lite or 5c on the American market). I'm after update android with 6.0 on 7.0 and QKSMS still asks me about set visible in the title. Problem in that it... is set but app does not recognize it. Because of this, I have an annoying message every time if i want to send a message. Reinstall application unfortunately doesn't work :( STEPS update android 6.0 to 7.0 (my phone have 6.0 factory) run QKSMS QKSMS request set default app. I click ok (even i checked in settings phone - is marked as default) Normal write SMS/MMS Disable app, run again and AGAIN asks about the same.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="280">
			<summary>Widget - update after new SMS</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/749</url>
			<bugID>Issue #749</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		DESCRIPTION Widget isn't updated (refreshed) after SMS sent. STEPS Send SMS either from the widget (Screenshot_01) or from the main app (Screenshot_03). EXPECTED The widget updates after SMS sent and contains the sent SMS, as seen in Screenshot_02 and Screenshot_04 in the &quot;Messaging&quot; widget. OBSERVATIONS The widget isn't updated after SMS sent, as seen in Screenshot_02 and Screenshot_04 in the &quot;Conversations&quot; (qksms) widget. Notes: I used qksms to send both SMS &quot;Test&quot; and &quot;Test2&quot;. qksms is set as the default messaging app. I don't have gapps installed Screenshot_01: Screenshot_02: Screenshot_03: Screenshot_04: Sysinfo:
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="281">
			<summary>App icon still shows unread message</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/752</url>
			<bugID>Issue #752</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		WhenI delete the message from the popup the app icon still shows unread message with a &quot;1&quot;. Will not clear until I receive a second message and I do not delete from the popup but I go to the App and delete from there. I love the App and will donate when I have used it for awhile and decide to keep it. Thanks, Art Cooke
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="282">
			<summary>Mms not sending on Verizon s6</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/754</url>
			<bugID>Issue #754</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		I have a galaxy s6 with Verizon both automatic and manual apn setting don't seem to be working. I can send pictures on the stock messenger but not on here any ideas on how to fix this DESCRIPTION A short description of the issue. Example: Conversations aren't marked as read when they are opened from a notification. STEPS Steps to reproduce the issue. EXPECTED Describe the expected behaviour. OBSERVATIONS Describe what happens instead of the expected behaviour.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="283">
			<summary>Is this app abandoned?</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/756</url>
			<bugID>Issue #756</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Just curious if it is.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="284">
			<summary>Notification doesn't show on lock screen.</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/757</url>
			<bugID>Issue #757</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		DESCRIPTION Been using this app for a few days and am having an issue. For some reason, notification do not show on my lock screen. They show up in the notification drawer when the phone is unlocked just fine, but don't show on lock screen. Using Honor 8 on Android 6.0. STEPS Receive text message. Press power button. EXPECTED Notification on lock screen should show when message is received and has not been read. Should show either sender, or sender and message depending on privacy. OBSERVATIONS No notification shown on lockscreen for received text. Other notifications (e.g. Pushbullet) show up fine.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="285">
			<summary>notification LED not working on Huawei P9 Lite (Android 7.0)</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/758</url>
			<bugID>Issue #758</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		DESCRIPTION I am running an Huawei P9 Lite with Android with EMUI-Version 5.0 and Android 7.0. When I recieve a message I can hear the notifcitation sound but the notification LED is not blinking. STEPS recieve message wait for LED to blink EXPECTED The LED should blink. OBSERVATIONS The LED does not blink.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="286">
			<summary>App icon not showing unread message count on Huawei P9 Lite (Android 7.0)</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/759</url>
			<bugID>Issue #759</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		DESCRIPTION I am running an Huawei P9 Lite with Android with EMUI-Version 5.0 and Android 7.0 and QKSMS is set a standard messaging app. When I recieve a message the App icon does not get an unread messages counter. STEPS recieve message take a look at the App icon EXPECTED The App icon should get an unread messages counter. OBSERVATIONS An unread messages counter is added to the former messaging app.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="287">
			<summary>Feature req : Delay / program one particular SMS</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/760</url>
			<bugID>Issue #760</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Hi, After trying different SMS apps, I fixed on QKSMS. QKSMS allows for delaying the sending of every SMS throug the parameters. It would be great to have control on the sending time of a given SMS. That possibilty would appear when writing SMS, through an option when pushing the &quot;+&quot; button on the right. The clock that appear would allow to parameter in the same screen for the message being written, the sending time. This new feature allows to program for SMS sending. Thx for reading ! Pierre 👍 1
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="288">
			<summary>Not Sending SMS via Samsung Galaxy S7</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/761</url>
			<bugID>Issue #761</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		DESCRIPTION All attempts to send SMS to someone in my Contacts fail, even after repeated attempts. STEPS Click icon for draft new message Draft it (a short one) App says it's &quot;sending ....&quot; which continues for a minute or two Eventually, the app gives me an alerts saying the attempt to send the message &quot;Failed.&quot; Repeated attempts to send or re-send yield the same failed result. EXPECTED An SMS app should both send and receive SMS messages easily and quickly. And at all. OBSERVATIONS Send the message. Give info on why it failed to send. Offer a Help button/function. Offer a User's Manual or Tutorial for Troubleshooting. It shouldn't be so hard to perform such a basic function.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="289">
			<summary>Force close when setting no notification sound</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/762</url>
			<bugID>Issue #762</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		DESCRIPTION Force close when user attempts to set no notification sound for conversation. STEPS Open conversation Enter conversation settings Change the notification sound (e.g. using the default system audio picker) to no sound App crashes Settings is not saved, notification sound remains unchanged EXPECTED After selecting no sound I expect there will be no sound notification for selected conversation. OBSERVATIONS It's not possible to set no sound notification. App crashes.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="290">
			<summary>Project Fi configuration</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/764</url>
			<bugID>Issue #764</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		DESCRIPTION Auto Configuration on Pixel w/Project Fi after not receiving some texts. STEPS n/a, just auto configuration EXPECTED Auto config to specific or various service providers to receive texts. OBSERVATIONS Have installed a new SIM and QKSMS pop-up noted need to auto config. It set Sprint as service, but Project Fi switches btw Sprint, TMo, and US Cellular. Does QKSMS auto reconfig when the service switches automatically? If not, may explain missing texts. Thanks in advance for assistance.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="291">
			<summary>Use of deprecated Resources.getDrawable()</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/766</url>
			<bugID>Issue #766</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Hi there, I just found that QKSMS is still using Resources.getDrawable() on line 477 in ThemeManager.java and line 260 in SwipeBackLayout.java. This API has been deprecated since Android 23 and I have found that you have already used ContextCompat.getDrawable() at other locations in QKSMS. I think it's better to replace all the usages of this deprecated API. Thanks!
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="292">
			<summary>app hanged when searching conversation</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/768</url>
			<bugID>Issue #768</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		DESCRIPTION App hanged if I empty search bar after filling it. STEPS Click the search icon Enter any search filter Empty search bar (backspace all the way) Hang EXPECTED Search bar should be able to be filled and emptied numerous time. OBSERVATIONS The application hanged.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="293">
			<summary>QKSMS closes completely when swiped from task manager</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/769</url>
			<bugID>Issue #769</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		When QKSMS is closed by swiping it away in the task manager, it doesn't run in background and is unable to receive any message until opened again. The messages that were not received won't ever be received, even when the app is opened again. (Wiko Ufeel Prime) Open QKSMS From your task manager, swipe the app to one side in order to close it. QKSMS would normally stay open in background and be able to check for new messages. Instead, new messages are never received. I don't know if this is specific to my phone, but I think so because it is quite annoying and more people would be complaining. I have the (bad) habit of &quot;closing&quot; all apps from the task manager, and with QKSMS I miss many messages... The problem was seemingly &quot;solved&quot; by adding hideFromRecents:true to the manifest (by the way, am I allowed to do so, since I don't redistribute the apk ? I do think I won't receive updates though, but anyway I needed to fix this) ; then QKSMS doesn't show in the task manager and hence can't be closed. There are probably other ways of doing this more properly, but I've never actually done any Android programming, so any fix that worked quick was fine for me. I just wanted you to be aware of that. Thanks for reading :) And if I'm not allowed to do this, please tell me, I'll uninstall the apk, delete all files and install the official Google Play app again.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="294">
			<summary>[Feature] Make &quot;private notifications&quot; setting also per-conversation</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/775</url>
			<bugID>Issue #775</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Wouldn't it be great if there was a way to choose &quot;private notifications&quot; setting per conversation? Expect a pull request soon ;)
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="295">
			<summary>Multiple Conversations - Same Contact Though</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/777</url>
			<bugID>Issue #777</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		After installing QKSMS and opening it, I have several conversations that show up where it is the same person I am texting with, but some of the texts show in one conversation and some show in another one. I used SMS Backup and Restore to download the SMS information to XML and I can see where some of the messages show the contact's number in the a variety of formats like: +1 (aaa) bbbcccc +1aaabbbcccc (aaa) bbbcccc I am not 100% sure what caused this. I did install a contact number formatting app that did appear to clean up and standardize my contact's numbers, but that does not seem to have helped this. This seems to have the effect of splitting the conversations with the same person in to multiple threads/conversations within QKSMS. Worth noting, Textra and Google Messages do not exhibit this behavior. They both show all of the messages under one conversation with that contact. Is there something that can be done with QKSMS to have it work in the same way, or perhaps have an option available to &quot;clean up&quot; the text message database to allow it to then display things in this same way? Thank you.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="296">
			<summary>No notification sound/vibration when conversation window open</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/778</url>
			<bugID>Issue #778</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		DESCRIPTION If the conversation window is left open and a new message comes in there is no notification tone or vibration. This happens if the screen is on or locked/off STEPS open a conversation wait for a message no sound if one comes in EXPECTED A notification! :-) OBSERVATIONS This is the same behavior as the android messaging app - which is why downloaded this in the hope that wasn't the case. as this is open source, there's a chance it can be fixed :-)
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="297">
			<summary>Notification badge is shown for blocked conversations</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/780</url>
			<bugID>Issue #780</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		DESCRIPTION Blocked conversations are marked as unread and shows badge icon counter on the app icon. Even if you manually open each blocked conversation and turn off notifications there they are still displayed on unread counter badge. Samsung Galaxy S8. STEPS Receive new message to blocked conversations (spam messages are received from the text name sender, not number, if that matters). EXPECTED Not showing badge counter for blocked conversations (may be set it toggle).
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="298">
			<summary>Notification turned off icon changes only after app restarted</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/781</url>
			<bugID>Issue #781</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		DESCRIPTION Notification icon in conversations list is shown only after the application is restarted. Galaxy S8 STEPS Open conversation Turn off notifications for it (touch the button) Go back to conversations list &quot;no notification&quot; icon is not displayed Restart the application Icon is displayed in conversation list EXPECTED Icon should be displayed without app restart OBSERVATIONS Icon is displayed in conversation list till the app is restarted
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="299">
			<summary>Feature request: show unread counter badge on the app icon for notification turned off conversations</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/782</url>
			<bugID>Issue #782</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		DESCRIPTION When notification is turned off for some conversations (not blocked ones) the badge counter icon is not shown upon receiving the new messages to that conversations, no other notifications are shown also. So you will never know (till you open the app) that there are new unread messages. Instead of that the unread counter badge is shown for new messages in blocked conversations.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="300">
			<summary>Feature request: Use android OS sound\vibration settings</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/783</url>
			<bugID>Issue #783</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		It would be great if vibration will turn on only when the vibration is turned on in android settings (when notification sound is turned off), so when sound is on - only sound notification is used, when sound is off - vibration.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="301">
			<summary>SwipeBackLayout doesn't show conversationList when swipe or back pressed KITKAT api 19</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/787</url>
			<bugID>Issue #787</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		when I swipe left to right on kitkat the conversationList doesnt show then after a while it comes up
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="302">
			<summary>[Feature Request] Mailing-List of SMS</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/791</url>
			<bugID>Issue #791</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Hello, First, thank you for your hard work, I switched recently to QKSMS. And it works well, so I'll keep it. I come here (is this the right channel?) because I have a little project to implement on top of QKSMS, but I lost myself a bit in the amount of code here. I hope you could hint me to the right answer? Situation A friend of me can't download nor update new apps on her old phone, and it's not practical for grouped conversation with other friends. So we are limited to SMS, but they don't handle grouped conversation very well either, the single thread for sending and receiving sms don't work. Solutions I aim to get a single threads of grouped messages for each people in our little group. Like sending and receiving messages from/to a mailing list but with SMS. I took a look at SMS gateways (OVH is a little expensive, 0.07€/sms) and the GroupMe app works only in the US :/ So, hey, I thought, I'm relatively used to code, so let's develop it ! Implementation I have a second SIM card for my phone (so, a spare phone number). Basically, a solution can be to send messages to a particular phone number (a sms server phone). It contains a (hardcoded?) list of recipients, their phone numbers and their nickname. This phone checks if the SMS is from a particular list of phone numbers (my friends), and checks if it starts with a specific string, like a 'G'. if that's the case, it lightly reformats the message body (to add a sender nickname). Then it transfers the message to the others people in the group. That's it, no need for dynamic changes for now. The question(s) Supposing everything is well defined until here, my questions to implement it is : Should the code to read and analyze received sms should be in an override of MessagingReceiver.onReceive method or in another place ? Is the HeadlessSmsSendService.onHandleIntent method the right one to call to transfer the SMS to the others recipients ? Thank you for your patience for this very long message :)
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="303">
			<summary>Performance issues</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/793</url>
			<bugID>Issue #793</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		I am unsure if this is actually my device or if there is a problem with QKSMS, but I figured I'll post an issue here just in case there is a bug somewhere in QKSMS causing it. So, a description of what is happening is the application becomes slow and begins to lag after being open (even when switched to from other apps) for a long period of time. Specifically, inputting text becomes very sluggish and navigating around message threads is very sluggish. Usually terminating the app through the Android recent apps screen speeds it back up. It seems like there may be a memory leak somewhere. If I find some time, I'll load a dev version of the app on my phone and see if I can do some profiling. Maybe ADB can help me identify the specific issue. If I diagnose the issue, I'll see if I can put a PR together. Just curious if anybody else is having performance issues. Steps to reproduce: Use QKSMS for an extended period of time Use the app normally Here is some device information App version: 2.7.3 Android version: 7.1.1 Device: Motorola Z2 Force Keyboard app: SwiftKey
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="304">
			<summary>Not able to create group when sending sms to multiple contacts</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/794</url>
			<bugID>Issue #794</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		When I compose new message and add multiple contacts and then send text to them they are inserted to separate threads rather than creating a new conversation thread
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="305">
			<summary>Saving draft messagers</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/795</url>
			<bugID>Issue #795</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		I really like this app, but i have not one small thing about save draft messagers, eg: once you have chosen a contact, then typed your message, and back out off the messaging app. It will save the draft but with no contact , and it cant be seen in main menu. So you have to go back into messaging, draft text is there but again no contact saved, so your having to type the contact again. Could you please look into this issue. Since i regualary use this app. But bit would help if this feature was fixed or added ? Thanks Regards Sob
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="306">
			<summary>Red number, despite no new texts</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/796</url>
			<bugID>Issue #796</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Even though I've read (and re-read, just in case) all the texts in QKSMS, the icon in Android has a red circle with 9. Recently 8. It keeps climbing. This is probably due to spam texts that the Should I Answer? app is deleting. Maybe QKSMS it's hiding those texts instead of deleting them? That makes the red number unhelpful. To see what I'm seeing, get a phone number that spammers have, install QKSMS and Should I Answer? apps, link them in the QKSMS settings, and wait for the spammers to send texts.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="307">
			<summary>Fullscreen and using AndroidBug5497Workaround</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/799</url>
			<bugID>Issue #799</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		I'm trying to use what's become the standard workaround for fixing the hidden layout issue caused by the keyboard in fullscreen mode/themes, &quot;AndroidBug5497Workaround&quot; and am having a really hard time figuring out where to place the class and how to implement it in QKSMS. See it here: https://stackoverflow.com/questions/7417123/android-how-to-adjust-layout-in-full-screen-mode-when-softkeyboard-is-visible/18249145#18249145 I'm still a beginner, but I've tried pretty blindly a few times, but nothing. Can this work? If so, a guide (for a newbie) or just sharing the relevant files where you successfully implemented it would be extremely helpful, and much appreciated. Compensation could also be arranged :-)
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="308">
			<summary>&quot;parse error&quot; on v3 APKs</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/806</url>
			<bugID>Issue #806</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		I'm trying to install QKSMS-v3.0.0-Preview-03.apk from Github, but I get: Parse error
There was a problem parsing the package.
 I have &quot;System Settings &gt; Security &gt; Unknown Sources: checked&quot;. I have tried downloading from the phone and from FF on Linux and nothing works, so I don't think it's APK D/L corruption. I've also tried QKSMS-v3.0.0-Preview-02.apk but I get the same error. FDroid install of 2.7.3 works, but I get the &quot;sending...&quot; forever bug in a group text, so trying v3 per #270. 2.7.3 does seem to eventually send, but it's not really usable. Using MMS settings as per https://www.mintsim.com/setup-for-android/ and thus far no amount of fiddling with settings (2.7.3) has helped so I was really hoping v3 would... Note I'm running Android 4.4.4 on an old Blackphone1 that has NO Google services of any kind (no store, no push, no nothing).
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="309">
			<summary>Fix Travis build</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/813</url>
			<bugID>Issue #813</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		No description provided.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="310">
			<summary>Group message/quick reply support?</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/828</url>
			<bugID>Issue #828</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Hi, noticed that you're working again with a new version of the app...I missed it... Anyway, are you going add group messages and quick reply/mark read support? Thanks
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="311">
			<summary>[BUG] MMS image different size displayed</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/922</url>
			<bugID>Issue #922</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Device: OnePlus 2 A2001 Version: 7.1.2 When attaching an MMS then the size of the image (when in the conversation) differs depending on the length of the caption. Should this not be consistent throughout?
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="312">
			<summary>[Request] Swipe back from a conversation</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/925</url>
			<bugID>Issue #925</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		It would be a QOL improvement
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="313">
			<summary>Proposal for an icon and a logo type for the application</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/939</url>
			<bugID>Issue #939</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Hello my name is Richard Caseres I am a graphic designer and I like to make contributions for open source projects from the graphic and advertising point of view. in this opportunity I contact you to propose a new icon and a logo more personalized and more current for your application in development this in order to give a better image to your project. I develop within the platform Utopian.io with blockchain of steemit, the rewards I receive from them however they require me to contact the developer of the project so that they can verify that my logo proposal will be used in the project and so do not compensate contributions that will not be used in the projects. Here I show you a model of the proposal of the logo if it is of tua degree I can provide you all the necessary files within a contribution in GitHub to be added to your project. So that within Utopian-io my contribution to your project is valid you must place on the main page of the project on GitHub an application for a new logo or icon as a contribution to your project to simply demonstrate that you will use the new icon and the new logo. Well I hope you like my proposal, thank you very much for your time to read this and I hope we are in contact. Greetings. 😕 1
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="314">
			<summary>GIFs asking who to send it to</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/940</url>
			<bugID>Issue #940</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		When you go to send a GIF from Gboard inside a conversation it asks who want to send it to instead of just attaching in the conversation
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="315">
			<summary>Some feedback from a daily user</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/956</url>
			<bugID>Issue #956</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Hi moezbhatti I'm using QKSMS 3.0 for a while now, and hereby I would like to write down my concerns, suggestions: Missing: avatar in notifications: I really would like to see who send me a message in a glimp (I see this is already on the to-do-list) Suggestions: please include the translations (I translated Dutch already) make the font inside the text-bubbles a little bit bigger, it's really small now Reconsider the colors in the dark theme. On my OnePlus 5t I can't see a difference between the dark background and the text-bubbles maybe some new icon so it looks more like the previous one (see below) On the conversationlist: maybe make the 'search'-bar like the themecolor? It looks so bright now don't show only emojis-messages inside a textbubble always show the timestamp of the latest message Bugs Color from avatar doesn't change to theme you set for that contact in the conversationlit (already reported) With the new QK reply: when you send a message with another app (Join) it doesn't show up in the QK reply window but it is visible in the app the automatic dark mode doesn't work on my OnePlus 5T Hope it is some constructive feedback ;) Many, many thanks for this app and that you listen to the community (something Pulse doesn't). Kind regards Jari
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="316">
			<summary>Scroll to top</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/974</url>
			<bugID>Issue #974</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		When you reply to a message that is on 2nd (or below) place in the conversationlist, and you go back to the conversation list, the message goes to the top of the list but the view doesn't. So you don't see the thread you just replied to. It would be nice if the thread is shown as first (so that the menu would scroll to the top). Pfoe, difficult to explain 😅
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="317">
			<summary>No update on F-droid</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/982</url>
			<bugID>Issue #982</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Hello dear devs ! I haven't saw issues about this, but I've seen that the F-droid apk have not been updated for 1 years ago and I don't want to download Qksms from Android Playstore. So, can you please update this on the F-droid repository? Thanks for your help.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="318">
			<summary>App does not wake phone/give notification when new SMS is received</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/987</url>
			<bugID>Issue #987</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		This is something I've experienced with both 3.0 and the old versions of QKSMS, and I'm honestly unsure whether it's on my end or a problem with the app. About 20% of the time, the app won't &quot;wake&quot; the phone and give me a sound/vibration. I only realize a new message is received once I open the app and see the message. When I used the old QKSMS I even converted it to a system app but it would still &quot;ignore&quot; about 5-10% of messages and wouldn't give a notification at all. I've pondered whether the app is underprivileged and could use 1 or 2 more permissions to successfully wake the phone 100% of the time. My phone is rooted and I'm sure that it has all the requested permissions. I haven't experienced this issue with neither the stock SMS app nor Textra, which makes me think it might be an issue with QKSMS. Is this something anyone else has experienced? I'd be happy to debug it if someone tells me how to do it. I've got CatLog installed but it seems hard to reproduce/test.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="319">
			<summary>Cannot receive MMS, maybe causing wakelock as well</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/998</url>
			<bugID>Issue #998</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		I am using QKSMS 2.7.3 on Fairphone Open with XPrivacy and AFWall+ on a Fairphone 2. The app cannot receive any MMS (sending only when enabling some foreign apps in AFWall+ and disabling WLAN, for some reason) and seems to create a wake lock as well, thus draining my battery very fast. Is that a bug or did I do anything wrong? Fairphone forum thread incoming MMS: https://forum.fairphone.com/t/qksms-and-incoming-mms/39178?u=hansibert Fairphone forum post wakelock: https://forum.fairphone.com/t/another-hot-fp2-with-empty-battery/39245/5?u=hansibert
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="320">
			<summary>Search does not appear to have indexed all conversations</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/1007</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1007</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Problem If I search the inbox for a word, an incomplete list of instances returns. Attempts to fix Re-sync with android database in settings Version Info QKSMS 3.0.4 (fresh install), LineageOS 14.1 Edit: After playing around with it today, it seems it's just returning a list of names that match, rather than search terms. In this case, is searching texts a planned feature?
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="321">
			<summary>[Question] Why were all the features removed?</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/1016</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1016</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		So I see in the new 3.0 versions that all the features have been taken out and now must be paid for. Will ALL of the old features be added back for at least qksms+ users? Also I see there is a new version on F-Droid but not yet available on G Play. Is the F-Droid version still a beta?
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="322">
			<summary>QK compose missing?</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/1017</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1017</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		after I updated QKSMS, the QK Compose feature disappeared. is there any way to bring it back?
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="323">
			<summary>Request: Disable avatars</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/1030</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1030</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		I don't like the contact images. I can read, after all. 👍 1
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="324">
			<summary>Can't select multiple conversation</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/1032</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1032</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Hi there, I installed QKSMS through F-Driod and in last update I got QKSMS+. Everything looks and works fine but that a feature that I really miss is selecting multiple conversation which was available in QKSMS. Hope to see this feature back as I am sure it is useful for many of us. Cheers! 👍 1 ❤️ 1
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="325">
			<summary>Improvements</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/1044</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1044</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Hello! Great app, really love it! I have a few suggestion to make it even better: Option to delete multiple messages at once. When selecting QK Reply, the heads-up should not show up as well. When selecting QK Reply, should be an option to make it appear from pressing the heads-up notification, not automatically, so that you dont have to enter the application. Selecting the colour of a conversation should change the bubble with the letter as well. (Optional, but eager to see) Option to set different patterns of vibration (maybe for different contacts). A wake-up screen option (for phones that dont have such a feature). Thank you for your work and soon I'll buy + edition, but I really hope that at least 1,2,3 will be part of the app.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="326">
			<summary>Android webview crashes</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/1045</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1045</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		DESCRIPTION When I first open the app and go to a conversation my Android System Webview sends a crash popup STEPS Open app go to any conversation OBSERVATIONS Only happens on first opening of the app, doesn't crash if I open it then go back to the all conversations menu then go into a different conversation.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="327">
			<summary>hi</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/1052</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1052</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		DESCRIPTION A short description of the issue. Example: Conversations aren't marked as read when they are opened from a notification. STEPS Steps to reproduce the issue. EXPECTED Describe the expected behaviour. OBSERVATIONS Describe what happens instead of the expected behaviour.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="328">
			<summary>Google Error Message When I Try to &quot;Donate&quot; or Upgrade to &quot;Lifetime Upgrade&quot; - On F-driod Version.</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/1056</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1056</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		DESCRIPTION This issue is about a bug on your application, and its making you lose chances of being appreciated for your wonderful work. Your application is wonderful and very useful, but there is a problem with the version on F-driod. When i tried to make a donation or upgrade to &quot;lifetime upgrade&quot;, i got a Google Error message, which completely hindered me from making the donation, and upgrading. I discovered that a similar issue was raised 2 years ago, but was later closed. I assume that it was closed because the issue had been resolved. But, i'm bringing it to your notice that the error still occurs on F-driod version. I tried out the version on Google Play, and its working very fine, and i got no error message. Please Note The Following: The version on Google Play Store is still on 2.7.3 after the update. F-driod can't use Google in-app billing. Please dump the version in Google Play Store and place some alternative for F-driod version. STEPS Download QKSMS from F-droid Launch the application Click on menu on the top left of the application Go to &quot;QKSMS+&quot; Click on &quot;donate+unlock&quot;, a google error message comes up. Click on &quot;life time upgrade&quot;, a google error message also comes up. EXPECTED I expect that clicking on &quot;donate&quot; or &quot;life time upgrade&quot; will bring up a means of payment to support the developer for his great work or upgrade to a higher level. OBSERVATIONS Clicking on &quot;Donate&quot; and/or &quot;life time upgrade&quot; brings up a google error message. https://youtu.be/jTZFCKA4c6A This bug report can also be found on utopian-io 👍 5 ❤️ 1
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="329">
			<summary>[Q] Possibility to change the status bar color ?</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/1066</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1066</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		DESCRIPTION Hello, I upgraded the application to 3.0.7 on my phone, I was at the screen in version 2.7.3. On the old version, it was possible to change both the color of the circles representing the different contacts as well as the color of the top space in contact with the status bar. On this new version, it is apparently only possible to change the color of the circles representing the contacts. Has the one to change the &quot;top&quot; color of the application been implemented or is it not yet available? EXPECTED No option to change the status bar color OBSERVATIONS There is no option to changing the &quot;top&quot; color of the app. Thanks in advance.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="330">
			<summary>Sending MMS is broken</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/1080</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1080</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		DESCRIPTION Since the latest update (installed via F-Droid), sending MMS isn't possible anymore and fails immediately without even trying, resulting in the &quot;Error sending message. Tap to retry.&quot; message. STEPS Add image to message Hit &quot;send&quot; Admire result EXPECTED The MMS gets sent. OBSERVATIONS &quot;Error sending message. Tag to retry.&quot; Tapping it makes the view jump up and scroll down again, with nothing happening.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="331">
			<summary>Wrong contact color</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/1084</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1084</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		DESCRIPTION When having contacts in conversation that do not have an image assigned they are sharing the same background color (cyan) Example: I have a conversation with S and a conversation with L. In QKSMS they both have cyan color when in Android Messages S is red and only L is cyan. STEPS Have two conversations with people that do not have custom images assigned Observe the color asignment EXPECTED Conversation colors to be randomly assigned OBSERVATIONS Is this a feature not supported in the FREE version of the app? QKSMS version 3.0.9
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="332">
			<summary>Not possible to copy or delete messages with an email in it</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/1085</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1085</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		No description provided.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="333">
			<summary>Add GitHub link to description in Play Store</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/1087</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1087</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		I don't use the Play Store, but I looked at QKSMS there, and noticed that mentions that QKSMS is open source, but there's no link to the source in the description. https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.moez.QKSMS 👍 3
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="334">
			<summary>Lost all messages prior to update</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/1094</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1094</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		DESCRIPTION I hadnt really looked but I went to send my wife a text for the first time since the update and it says &quot;This is the start of your conversation&quot; and nothing is there. So I went into all my other contacts and its the same way. Now I go into another SMS/MMS app and its all there. QKSMS has no record of any messages prior to the upgrade. STEPS Steps to reproduce the issue. EXPECTED Describe the expected behaviour. OBSERVATIONS Describe what happens instead of the expected behaviour.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="335">
			<summary>Remove setup request as the default SMS app at startup</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/1096</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1096</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Hi, Possibly if you could remove the initial message at startup that asks you to set the app as default for SMS messages every time, it's pretty annoying, thanks
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="336">
			<summary>Is this a feature of the app?</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/1097</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1097</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		I got a message from my operator about missed calls but in that message just before the phone numbers were listed, there were the contact names written just as I've got them saved on my phone. Like this: You got a missed call from contact name phone number So is this QK grabbing info of that number and putting it in the message for ease of use or is my operator somehow lurking in my contacts list?
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="337">
			<summary>Need advice on how to make my own theme</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/1102</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1102</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		DESCRIPTION I was wondering if theres a easy way to change the UI like modifying the look of the send button, the place where we type our text, the bubble text, remove icons. if not can anyone guide me on where i should modify the code to achieve this? STEPS N/A EXPECTED N/A OBSERVATIONS N/A
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="338">
			<summary>Add Fingerprint/Incognito Mode</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/1109</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1109</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Enhancement to have fingerprint before entering app, or access certain messages with fingerprint. Incognito mode or another type of private box for certain threads.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="339">
			<summary>Proposed logo</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/1111</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1111</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Hi @moezbhatti! im k-syusteem, this is my first contribution to GOLEM, I have designed a logo that is a minimalist and clean logo. Give me feedback if you like this, and I am also welcome if any suggestions for improvement. 👎 1
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="340">
			<summary>Double tapping space removes the last letter of the word and then adds the period and space.</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/1127</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1127</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		DESCRIPTION After the latest update (3.1.2) and using the SwiftKey app, when you double tap space to add a period, it will delete the last letter of the word and add the period and space. STEPS Every time you double tap space. EXAMPLE If I type &quot;Hello&quot; and double tap space it will result in &quot;Hell. &quot; I am using SwiftKey to reproduce this issue which only occurs while using QKSMS. If I switch to the LG Keyboard the double tap space doesn't add a space after the period at all. QKSMS Version: 3.1.2 Device: LG V30+ OS: 7.1.2 Android
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="341">
			<summary>Almost all messages show up twice -- major bug</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/1131</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1131</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Started using 3.1.3, and for some reason almost all messages show up twice. I jumped from 3.0.9 to 3.1.3 so it could have happened anywhere between those updates. Anyone else experiencing this? I attached some screenshots; if you are able to see any sort of pattern or reason for this, it's beyond me. And just to be clear: the messages are only displayed twice, they are not sent twice. Using Android Nougat 7.0.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="342">
			<summary>Group Names</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/1132</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1132</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Feature Request: for group messaging make it possible to assign a conversation name to the group message. So in the conversation list it's one custom name instead of all the contacts names.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="343">
			<summary>Send button can't be tapped after creating a new message</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/1135</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1135</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		DESCRIPTION When I try to create a new message, I choose the contact, type the message and then I can't press the send button, it does nothing when tapped. STEPS Tap the + fab Choose a contact Type anything Press send button, it does nothing in my case. EXPECTED Send button should just send the message. OBSERVATIONS My phone is Huawei P10 Lite, stock 7.0, not rooted.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="344">
			<summary>Resize text box while typing</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/1140</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1140</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		DESCRIPTION Text box won't resize unless you stop writing for a second STEPS Type a longer message and see that on the second line that box doesnt resize
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="345">
			<summary>Improvement: Pressing the heads-up message will show the conversation without opening the app</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/1142</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1142</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		I saw this feature on some messages app and I really like. You can see the whole conversation with that person without having to open the app, because it opens a window from where you can type.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="346">
			<summary>Improvement: Pressing the heads-up message will show the conversation without opening the app (Again)</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/1144</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1144</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		I was saying that the app won't auto-show the conversation, but by pressing the heads-up. Textra has something very similar, by using it you can understand what I am referring to. Also, the app should not close after sending a message, having to dismiss it by taping somewhere else on the screen
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="347">
			<summary>[Suggestion] Create a dedicated QKSMS+ app</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/1147</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1147</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		I'd love to purchase QKSMS+, but in-app purchases aren't shared with family members. A dedicated QKSMS+ app would allow this. 👎 1
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="348">
			<summary>Attaching photos makes you choose a source</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/1152</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1152</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		When attaching photos now it makes you choose a source instead of allowing you to choose from multiple sources
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="349">
			<summary>Suggestion for the to do list you made.</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/1154</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1154</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Can you please indicate which things in your to do list will require qksms+? Perhaps mark them with a tag this way we can let people know if their request will require plus or not. I am referring to the place that says done, to do, backlog, up next, ect. Thank you!
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="350">
			<summary>New Message Suggestion</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/1158</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1158</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		DESCRIPTION When composing a new message, the conversation has to be found by backspacing the input. STEPS Hit the &quot;+&quot; Floating Action Button. Type a few letters of the name of the contact. When you select the contact, the name appears at the top. However, the letters you typed while searching are still there. In order to access the message field, you have to backspace. EXPECTED When a name is selected, the message history should immediately appear without backspacing. OBSERVATIONS Instead of the conversation appearing, you have to backspace the name if you partially typed it to view the conversation history.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="351">
			<summary>Add &quot;Solar Hijri calendar&quot; format option for messages timestamp.</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/1159</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1159</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		DESCRIPTION I want to try add &quot;Solar Hijri calendar&quot; format as an option for messages timestamp, if I could, will you merge my PR? 😊
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="352">
			<summary>Messages syncing forever?</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/1162</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1162</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		I'm having an issue with using this on Android 8.0 Oreo. When I start up the app, it offers the permissions and such to grant/set as default (which I accept) and then it begins &quot;Syncing Messages.&quot; It gets stuck here, though, and doesn't progress--even after several minutes. If it makes any difference, I'm on a Moto Z Play, unrooted, recently updated to Oreo, and also have a Substratum theme activated. The issue occurs on a fresh installation of the app (clear data + uninstall + reinstall) from F-Droid. A thing of note: I had the app set up and configured in the past, many versions ago, but left it for a while as MMS didn't really work for me. I'm trying to give it another go. Steps to Reproduce: Clear data and reinstall the app. Open app, grant permissions, watch as &quot;Syncing messages&quot; appears Enjoy the heat death of the universe Expected Result: Messages would sync, preferably with a progress bar of some sort, and then everything would work with absolutely no bugs. Actual Result: Stuck on &quot;Syncing messages&quot; at the main menu. Here's some more info: Version: 3.2.0 (F-Droid_ Device: motorola XT1635-02 (Moto Z Play, US) SDK: 26 (?) Carrier: T-Mobile
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="353">
			<summary>Notification when image has been received but not downloaded</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/1168</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1168</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		DESCRIPTION When I'm not on data, occasionally someone will send me an image via MMS. Not being on data, I obviously can't see it, but I'm not notified that an image was even sent. In the default LG messaging app, I do get notified, so I know to turn on data and download it. STEPS Disable mobile data Be sent an image via MMS EXPECTED A placeholder message tells you there is an image you can download. OBSERVATIONS I never know that I've been sent an image, unless they ask about it. 👍 1
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="354">
			<summary>Cannot send picture</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/1171</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1171</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		How to reproduce Instal QKSMS Open QKSMS Click conversations Send a picture But not working 👎 1
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="355">
			<summary>proposed for make new logo</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/1174</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1174</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		hallow sir I want to make a logo for this projects if you have any requirements then let me know.its free for any open source projects.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="356">
			<summary>[REQUEST]Random/Custom Color Themes on Maim Page</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/1175</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1175</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		DESCRIPTION Is it possible to add a randomized color theme to the main page of qksms like Android messages? It makes finding specific conversations much easier and would add more customization and color to the landing page.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="357">
			<summary>Emoticons not available</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/1177</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1177</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		DESCRIPTION Emoticons are not available from the keyboard. Version is 3.2.0 Android version is Lineage OS version 14.1-20180602-NIGHTLY-pme, based on Android 7.1.2, running on HTC10 STEPS Run the app Select an existing contact Click on the text field EXPECTED The keyboard displays with a dedicated touch/button to select emoticons OBSERVATIONS The keyboard button to display emoticons doesn't appear.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="358">
			<summary>Pinning Ability</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/1178</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1178</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Could you add the ability to pin conversations to the top of the main page. I feel that it's a small quality of life feature that's super helpful when you have important conversations you want to keep track of. 👍 1
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="359">
			<summary>Seeking info about QKSMS database</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/1180</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1180</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		It appears that QKSMS does not directly use the default android SMS database. I would like to understand more about how it works and what to expect, from the user perspective. Currently I am testing QKSMS, and do not have it set as my default sms app. I'm just trying to compare it to my default app. When I receive a new sms, it appears in my default app, but does not appear in QKSMS unless I manually re-sync messages. If I delete a message in QKSMS, it is not deleted in my default SMS app. If I delete a message in the default app, it is not deleted in QKSMS unless I manually re-sync messages. The databases do not appear to sync automatically. The manual re-sync appears to be a one-way sync from the default db to QKSMS. Is this correct? It's not clear if/how this would change if I did set QKSMS as my default app. It's also not clear what would happen if I use QKSMS for a while and later decide to switch to a different sms app. Would I loose messages that were received while QKSMS was the default app, or are they somehow copied to the default database? Overall this does not seem very transparent or friendly for new users. Putting some explanation into the wiki would be a good start.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="360">
			<summary>New Logo Design</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/1183</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1183</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		Hello, I want to offering you a new logo for your app?
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="361">
			<summary>improve time options when receiving SMS</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/1184</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1184</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		QKSMS just shows the time, when the SMS was received on my phone. Example: Phone gets switched off (or loses reception) at 1:00 and will be on the network again at 9:00. Someone sends a message at 2:00. Phone will display 9:00, and there is no way to figure out when the message really was sent. This is sometimes annoying e.g. if you are travelling and do not have full coverige all the time. Then you won't know if messages like &quot;I'm there now&quot; still are current or already old. STEPS Switch off phone Send a message from another phone to the phone number you switched off Wait for 5 minutes Switch the phone on again. For the message you'll only see the time when the phone was switched on, not the time when the message was sent. EXPECTED It would be nice to have the option: &quot;display sent/network time&quot;, or there is even enough space to display both times, if different. 👍 2
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="362">
			<summary>Soft buttons are invisible or barely rendered.</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/1197</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1197</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		The common Android buttons throughout most apps (triangle pointing down or left, circle, and square) are not rendered appropriately in QKSMS+, built by F-Droid. If you press where they should be, they function appropriately. If you look very closely, you can barely see the outlines of the buttons, so they are not totally invisible to the keen observer. No fancy steps to reproduce this issue. It occurs globally throughout QKSMS+. Thanks! 👍 1
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="363">
			<summary>Use swipe to refresh to sync messages</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/1204</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1204</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		It's better to use swipe to refresh to sync messages, instead of an option in the setting menu.
	</description>
		</report>
		<report Number="364">
			<summary>SMS verification code for 2FA not appearing</summary>
			<url>https://github.com/moezbhatti/qksms/issues/1206</url>
			<bugID>Issue #1206</bugID>
			<label>None yet</label>
			<description>
		DESCRIPTION I had a strange bug with QKSMS when trying to receive the verification code for turning on 2FA in my bit.ly account. After requesting the code, I didn't get any notification. A second time - still nothing. I even tried a third time the next day but still nothing. It was only after opening Android Messages and Pulse did I notice the phone numbers containing the verification codes, but they didn't show up in QKSMS. Huawei Nova 2i (Mate 10 Lite), 8.0 Oreo STEPS Request for a 2FA verification code Check if the code appears in QKSMS EXPECTED The 2FA verification code should appear in QKSMS, like it does in other SMS apps. OBSERVATIONS The verification code doesn't show up in QKSMS for some reason. 👍 1
	</description>
		</report>
	</reports>
